<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<gameList xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<game id="1468" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./1943 - The Battle of Midway (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>1943 : The Battle of Midway</name>
		<desc>A SEQUÊNCIA DE 1942, QUE AINDA É UM SHOOTER VERTICAL, FAZ O JOGADOR MAIS UMA VEZ LUTAR NAS NUVENS DURANTE A SEGUNDA GUERRA MUNDIAL, DESTA VEZ EM UMA INTENSA BATALHA PERTO DA COSTA DAS ILHAS MIDWAY.

ESSA NOVA VERSÃO INCLUI UMA BARRA DE ENERGIA, QUE DIMINUI QUANDO O JOGADOR É ATINGIDO OU POR USAR UMA ARMA ESPECIAL. A BARRA DE ENERGIA PODE SER REABASTECIDA COM POWER-UPS, ENQUANTO ARMAS ESPECIAIS (RAIOS, CICLONES E ONDAS) PODEM DERRUBAR TODOS OS OPONENTES NA TELA.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19881002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4BB5825E</hash>
		<image>./images/1943 - The Battle of Midway (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/1943 - The Battle of Midway (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/1943 - The Battle of Midway (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/1943 - The Battle of Midway (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1556" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./8 Eyes (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>8 Eyes</name>
		<desc>8 EYES NARRA AS AVENTURAS DE ORIN, O FALCOEIRO, QUE DEVE VISITAR OITO CASAS EM OITO TERRAS DIFERENTES E DERROTAR SEUS OITO GUARDIÕES, A FIM DE COLETAR OITO JOIAS CHAMADAS OLHOS. É UM JOGO DE AÇÃO / AVENTURA DE ROLAGEM LATERAL ONDE O PERSONAGEM PRINCIPAL PODE ATACAR COM UMA ESPADA DE ALCANCE UM POUCO LIMITADO. NO ENTANTO, ESSA NÃO É A FERRAMENTA MAIS PODEROSA À SUA DISPOSIÇÃO - ORIN TAMBÉM TEM SEU FIEL FALCÃO QUE ELE PODE MANDAR ATACAR INIMIGOS OU ACIONAR ALAVANCAS. NO MODO SINGLE-PLAYER, O JOGADOR CONTROLA TANTO O FALCOEIRO QUANTO O FALCÃO. NO ENTANTO, O JOGO TAMBÉM OFERECE UM MODO COOPERATIVO ONDE O PRIMEIRO JOGADOR CONTROLA ORIN E O SEGUNDO JOGADOR CONTROLA SEU FALCÃO EM UM MODO QUE OFERECE MAIOR CAPACIDADE DE VOO.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19900102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thinking Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>Taxan</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>13C668F2</hash>
		<image>./images/8 Eyes (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/8 Eyes (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/8 Eyes (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/8 Eyes (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18553" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Abadox (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Abadox : The Deadly Inner War</name>
		<desc>SOMEWHERE IN THE GALAXY, A HUGE ALIEN SPACE CREATURE KNOWN AS PARASITIS TRAVELS BETWEEN REALMS DIGESTING IT'S PRAY. IT'S LATEST VICTIM IS THE PLANET ABADOX WHICH IS NOW CONSUMED BY THE ALIEN ENTITY. HOWEVER, IN ORDER TO DIGEST THIS PLANET, PARASITIS HAS HAD TO ASSUME TO FORM OF THE PLANET ITSELF. ABADOX'S STARFLEET, THE WORLD ALIVE FORCE (WAF) USES THIS TIME TO LAUNCH AN ALL OUT ASSAULT ON THE ALIEN LIFEFORM, OF WHICH YOU ARE A SINGLE SOLDIER.

ABADOX IS A SIDE-SCROLLING SHOOTER. YOU MUST FIRE UPON VARIOUS ENEMIES THAT TRAVEL ACROSS THE SCREEN AND DESTROY THEIR BOSSES AS WELL. ONE BUTTON CONTROLS YOUR SHOOTING AND ANOTHER CONTROLS YOUR SHIELD ABILITY.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Milton Bradley Co.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E2687EC0</hash>
		<image>./images/Abadox (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Abadox (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Abadox (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Abadox (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1342" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hudson's Adventure Island (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island</name>
		<desc>NO PACÍFICO SUL, MASTER HIGGINS VIVIA EM PAZ VESTINDO APENAS UMA SAIA DE GRAMA E UM BONÉ ATÉ QUE O EVIL WITCH DOCTOR DECIDE CAPTURAR A PRINCESA LEILANI. CABE AO MASTER HIGGINS COLETAR MACHADOS, BOLAS DE FOGO E SKATES PARA AJUDAR SUA NOBRE BUSCA.

SENDO UM JOGO DE PLATAFORMA COM ROLAGEM LATERAL, MASTER HIGGINS SE MOVE PELA TELA DA ESQUERDA PARA A DIREITA E ENCONTRA POWER-UPS EM OVOS GIGANTES, COMO POR EXEMPLO UM SKATE QUE RESULTA EM UM GRANDE AUMENTO NA VELOCIDADE. AO SER ATINGIDO, MASTER HIGGINS PERDE SEU PODER. SE ELE NÃO ESTÁ EM UM SKATE, SER ATINGIDO SIGNIFICA MORTE INSTANTÂNEA. OUTRA MECÂNICA DO JOGO É A FOME, QUE É INDICADA ATRAVÉS DE UM MEDIDOR QUE DIMINUI CONSTANTEMENTE. SE CHEGAR A ZERO, O HERÓI MORRE E A ÚNICA MANEIRA DE PREENCHÊ-LO É COLETANDO COMIDA NO CAMINHO. CHEFES ESPERAM POR ELE NO FINAL DOS NÍVEIS, ATÉ O PRÓPRIO EVIL WITCH DOCTOR.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9778675E</hash>
		<image>./images/Hudson's Adventure Island (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Hudson's Adventure Island (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Hudson's Adventure Island (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hudson's Adventure Island (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1499" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Adventures of Lolo 3 (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Adventures of Lolo 3</name>
		<desc>THIS TIME, LOLO HAS A RED FRIEND WHO WILL DO FOR HIM SOME OF THE WORK. UNLIKE THE TWO PREVIOUS LOLO GAMES, HERE YOU CAN WANDER AROUND A WORLD MAP AND ENTER DIFFERENT LOCATIONS IN A NON-LINEAR FASHION. HOWEVER, SOME OF THE LOCATIONS REMAIN BLOCKED UNTIL YOU FIND A KEY AFTER COMPLETING ANOTHER LEVEL. 

THE GAMEPLAY IS VERY SIMILAR TO THE ONE OF THE TWO PREVIOUS GAMES. YOU HAVE TO COLLECT ALL THE HEARTS IN EACH ROOM. ENEMIES WILL PREVENT YOU FROM DOING THAT, AND OTHERS WILL APPEAR ONCE YOU HAVE EATEN ALL THE HEARTS AND ARE HURRYING TOWARDS THE EXIT. THE PUZZLES INVOLVE MOSTLY PUSHING THINGS TO PREVENT ENEMIES FROM STOPPING YOU.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1EE3AB9F</hash>
		<image>./images/Adventures of Lolo 3 (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Adventures of Lolo 3 (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Adventures of Lolo 3 (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Adventures of Lolo 3 (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1666" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Amagon (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Amagon</name>
		<desc>IN AMAGON, YOUR MISSION IS TO INVESTIGATE A DANGEROUS, MONSTER-INFESTED ISLAND.  AS AMAGON, YOU BEGIN THE GAME WITH ONLY A MACHINE GUN AND A LIMITED AMOUNT OF AMMO TO PROTECT YOURSELF FROM THE INHABITANTS OF THE ISLAND. GAMEPLAY IS AN ARCADE STYLE PLATFORM GAME WITH SIX LEVELS, EACH WITH A VARIETY OF CREATURES AND A LARGE BOSS AT THE END. WHEN YOU DESTROY AN ENEMY, A POWER UP WILL SOMETIMES BE LEFT BEHIND. COLLECTING THESE CAN GIVE YOU EXTRA POINTS, AN EXTRA LIFE, MORE AMMO, OR A MEGA KEY. IF YOU HAVE ENOUGH POINTS AND COLLECT A MEGA KEY, YOU THEN HAVE THE ABILITY TO TRANSFORM INTO MEGAGON. IN THIS FORM, YOU ARE LARGER IN SIZE, CAN JUMP FURTHER, AND HAVE INCREASED STRENGTH. YOU START THE TRANSFORMATION WITH AN AMOUNT OF MEGA POINTS; EACH TIME A CREATURE INJURES YOU, POINTS ARE LOST. WHEN ALL OF THE MEGA POINTS ARE GONE YOU WILL TRANSFORM BACK INTO YOUR NORMAL SIZE.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19890401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E1A7F162</hash>
		<image>./images/Amagon (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Amagon (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Amagon (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Amagon (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1391" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rygar (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Argos no Senshi</name>
		<desc>A HERO HAS ARRIVED TO DEFEAT THE FORCES OF EVIL IN THE LAND OF ARGOOL, AND YOU ARE THIS HERO. DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES? THIS GAME WAS ONE OF THE FIRST ADVENTURES TO HIT THE NES AND THE REMARKABLE ASPECT ON TOP OF THIS WAS THE MULTIPLE VIEWPOINTS THE GAMES OFFERS. WHEN YOU ARE IN AN ACTION ZONE, THE GAME IS A SIDE-SCROLLING ACTION GAME; HOWEVER, THEN YOU ARE TRAVELLING BETWEEN ZONES, THE GAME TAKES ON AN OVERHEAD VIEW THAT CAN ALSO LEAD TO COMBAT SITUATIONS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>294C22CF</hash>
		<image>./images/Rygar (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Rygar (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Rygar (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rygar (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1401" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Arkanoid (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Arkanoid</name>
		<desc>THE ORIGINAL BREAKOUT CONCEPT INVOLVES CONTROLLING A BAT AT THE BOTTOM OF THE SCREEN AND USING IT TO CATCH AND DIRECT A BALL SO AS TO HIT ALL THE BRICKS WHICH ARE ARRANGED AT THE TOP OF THE SCREEN. IT WAS UNPOPULAR FOR OVER A DECADE, BEFORE TAITO REVIVED IT WITH SOME NEW IDEAS IN THIS ARCADE GAME.

THE GAME'S PLOT REDEFINES THE BAT AS A VAUS SPACESHIP, THE BALL AS AN ENERGY BOLT, AND THE BRICKS FORM A MYSTERIOUS WALL STOPPING THE SHIP FROM PROGRESSING TO SAFETY.

BY THE MID-80S, POWER-UPS WERE POPULAR IN MOST TYPES OF ARCADE GAMES, AND ARKANOID FEATURES THEM. THEY ARE CAUGHT BY POSITIONING THE BAT BELOW THEM AS THEY FALL (MEANING THAT YOU RISK MISSING THE BALL IF YOU GO FOR THEM AT THE WRONG TIME). THE POWER-UPS INCLUDE LASERS (WHICH ARE MOUNTED TO EACH SIDE OF THE SHIP AND ALLOW YOU TO SHOOT OUT THE BLOCKS), A CATCHING DEVICE (SO AS TO BE ABLE TO FIRE THE BALL OFF AT A DIFFERENT ANGLE EVERY TIME YOU HIT IT) AND ONE THAT SLOWS THE BALL.... SORRY, BOLT.... DOWN. NEEDLESS TO SAY, THE GAME INSPIRED TONNES OF CLONES, FEW OF WHICH ADDED ANYTHING ELSE.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>64A5F62A</hash>
		<image>./images/Arkanoid (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Arkanoid (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Arkanoid (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Arkanoid (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1453" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Balloon Fight (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Balloon Fight</name>
		<desc>EM BALLOON FIGHT VOCÊ PRECISA VOAR COM O AUXÍLIO DE DOIS BALÕES E TENTAR ESTOURAR OS BALÕES DOS SEUS OPONENTES ANTES DELES ESTOURAREM OS SEUS. QUANDO TODOS OS BALÕES DE UM OPONENTE FOREM ESTOURADOS, UM PARA-QUEDAS SE ABRIRÁ PARA QUE ELE POUSE EM SEGURANÇA. NESSE MOMENTO VOCÊ PRECISA DERROTÁ-LO CAINDO DIRETAMENTE SOBRE ELE ANTES QUE ELE POSSA ENCHER UM NOVO BALÃO E VOLTAR À BATALHA. SE AMBOS OS SEUS BALÕES FOREM ESTOURADOS, VOCÊ CAIRÁ NA ÁGUA ABAIXO E PERDERÁ UMA VIDA. HÁ TAMBÉM UMA SEGUNDA VARIAÇÃO DE JOGO CHAMADA "BALLOON TRIP", ONDE VOCÊ PRECISA COLETAR TANTOS BALÕES QUANTO POSSÍVEL, EVITANDO CAIR NO OCEANO E DESVIANDO DE LABIRINTOS DE RAIOS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>6834967B</hash>
		<image>./images/Balloon Fight (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Balloon Fight (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Balloon Fight (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Balloon Fight (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1298" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Batman - Return of the Joker (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Batman : Return of the Joker</name>
		<desc>THE JOKER LIVES AGAIN IN SUNSOFT'S SEQUEL TO THEIR NES 
ORIGINAL. THE JOKER HAS SOMEHOW MANAGED TO ESCAPE FROM ARKHAM ASYLUM ONCE AGAIN, AND BATMAN MUST FIGHT HIM ACROSS SEVEN STAGES TO RESTORE PEACE TO GOTHAM CITY.

BATMAN CARRIES A GAUNTLET SHOOTING BASIC BULLETS BY DEFAULT. THIS CAN BE UPGRADED WITH WEAPON POWERUPS LOCATED IN BOXES THROUGHOUT THE LEVEL, GIVING ACCESS TO HOMING AND ENERGY WEAPONS. EVERY UPGRADE WEAPON CAN BE CHARGED UP FOR A SECONDARY ATTACK, DIFFERENT FOR EACH WEAPON. BATMAN ALSO HAS A SLIDE USEFUL AGAINST MOST ENEMIES AND SOME BOSSES. 

BOSS FIGHTS INTRODUCE A SYSTEM WHERE LIFE IS MEASURED BY POINTS INSTEAD OF TICK MARKS OR BARS. IN THESE SECTIONS, BATMAN HAS SIGNIFICANTLY MORE HEALTH, AND CAN TAKE MANY MORE HITS WHEN RUMBLING WITH THESE STRONGER FOES.

LEVELS INCLUDE A SNOWY LANDSCAPE, MOVING TRAIN, MILITARY BASE, AND SEWERS. TWO LEVELS REQUIRE YOU TO RUN AND DODGE EXPLOSIONS WHILE VEHICLES KEEP PACE IN THE BACKGROUND. SOME LEVELS ALSO HAVE BATMAN ACTIVATE A JETPACK AND PLAY THROUGH A SHORT SIDE-SCROLLING SHOOTER. 

THIS GAME IS ONE OF THE FEW BATMAN GAMES THAT WAS NOT BASED DIRECTLY ON A MOVIE OR TELEVISION SERIES.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19911202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A4E35810</hash>
		<image>./images/Batman - Return of the Joker (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Batman - Return of the Joker (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Batman - Return of the Joker (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Batman - Return of the Joker (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1287" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Batman - The Video Game (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Batman : The Video Game</name>
		<desc>THE NES VERSION OF BATMAN: THE VIDEO GAME IS LOOSELY BASED ON THE 1989 MOVIE. IT IS A SIDE-SCROLLING GAME, WITH A BLUE DRESSED BATMAN FIGHTING ENEMIES SUCH AS ROBOTS, JET-PACKED SOLDIERS, NINJAS AND MUTANTS.

THE GAME CONSISTS IN FIVE LEVELS SOMEWHAT RELATED TO THE MOVIE: GOTHAM CITY STREETS (WITH KILLER MOTH AS THE FINAL BOSS), AXIS CHEMICAL FACTORY (WITH MACHINE INTELLIGENCE SYSTEM AS BOSS), UNDERGROUND CONDUIT (WITH ELECTROCUTIONER AS BOSS), THE LABORATORY RUINS (THE DUAL-CONTAINER ALARM AS BOSS) AND GOTHAM'S CATHEDRAL (WITH FIREBUG AS BOSS) WHERE BATMAN FINALLY FACES THE JOKER. BEFORE EACH LEVEL, A CUTSCENE WITH SCENES FROM THE MOVIE IS DISPLAYED.

BESIDES HIS EVER TRUSTING PUNCHES, BATMAN HAS PLENTY OF WEAPONS IN HIS UTILITY BELT: THE BATARANG, THE SPEAR GUN AND THE DIRK (A THREE DIRECTION WEAPON). BATMAN HAS AN AMMUNITION COUNTER SHARED FOR THE THREE WEAPONS. THE BATARANG TAKES ONE PELLET PER SHOT, THE SPEAR GUN TWO PELLETS AND THE DIRK, THREE. BATMAN ALSO HAS AN EIGHT HIT LIFE BAR, WHICH CAN BE REPLENISHED BY COLLECTING HEARTS DROPPED BY KILLED ENEMIES. THE ENEMIES WILL ALSO DROP PELLET ITEMS (10 PELLETS PER ITEM) AND BONUS ITEMS (WHICH WILL ONLY SUM UP POINTS).

BATMAN CAN ALSO PERFORM A "WALL JUMP": HE'LL GRAB A WALL WHEN JUMPING TOWARD IT, ALLOWING HIM TO ESCALATE SOME NARROW PASSAGES. BATMAN HAS THREE LIVES AND UNLIMITED CONTINUES.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>61522744</hash>
		<image>./images/Batman - The Video Game (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Batman - The Video Game (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Batman - The Video Game (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Batman - The Video Game (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1660" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Battle City (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Battle City</name>
		<desc>BATTLE CITY IS A REFINED VERSION OF NAMCO'S OLD ARCADE GAME TANK BATTALION. DESTROY DIFFERENT ENEMY TANKS, WHILE TRYING TO KEEP THEM AWAY FROM YOUR BASE. WHEN YOU HAVE DESTROYED 20 ENEMY TANKS YOU ADVANCE TO THE NEXT LEVEL WITH DIFFERENT LAYOUT. IN EACH LEVEL THERE'S SOME OBSTACLES WHICH YOU CAN USE TO YOUR ADVANTAGE. OBSTACLES INCLUDE RED BRICKS WHICH YOU CAN SHOOT OUT OF YOUR WAY, SILVER BRICKS WHICH ARE HIGHLY ARMORED, WATER AND ICE. YOU START THE GAME WITH A BASIC TANK, WHICH YOU CAN POWER UP TO BETTER ONE LITTLE BY LITTLE. 

THE NES GAME INCLUDES A CONSTRUCTION MODE, SO YOU CAN MAKE YOUR OWN LEVELS WHEN YOU HAVE PLAYED THROUGH ALL THE 35 ORIGINAL LEVELS.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>881FADF3</hash>
		<image>./images/Battle City (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Battle City (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Battle City (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Battle City (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1247" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Battletoads (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads</name>
		<desc>BATTLETOADS É UM JOGO DO TIPO BEAT'EM UP. A RAINHA DAS TREVAS SEQUESTROU A PRINCESA ANGELICA E SUA MELHOR AMIGA, PIMPLE. O PROFESSOR BIRD ENVIARÁ VOCÊ PARA RAGNAROK, MAS, A PARTIR DESSE MOMENTO, TUDO DEPENDERÁ DE VOCÊ!
VOCÊ CONTROLARÁ UM GRUPO DE SAPOS LUTADORES (OS BATTLETOADS) ATRAVÉS DE VÁRIOS NÍVEIS. ALGUNS SÃO DESLOCAMENTOS LATERAIS, OUTROS SÃO VERTICAIS E OUTROS AINDA MUDAM DE EIXO DE ROTAÇÃO A MEDIDA QUE O NÍVEL É JOGADO.
VOCÊ PRECISARÁ LUTAR ENQUANTO AVANÇA, AS VEZES USANDO PRANCHAS E FOGUETES, DISPARANDO CONTRA OS INIMIGOS E EVITANDO-OS EM ALGUMAS SITUAÇÕES. AO FINAL DE CADA NÍVEL HAVERÁ UM CHEFE, ENQUANTO EM ALGUMAS ÁREAS HAVERÃO MINI-CHEFES NO MEIO DO CAMINHO.
AO FINAL VOCÊ ENCONTRARÁ A TORRE DA SOMBRAS, ONDE LHE ESPERA A RAINHA DE ESCURIDÃO. E AÍ? VAI ENCARAR SAPO? VAMOS VER SE VOCÊ SE ATREVE E TEM CORAGEM!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>0D70B152</hash>
		<image>./images/Battletoads (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Battletoads (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Battletoads (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Battletoads (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1324" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bionic Commando (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Bionic Commando: Elite Forces</name>
		<desc>YOU PLAY A SOLDIER WITH A BIONIC ARM THAT EXTENDS AND CONTRACTS.  YOUR ARM ALLOWS YOU TO GRAB ON TO FIXED OBJECTS TO SWING AROUND AND CLIMB UP LEVELS -- NO JUMPING ALLOWED! THE ARM ALSO GRABS OPPONENTS AND PULL THEM TOWARDS YOU.

YOUR MISSION IS TO INFILTRATE THE ENEMY FORTRESS, FIND YOUR MISSING COMRADE, "SUPER JOE", AND TAKE OUT THE EVIL LEADER, "GENERALISSIMO KILT", OF THE INVADING FORCE THAT HAS BEEN ATTACKING YOUR PEOPLE FOR THE LAST 2 YEARS.

AFTER MOST LEVELS THE BIONIC COMMANDO WILL RECIEVE ITEMS. OFTEN THESE ITEMS ARE REQUIRED TO SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETE OTHER LEVELS. ADDITIONALLY, EACH LEVEL WILL REQUIRE A DIFFERENT COLORED COMMUNICATOR IN ORDER TO MAKE SENSE OF MESSAGE TRAFFIC</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19881202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0D45D648</hash>
		<image>./images/Bionic Commando (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bionic Commando (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bionic Commando (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bionic Commando (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1404" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomber King (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Bomber King</name>
		<desc>IN A DESPERATE MEASURE TO COMBAT THE OVERPOPULATION OF EARTH, SCIENTISTS WORK TO CREATE AN ARTIFICIAL PLANET NAMED ALTILE, NAMED AFTER THE SCIENTIST WHO DESIGNED IT. DURING THE CONSTRUCTION OF ALTILE, HUMANITY HAS BECOME UNITED AND PEACEFUL. DURING THIS NEW ERA OF PROSPERITY, EARTH DECOMMISSIONS THE ROBOWARRIORS, A FORCE OF HEAVILY ARMED HALF-MAN HALF-ROBOT WAR VEHICLES. BUT FROM ANOTHER DIMENSION, ALIENS CALLING THEMSELVES THE XANTHO EMPIRE AND LEAD BY THE BEING XUR INVADE PLANET ALTILE AND TERRAFORM IT FOR THEIR OWN USES. THE SURVIVORS OF ALTILE SEND OUT A DISTRESS CALL TO EARTH. RECEIVING THIS MESSAGE, THE PEOPLE OF EARTH QUICKLY ACTIVATE THE LATEST AND MOST POWERFUL OF THE ROBOWARRIORS, A MODEL KNOWN AS ZED (Z-TYPE EARTH DEFENSE) AND SEND IT AT TOP SPEED TO ALTILE.

CONTROLLING ZED FROM AN OVERHEAD VIEW, THE PLAYER IS ABLE TO MOVE IN ANY OF 4 DIRECTIONS (UP,DOWN,LEFT,RIGHT), DROP BOMBS AND SHOOT A PROJECTILE WEAPON. THE TERRAIN OF ALTILE IS MADE UP OF MANY OBSTACLES AND THE BOMBS SERVE TO DESTROY THESE AND MAKE PASSAGE FOR ZED. DESTROYING ANY ENEMY OR OBSTACLE MAY YIELD DIFFERENT POWER-UPS WHICH CONTAIN ANY OF 10 DIFFERENT EFFECTS (INCLUDING AMMUNITION AND ENERGY REFILLS) WHICH MAY BE STOCKED AND USED AT ANY TIME FROM THE MENU. OR THE POWER-UPS MAY BE INSTANT-USE REFILLS FOR BOMBS AND ENERGY SUPPLIES.

ADDITIONALLY SOME LEVELS CONTAIN KEYS, WHICH UNLOCK DOORS AND CHALICES WHICH PREVENT THE LEVEL FROM RUNNING ON ENDLESSLY. SECRET AREAS SUCH AS A WELL OF HOPE AND A ROOM OF IDOLS MAY ALSO BE FOUND. ALTOGETHER, THERE ARE EIGHT DIFFERENT "WORLDS" FOR ZED TO CONQUER, CONTAINING NUMEROUS STAGES AND GUARDED BY A VICIOUS BOSS MONSTER.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19881202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>185D12F2</hash>
		<image>./images/Bomber King (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bomber King (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bomber King (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bomber King (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1482" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomberman II (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Bomberman II</name>
		<desc>BOMBERMAN ESTAVA ANDANDO NA RUA UM DIA QUANDO TESTEMUNHOU UM ASSALTO. ERA O BOMBERMAN NEGRO, QUE DERRUBA O NOSSO HERÓI E DEIXA O DINHEIRO PARA INCRIMINÁ-LO. AGORA BOMBERMAN FOI LEVADO PARA A CADEIA E DEVE LUTAR PARA SAIR DESTE LUGAR USANDO O ÚNICO MÉTODO QUE ELE CONHECE: BOMBAS!

BOMBERMAN É O SEGUNDO JOGO DA SÉRIE BOMBERMAN E A MECÂNICA É SEMELHANTE AO PRIMEIRO. SEU OBJETIVO PERMANECE O MESMO: VOCÊ DEVE DESTRUIR TODOS OS INIMIGOS EM UM NÍVEL E DEPOIS ENCONTRAR A SAÍDA PARA O PRÓXIMO. BOMBARDEAR A SAÍDA É SEMPRE UMA MÁ IDEIA. POWER-UPS ENCONTRADOS AUMENTARÃO O TAMANHO DA EXPLOSÃO, O NÚMERO DE BOMBAS NA TELA AO MESMO TEMPO, A VELOCIDADE DO JOGADOR OU LHE DARÁ A HABILIDADE DE ANDAR ATRAVÉS DAS PAREDES.

ALÉM DO JOGO SINGLE PLAYER, BOMBERMAN II INTRODUZ UM MODO VERSUS PARA 2 JOGADORES E UM BATTLE MODE PARA 3. SEU OBJETIVO É DESTRUIR OS OUTROS JOGADORES ENQUANTO VOCÊ ESTIVER VIVO.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<hash>60DBC62A</hash>
		<image>./images/Bomberman II (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bomberman II (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bomberman II (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bomberman II (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1337" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomberman (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Bomberman</name>
		<desc>BOMBERMAN ERA UM ROBÔ EM UMA FÁBRICA DE BOMBAS QUE ANSIAVA POR SUA LIBERDADE. CIRCULAVAM BOATOS DE QUE ESCAPAR PARA A SUPERFÍCIE PERMITIRIA QUE O ROBÔ SE TORNASSE HUMANO. SAIR SERIA O DESAFIO. CADA SALA É HABITADA POR MONSTROS QUE DEVEM SER NEUTRALIZADOS E A PRÓPRIA SAÍDA ESCONDIDA DEBAIXO DE TIJOLOS.

O PRIMEIRO DA SÉRIE BOMBERMAN, É UM JOGO PARA UM JOGADOR COM UMA VISÃO DE CIMA E CONTROLES SIMPLISTAS. DE FATO, ALÉM DO MOVIMENTO, VOCÊ SÓ TEM UMA HABILIDADE: COLOCAR BOMBAS. CADA BOMBA EXPLODE EM FORMA DE CRUZ (4 DIREÇÕES) QUE PODE DESTRUIR INIMIGOS OU BLOCOS. É POSSÍVEL ENCONTRAR POWER-UPS QUE AUMENTAM O TAMANHO DA EXPLOSÃO, COLOCAM BOMBAS ADICIONAIS, AUMENTAM A VELOCIDADE DO BOMBERMAN OU PERMITE ATRAVESSAR AS PAREDES. SEU OBJETIVO EM CADA NÍVEL É DESTRUIR TODOS OS INIMIGOS E ESCAPAR PELA SAÍDA ANTES QUE O TEMPO LIMITE SEJA ATINGIDO. CUIDADO: ATINGIR A SAÍDA COM UMA EXPLOSÃO LIBERA MAIS INIMIGOS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>EEA73023</hash>
		<image>./images/Bomberman (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bomberman (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bomberman (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bomberman (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1365" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bram Stoker's Dracula (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Bram Stoker's Dracula</name>
		<desc>BRAM STROKER'S DRACULA IS A SIDE-SCROLLER PLATFORM GAME LOOSELY BASED ON THE 1992 FILM OF THE SAME NAME. PLAYERS TAKE THE ROLE OF JONATHAN HARKER WHOSE MISSION TO TO DESTROY COUNT DRACULA BY FIRST HEADING TO TRANSYLVANIA AND THEN LONDON.

JONATHAN HARKER CAN MOVE LEFT AND RIGHT, JUMP AND ATTACK WITH A WEAPON, THE MOST BASIC OF WHICH IS A KNIFE. THE STATUS DISPLAY ON THE SCREEN SHOWS HARKER'S HEALTH BAR, COUNTDOWN TIMER TO COMPLETE THE LEVEL AND CURRENTLY HELD WEAPON.  THROUGHOUT THE LEVELS QUESTION MARK BOXES (SIMILAR TO THE MARIO GAMES) CAN BE FOUND, ATTACKING THESE WILL REVEAL POWER UPS WHICH INCLUDE HEALTH RESTORATION, TIMER INCREASE AND NEW WEAPONS. AMONG THESE NEW WEAPONS ARE AXES, DAGGERS AND A SHOTGUN. QUESTION MARK BOXES CAN ALSO BE USED AS PLATFORMS TO REACH OTHER AREAS AND ENEMIES. EACH STAGE IS DIVIDED INTO TWO SECTIONS: THE "DAYTIME" AND THE "NIGHTTIME". THESE ARE ENTIRELY DIFFERENT LEVELS COMPARABLE TO STAGE 1-A AND 1-B. HARKER MUST JUMP TO VARIOUS PLATFORMS AND OBSTACLES AND DEFEAT MINOR ENEMIES THROUGHOUT THE LEVELS. THE END OF A NIGHTTIME LEVEL IS USUALLY GUARDED BY A BOSS CREATURE WHO MUST BE DEFEATED TO PROGRESS.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3E1FC57B</hash>
		<image>./images/Bram Stoker's Dracula (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bram Stoker's Dracula (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bram Stoker's Dracula (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bram Stoker's Dracula (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1510" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bucky O'Hare (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Bucky O'Hare</name>
		<desc>CAPTAIN BUCKY O'HARE AND HIS LOYAL CREW; BLINKY, DEADEYE, JENNY AND WILLY, FIGHT TO SAVE THE ANIVERSE FROM THE SCOURGE OF THE TOAD ARMADA. THAT IS UNTIL BUCKY'S SHIP IS ATTACKED AND HIS CREW TAKEN PRISONER. NOW A LONE BUNNY ON A MISSION, BUCKY MUST FIGHT TO RESCUE HIS COMRADES FROM FOUR HOSTILE PLANETS AND THEN CONFRONT THE AIR MARSHALL ON HIS FLAGSHIP.

BUCK O'HARE IS A SIDE-SCROLLER GAME BASED OFF OF THE CARTOON OF THE SAME NAME. BUCKY'S MAIN ABILITIES ARE A JUMP AND A BLASTER WEAPON, WHICH HE CAN CHARGE UP TO MAKE AN EVEN MORE POWERFUL JUMP. LIFE AND WEAPON BARS ARE DISPLAYED AT THE BOTTOM OF THE SCREEN. BUCKY CAN OBTAIN NEW WEAPONS THROUGHOUT THE GAME FROM HIS CREW MEMBERS.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>692E26AC</hash>
		<image>./images/Bucky O'Hare (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bucky O'Hare (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bucky O'Hare (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bucky O'Hare (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1762" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Captain America and The Avengers (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Captain America and the Avengers</name>
		<desc>THE MANDARIN HAS KNOCKED OUT IRON MAN AND THE VISION. THIS TIME IT IS PERSONAL.

YOU PLAY AS CAPTAIN AMERICA OR HAWKEYE. IN THE ONE PLAYER MODE, YOU MUST FIGHT YOUR WAY THROUGH VARIOUS THUGS TO RESCUE IRON MAN AND THE VISION. THIS GAME IS A SIDE SCROLLER, SOMEWHAT REMINISCENT OF BIONIC COMMANDO IN WHICH YOU FIGHT THROUGH A LEVEL THEN MOVE TO AN OVERHEAD MAP TO DECIDE WHERE TO GO NEXT. IN BETWEEN LEVELS, WASP GIVES YOU HINTS.

CAPTAIN AMERICA'S ATTACKS ARE: WHEN HE IS STANDING, SHIELD THROW; WHEN HE IS CROUCHING, PUNCH AND WHEN HE IS JUMPING, KICK. ALSO, IF YOU PUSH TWICE IN A DIRECTION, CAP CAN DO A POWERFUL FORWARD CHARGE WITH HIS SHIELD FOR A SHORT DISTANCE.

HAWKEYE'S ATTACKS ARE ALL ARROW SHOTS. HE CAN SHOOT LEFT, RIGHT, UP, UPPER-LEFT OR UPPER-RIGHT.

IF YOU COMPLETE AN AREA WITH ONE CHARACTER THEN COMPLETE IT WITH THE OTHER CHARACTER RIGHT AWAY, YOU CAN PRESS START TO SWITCH BETWEEN CAP OR HAWKEYE. THIS HAS THE ADVANTAGE THAT CAP'S FORWARD CHARGE IS POWERFUL AND BY GRABBING POLES, HE CAN THEN JUMP TO AREAS HAWKEYE CANNOT.

HAWKEYE CAN SHOOT ENEMIES OR TARGETS TOO HIGH FOR CAP TO JUMP UP AND KICK.

IN THE BATTLE MODE, THIS IS A TWO PLAYER, ONE-ON-ONE BATTLE. PLAYER ONE CHOOSES FROM CAPTAIN AMERICA OR HAWKEYE (THE GOOD GUYS) AND PLAYER TWO CHOOSES FROM WIZARD, ULTRON OR CROSSBONES (THE BAD GUYS).

YOU FIGHT EACH OTHER UNTIL ONE PLAYER HAS WON THREE ROUNDS.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>2514CECA</hash>
		<image>./images/Captain America and The Avengers (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Captain America and The Avengers (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Captain America and The Avengers (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Captain America and The Avengers (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1421" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Captain Planet and the Planeteers (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Captain Planet and the Planeteers</name>
		<desc>BASED ON THE CARTOON SERIES OF THE SAME NAME, CAPTAIN PLANET AND THE PLANETEERS ARE ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTORS. EACH PLANETEER IS ENDOWED WITH A SPECIAL ELEMENTAL POWER WHICH IS USED TO COMBAT POLLUTION, PRESERVE THE ENVIROMENT AND KEEP EVERYTHING SHIP-SHAPE. WHEN THE PLANETEERS POWERS COMBINE THEY SUMMON CAPTAIN PLANET, A SUPERHERO CAPTAIN PLANET, GUARDIAN OF THE EARTH, IS SUMMONED. THE POWERS OF GAIA KEEP WATCH OVER THE WORLD, AND ASSIGN THE PLANETEERS TO WHERE THEY ARE NEEDED.

CAPTAIN PLANET AND THE PLANETEERS IS AN ACTION SIDESCROLLER GAME DIVIDED INTO TWO SECTIONS: INSIDE LEVELS AND OUTSIDE LEVELS. OUTSIDE LEVELS USUALLY PUT THE PLANETEERS IN SOME KIND OF VEHICLE WHICH CAN MOVE IN ANY OF EIGHT DIRECTIONS ON THE SCREEN. THE PLANETEERS CAN USE ANY OF THEIR ELEMENTAL POWERS, DRAINED FROM AN ENERGY BAR: FIRE SHOOTS A FIREBALL DIRECTLY AHEAD, WATER SHOOTS OUT A WATER WAVE, WIND LETS LOOSE A DEFENSIVE AIR CURRENTS, EARTH TOSSES STONES OUT TO THE EARTH AND HEART CALMS ANIMAL CREATURES. TOUCHING AN ENEMY OR PROJECTILE RESULTS IN INSTANT DEATH. 

INSIDE LEVELS SUMMON CAPTAIN PLANET HIMSELF, WHO CAN PUNCH OR TURN HIMSELF INTO A SWIRLING VERSION OF ANY OF THE FIVE ELEMENTS. CAPTAIN PLANET CAN ALSO MOVE/FLY IN ANY OF EIGHT DIRECTIONS AND ALSO CAN ONLY TAKE ONE HIT BEFORE DYING. POWER-UPS CAN ALSO BE FOUND ON THESE LEVELS.</desc>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>19920902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chris Gray Enterprises</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1F403CC1</hash>
		<image>./images/Captain Planet and the Planeteers (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Captain Planet and the Planeteers (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Captain Planet and the Planeteers (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Captain Planet and the Planeteers (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania II - Simon's Quest </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1268" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania</name>
		<desc>A CADA CEM ANOS, O VAMPIRO SOMBRIO CONHECIDO COMO DRÁCULA RESSUSCITA E ATERRORIZA A TERRA. UM CAÇADOR DE VAMPIROS CHAMADO SIMON BELMONT BRAVAMENTE SE AVENTURA NA MANSÃO DO CONDE PARA DERROTÁ-LO. AO LONGO DO CAMINHO ELE TERÁ QUE DERROTAR ESQUELETOS, MORCEGOS, HOMENS-PEIXE, CABEÇAS DE MEDUSA E OUTRAS CRIATURAS DO MAL.

CASTLEVANIA É UM JOGO DE AÇÃO DE PLATAFORMA DE ROLAGEM LATERAL. O JOGADOR QUE ASSUME O PAPEL DE SIMON BELMONT É CAPAZ DE PULAR E CHICOTEAR. PODERES PODEM SER OBTIDOS DERROTANDO INIMIGOS OU DESTRUINDO VELAS QUE APARECEM NO CASTELO. UM DESSES POWER-UPS AUMENTA O PODER E O COMPRIMENTO DO CHICOTE DE SIMON. DIFERENTES ARMAS PODEM SER COLETADAS, QUE CONSOMEM CORAÇÕES QUANDO USADAS, ESSES CORAÇÕES TAMBÉM PODEM SER COLETADOS DE MONSTROS E VELAS. ALÉM DISSO, ALGUMAS PAREDES ESCONDERÃO SEGREDOS COMO O PERU RESTAURADOR DE SAÚDE OU AS HABILIDADES DE TIRO DUPLO E TRIPLO PARA AS ARMAS QUE SIMON COLETOU. NO FINAL DE CADA SEÇÃO DO CASTELO EXISTE UM CHEFE, QUE DEVE SER DERROTADO. A PROGRESSÃO ATRAVÉS DO CASTELO EVENTUALMENTE LEVA A UM CONFRONTO COM O PRÓPRIO CONDE DRÁCULA.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9FA16E6C</hash>
		<image>./images/Castlevania (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Castlevania (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Castlevania (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Castlevania (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="18615" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Challenger (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Challenger</name>
		<desc>ONE OF HUDSON SOFT'S EARLIEST NES TITLES, CHALLENGER IS AN ARCADE-STYLE GAME THAT COMBINES SIDE SCROLLING, RUN 'N JUMP ACTION WITH OVERHEAD, EXPLORATORY GAMEPLAY. THE GAME CONSISTS OF TWO PARTS.

THE FIRST LEVEL (OR "SCENE") HAS YOU RACING THE CLOCK TO GET TO THE FRONT OF A TRAIN, WHERE A PURPLE-FACED VILLAIN IS HOLDING YOUR SIGNIFICANT OTHER (OR, PERHAPS JUST SOME ANONYMOUS PRINCESS). YOU HAVE AT YOUR DISPOSAL A TRUSTY THROWING KNIFE TO TAKE CARE OF ENEMIES. YOU WILL ALSO HAVE TO DODGE OBSTACLES AND JUMP GAPS IN THE TRAIN. THIS SECTION IS TAKEN FROM THE EARLIER HUDSON GAME, STOP THE EXPRESS.

SCENE 2 PLACES YOU IN AN OVERHEAD, MAZE-LIKE ENVIRONMENT, WHERE YOU ONCE AGAIN HAVE TO FIGHT THE CLOCK. THIS TIME THOUGH, YOU HAVE TO NAVIGATE YOUR WAY THROUGH THE AREA, IN SEARCH OF ALL THE DIFFERENT "KEYWORDS", WHICH ARE PLACED IN DIFFERENT CAVES. ONCE YOU HAVE CLEARED ALL THE CAVES, THE PATH WILL BE OPEN TO THE BOSS' FINAL LAIR.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19851015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1CE158B8</hash>
		<image>./images/Challenger (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Challenger (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Challenger (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Challenger (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1965" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Championship Lode Runner (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Championship Lode Runner</name>
		<desc>A FOLLOW-UP TO THE ORIGINAL LODE RUNNER, WITH IDENTICAL GAMEPLAY.  THIS PACKAGE CONTAINED 50 OF THE MOST CHALLENGING LEVELS EVER DESIGNED, AND WAS INTENDED FOR EXPERT PLAYERS ONLY.  IT DID NOT INCLUDE THE LEVEL EDITOR, YOU HAD TO PLAY THROUGH THE LEVELS IN ORDER, BUT A SAVE-GAME OPTION WAS PROVIDED (ALTHOUGH YOU LOST ONE LIFE EVERY TIME YOU RESTORED).</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>36B47D6E</hash>
		<image>./images/Championship Lode Runner (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Championship Lode Runner (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Championship Lode Runner (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Championship Lode Runner (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1965" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Championship Lode Runner Kai (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Championship Lode Runner</name>
		<desc>A FOLLOW-UP TO THE ORIGINAL LODE RUNNER, WITH IDENTICAL GAMEPLAY.  THIS PACKAGE CONTAINED 50 OF THE MOST CHALLENGING LEVELS EVER DESIGNED, AND WAS INTENDED FOR EXPERT PLAYERS ONLY.  IT DID NOT INCLUDE THE LEVEL EDITOR, YOU HAD TO PLAY THROUGH THE LEVELS IN ORDER, BUT A SAVE-GAME OPTION WAS PROVIDED (ALTHOUGH YOU LOST ONE LIFE EVERY TIME YOU RESTORED).</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B38152D1</hash>
		<image>./images/Championship Lode Runner Kai (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Championship Lode Runner Kai (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Championship Lode Runner Kai (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Championship Lode Runner Kai (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1314" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Chip 'N Dale : Rescue Rangers</name>
		<desc>A CONEXÃO SALVA-AÇÃO (RESCUE RANGERS) É UM GRUPO DE PEQUENOS HERÓIS. COMPOSTO POR DOIS ESQUILOS, DOIS RATOS E UMA MOSCA... ESSES HERÓIS PODEM SER PEQUENOS, MAS NÃO HÁ CASO MUITO GRANDE PARA ELES ASSUMIREM. ESTE JOGO COMEÇA DE FORMA SIMPLES, COM A MISSÃO DE RESGATAR UM GATINHO PEQUENO, MAS LOGO SE TRANSFORMA EM UM ENREDO MAIS AMPLO QUE COLOCA O GRUPO CONTRA O SEU ARQUI-INIMIGO, O REI DO CRIME FELINO, GATÃO (FAT CAT).</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>DABA75E3</hash>
		<image>./images/Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1474" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Blaster Master (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Chou-Wakusei Senki : MetaFight</name>
		<desc>EM BUSCA DE SEU SAPO FRED QUE FUGIU, CAIU EM UM BURACO NO QUINTAL E SE TORNOU RADIOATIVO, JASON ENCONTRA-SE NO CENTRO DO PLANETA. LÁ ELE ENCONTRA UM TANQUE DE BATALHA TOTALMENTE FUNCIONAL CHAMADO SOPHIA THE 3RD, E VAI SE AVENTURAR PELO SUBSOLO. AGORA SUA MISSÃO É ENCONTRAR NOVAS ARMAS E PARTES ADICIONAIS PARA MELHORAR SOPHIA QUE, POR SUA VEZ, PERMITIRÃO QUE ELE EXPLORE MAIS ÁREAS, DERROTANDO OS MAIS VARIADOS MUTANTES E SEU LÍDER, PLUTONIUM BOSS, ATÉ QUE FINALMENTE ENCONTRE SEU SAPO MUTANTE.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19881101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>37FEFB6C</hash>
		<image>./images/Blaster Master (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Blaster Master (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Blaster Master (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Blaster Master (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1528" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Clu Clu Land (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Clu Clu Land</name>
		<desc>A UNIQUE PUZZLE GAME IN WHICH YOU PLAY A FISH LIKE CREATURE WHO MUST EXPLORE THE MANY PLAY FIELDS COLLECTING GOLD BARS THAT FORM A PICTURE. ENEMIES LITTER THE FIELD, WHICH YOU CAN BLAST AWAY WITH A WAVE OF ENERGY, REMOVING THEM FOR A SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME FROM THE GAME. YOU ALSO NEED TO GRAB ONTO THE POSTS AND WALLS TO TURN INTO THE GAPS ON THE FIELD, ADDING AN ELEMENT OF TIMING TO THE GAME.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19841122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>B0E57A95</hash>
		<image>./images/Clu Clu Land (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Clu Clu Land (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Clu Clu Land (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Clu Clu Land (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1797" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Code Name - Viper (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Code Name : Viper</name>
		<desc>SET AGAINST THE BACKDROP OF THE WAR ON DRUGS FROM THE LATE 1980S/EARLY 1990S, CODE NAME: VIPER DIRECTLY CONFRONTS THE DRUG CARTEL AT THEIR BASES IN SOUTH AMERICA. YOU PLAY AN AMERICAN SECRET AGENT WHO MUST INFILTRATE THE CARTEL DRUG BASES AND MANSIONS, FREE HOSTAGES AND INFORMANTS, AND PIECE TOGETHER CLUES ABOUT WHO THE KINGPIN IS-- AND INEVITABLY BRING HIM DOWN. EQUIP YOURSELF WITH A PROGRESSIVELY MORE POWERFUL ARSENAL AS THE GAME PROGRESSES IN STANDARD NES SIDE-SCROLLER FASHION.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>81B717D6</hash>
		<image>./images/Code Name - Viper (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Code Name - Viper (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Code Name - Viper (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Code Name - Viper (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1493" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Commando (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Commando</name>
		<desc>SEVERAL LEVELS AWAIT YOUR SUPER-TOUGH COMMANDO IN THIS ARCADE CONVERSION. ARMED WITH ONLY A STANDARD RIFLE AND A FEW GRENADES YOU MUST TAKE ON HORDES OF NAZIS. SOME ARE WANDERING AROUND IN THE OPEN, WHILE OTHERS HAVE PICKED OUT HIDING PLACES, WHICH YOU MUST APPROACH FROM CERTAIN ANGLES. TREES, RIVERS AND BRIDGES CREATE A VARIED COMBAT-LIKE TERRAIN AND MUST BE INCORPORATED INTO YOUR THINKING. EXTRA GRENADES CAN BE COLLECTED, AND WILL DEFINITELY BE REQUIRED, AS THEY ALLOW YOU TO KILL FORM DISTANCE AND THUS AVOID SOME ENEMY SHOTS.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19861102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F21DA94E</hash>
		<image>./images/Commando (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Commando (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Commando (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Commando (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1622" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Conquest of the Crystal Palace (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Conquest of the Crystal Palace</name>
		<desc>LONG AGO THE CRYSTAL PALACE WAS A THRIVING KINGDOM, HOWEVER THE EVIL WAR SPIRIT ZARAS APPEARED ONE DAY AND BROUGHT DESTRUCTION TO THE LANDS! THE PEOPLE OF THE CRYSTAL PALACE LEFT AS ZARAS AND HIS HENCHMAN TOOK OVER, CHANGING THE KINGDOM INTO A MAZE OF MANY DANGERS. YOU CONTROL FARRON, THE HERO OF THE STORY WHO NEEDS TO ENTER THE CRYSTAL PALACE AND DESTROY THE BAD GUYS IN ORDER TO RESTORE PEACE. THE GAME IS AN ACTION PLATFORM GAME THAT SCROLLS BOTH HORIZONTALLY AND VERTICALLY. ON EACH OF FIVE STAGES YOU'LL NEED TO FIGHT VARIOUS ENEMIES THROUGHOUT THE VARIED TERRAIN, AND FINALLY DEFEAT THE BOSS AT THE END. YOU'LL START WITH JUST A SIMPLE SWORD, BUT ADDITIONAL WEAPONS CAN BE FOUND OR BOUGHT IN ORDER TO HELP YOU OUT. IF YOU GET INTO TROUBLE, YOU CAN ALSO CALL YOUR DOG ZAP ONTO THE SCREEN; HE'LL JUMP AROUND CAUSING DAMAGE TO THE ENEMIES GIVING YOU A CHANCE TO ESCAPE. YOU MAY ALSO COME ACROSS KIM'S SHOPS ALONG YOUR JOURNEY. HERE YOU CAN BUY VARIOUS ITEMS, INCLUDING ADDITIONAL  LIVES, REPLENISH YOUR HEALTH, MORE POWERFUL WEAPONS, AND OTHER USEFUL ITEMS. TO PURCHASE ITEMS, YOU'LL NEED MONEY WHICH CAN BE COLLECTED AFTER DEFEATING ENEMIES IN BATTLE.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Asmik Ace Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Quest</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E1B207AA</hash>
		<image>./images/Conquest of the Crystal Palace (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Conquest of the Crystal Palace (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Conquest of the Crystal Palace (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Conquest of the Crystal Palace (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1393" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Contra Force (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Contra Force</name>
		<desc>CONTRA FORCE, A SPECIAL FORCES TEAM INCLUDING COMMANDO BURN, SMITH, BEANS, AND IRON, PROTECTS NEO CITY FROM THE TERRORIST GROUP, D.N.M.E.

THIS IS THE THIRD CONTRA GAME FOR THE NES (AND WAS RELEASED JUST AFTER CONTRA III: THE ALIEN WARS FOR SNES). THERE ARE FIVE MISSIONS, INVOLVING BOTH SIDE-SCROLLING AND OVERHEAD SHOOTING LEVELS. SWITCH BETWEEN THE FOUR COMMANDOS AND FIND SECRET PASSAGES, NOT TO MENTION A LARGE ARSENAL OF WEAPONS: ROCKET LAUNCHERS, FLAME THROWERS, BAZOOKAS, LAND MINES, RIFLES, TIME BOMBS.  FOR ONE OR TWO PLAYERS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D319A50B</hash>
		<image>./images/Contra Force (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Contra Force (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Contra Force (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Contra Force (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18624" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Contra (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Contra</name>
		<desc>NO ANO DE 2631, UM PEQUENO METEORITO CAIU NO ARQUIPÉLAGO DE GALUGA, LOCALIZADO A 20 QUILÔMETROS A NORDESTE DA COSTA DA NOVA ZELÂNDIA. DOIS ANOS DEPOIS, O GRUPO TERRORISTA CONHECIDO COMO RED FALCON CAPTUROU A ILHA QUE ESTAVA EM PREPARAÇÃO PARA UMA INVASÃO ALIENÍGENA. OS MARINES TERRESTRES ENVIARAM DOIS MEMBROS DA UNIDADE ELITE CONTRA, BILL RIZER E LANCE BEAN, PARA NEUTRALIZAR OS TERRORISTAS. 

CONTROLANDO BILL(JOGADOR 1) OU LANCE(JOGADOR 2), O JOGADOR DEVERÁ CHEGAR AO FINAL DE CADA FASE, ATIRANDO EM TUDO QUE ESTIVER AO ALCANCE, EVITANDO O FOGO DOS INIMIGOS. O JOGADOR PODE MELHORAR SEU RIFLE PADRÃO COM UMA DAS QUATRO DIFERENTES ARMAS, INCLUINDO O PODEROSO S(SPREAD SHOT).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>58B83530</hash>
		<image>./images/Contra (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Contra (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Contra (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Contra (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1834" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crisis Force (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Crisis Force</name>
		<desc>THE YEAR IS 199X AND A ROBOT ARMY HAS INVADED TOKYO CITY. A BOY AND A GIRL (WHO REMAIN UNNAMED) BOARD THEIR SHIPS TO FIGHT OFF THE THREAT.

THIS IS A VERTICAL SCROLLING SHOOT-EM-UP GAME VIEWED FROM OVERHEAD, WHERE THE PLAYER PILOTS A FIGHTER SHIP THROUGH SEVEN LEVELS OF INTENSE SHOOTING ACTION. EACH LEVEL HURLS ENEMIES AND BULLETS AT THE PLAYER'S SHIP, ENDING WITH A BOSS FIGHT, EXCEPT FOR ONE WHICH INSTEAD IS A BOSS RUSH LEVEL. THE GAME ALLOWS FOR TWO PLAYERS TO PLAY AT THE SAME TIME.

THE PLAYER HAS A CHOICE OF TWO WEAPONS; BULLETS OR LASERS. WEAPONS CAN BE CHANGED BY PICKING UP GEMS OF DIFFERENT COLORS. PICKING UP THE SAME COLOR AS YOU ALREADY HAVE ALLOWS YOU TO UPGRADE YOUR CURRENT WEAPON A FEW TIMES. THE PLAYER'S SHIP CAN CHANGE FORM AND WITH IT THE WAY THAT THE WEAPONS WORK. THIS ALLOWS THE PLAYER TO PICK THE BEST WEAPON STRATEGY FOR EACH SITUATION. THE PLAYER ALSO HAS A LIMITED AMOUNT OF BOMBS THAT ARE USEFUL TO GET OUT OF TRICKY SITUATIONS.

WHEN A WEAPON IS UPGRADED IT ALSO ACTS AS A SHIELD SO THE SHIP CAN TAKE AN ENEMY BULLET WITHOUT DYING. THIS WILL HOWEVER DEGRADE THE WEAPON DOWN TO THE FIRST LEVEL AGAIN. THERE ARE ALSO PICKUPS THAT ALTER THE SHIP'S SPEED AND A SPECIAL GEM THAT, IF FIVE OF THEM ARE COLLECTED, TEMPORARILY TRANSFORMS THE SHIP INTO AN INVINCIBLE SUPER SHIP.

CRISIS FORCE WAS ONLY RELEASED IN JAPAN.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>916D16F3</hash>
		<image>./images/Crisis Force (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Crisis Force (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Crisis Force (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Crisis Force (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="65464" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cross Fire (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Cross Fire</name>
		<desc>THE NARCOTICS TRIANGLE IS A ZONE DOMINATED BY EVIL WHERE POWERFUL DRUG CARTELS PREVAIL. COLOMBIA IN SOUTH AMERICA, MONGOLIA IN ASIA, AND IRAN IN THE MIDDLE EAST - THESE ARE THE COUNTRIES IN WHICH THE WORLD'S THREE LARGEST DRUG PRODUCERS ARE BASED. BECAUSE OF THESE CRIME-RIDDEN GROUPS, THE WORLD IS EXPERIENCING UNPRECEDENTED CORRUPTION AND DANGER TOWARD THE END OF THE 20TH CENTURY, PEOPLE ARE THE WORLD ARE ADDICTED TO DRUGS, AND ARE LOSING ALL MOTIVATION TO CONTINUE THEIR JOBS. AS A UNITED GROUP, THE THREE MAJOR DRUG ORGANIZATIONS ARE SECRETLY SCHEMING TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE CHAOS AND INVADE AND CONQUER THE WORLD. SHARING THIS COMMON GOAL, THE THREE GROUPS COMBINE THEIR EVIL IDEAS AND BEGIN TO CARRY OUT THEIR PLANS. HEADS OF STATE ARE KIDNAPPED AND HELD HOSTAGE AT THE ORGANIZATION HEADQUARTERS. SEEING THE SERIOUSNESS OF THE SITUATION, BILLY FINALLY DECIDES TO TAKE ACTION AND SETS OUT TO DESTROY THE EVIL DRUG EMPIRE.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kyugo Boueki</developer>
		<publisher>Kyugo Boueki</publisher>
		<hash>5972797A</hash>
		<image>./images/Cross Fire (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Cross Fire (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Cross Fire (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cross Fire (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1538" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crystalis (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Crystalis</name>
		<desc>OCTOBER 1ST, 1997 IS KNOWN AS END DAY. A GREAT WAR ENCIRCLES THE GLOBE AND BRINGS ABOUT AN END TO CIVILIZATION. THE SURVIVING HUMANS CONCLUDED THAT THEY COULD NEVER REPEAT THEIR MISTAKES AND BUILD A GREAT TOWER IN THE SKY TO WATCH OVER THE WORLD AND ACT ACCORDINGLY TO COMBAT "EVIL". ONE HUNDRED YEARS HAVE PASSED SINCE THEN AND A HIDDEN CRYOGENIC CHAMBER IN THE MOUNTAINS SPRINGS TO LIFE...

CRYSTALIS IS A TOP-DOWN ACTION RPG. STARTING FROM THE CRYOGENIC CHAMBER, THE PLAYER TAKES THE ROLE OF A MYSTERIOUS HERO WHO MUST UNCOVER THE MYSTERY OF THE TOWER. THE CHARACTER MAY EQUIP WEAPONS, ARMOR, SHIELDS AND GLOBE/BRACELETS ON HIS BODY AND A SINGLE ITEM FROM HIS INVENTORY FOR USE IN THE FIELD. TO AID IN THE HERO'S GOAL. HE WILL MEET UP WITH THE FOUR WISE PEOPLE AND LEARN THEIR MAGIC, WHILE ALSO OBTAINING THE FOUR ELEMENTAL SWORDS WHICH WILL HELP HIM PROGRESS. PLAYERS GAIN EXPERIENCE AND GOLD FROM DEFEATING MONSTERS. THE EXPERIENCE IS USED TO GAIN LEVELS AND IMPROVE STATISTICS, HOWEVER A MINIMUM LEVEL IS REQUIRED BEFORE ONE CAN DO DAMAGE TO SPECIFIC BOSSES. GOLD IS USED TO PURCHASE ITEMS IN SHOPS.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>37CACBDA</hash>
		<image>./images/Crystalis (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Crystalis (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Crystalis (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Crystalis (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="71344" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Darkwing Duck (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Darkwing Duck</name>
		<desc>THE KINGPINS OF CRIME ARE AT IT AGAIN! THE MYSTERIOUS CRIMINAL ORGANIZATION F.O.W.L. HAS HATCHED A PLAN TO TAKE CONTROL OF THE PEACEFUL CITY OF ST. CANARD. SIX OF THEIR MOST HEINOUS HENCHMEN ARE RUNNING RAMPANT THROUGH THE CITY AND ONLY THE DARING DARKWING DUCK CAN BRING THEM TO JUSTICE! JOIN DARKWING AS HE EXPLORES THE WOODS TO WEED OUT BUSHROOT'S EVIL PLAN. SEARCH THE WAREHOUSES ALONG THE WHARF FOR MEGA VOLT AND PULL THE PLUG ON AN ELECTRIFYING SCHEME. TRACK DOWN ALL SIX OF FOWL'S CRAFTY CRIMINALS AND THEN PREPARE YOURSELF AS DARKWING SQUARES OFF AGAINST THE SINISTER STEELBEAK IN HIS FIENDISH FLOATING FORTRESS!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2ECDF63D</hash>
		<image>./images/Darkwing Duck (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Darkwing Duck (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Darkwing Duck (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Darkwing Duck (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1796" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Clash at Demonhead (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Dengeki : Big Bang!</name>
		<desc>PROFESSOR PLUM AND HIS DESIGNS FOR THE "DOOMSDAY DEVICE", DEAD END HAVE BEEN TAKEN BY THE DIABOLICAL LAWBREAKERS - A SINISTER GROUP DEDICATED TO THE DESTRUCTION OF MANKIND. IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE THE DEVICE IS ASSEMBLED AND THE FINAL COUNTDOWN BEGINS. 
AS SERGEANT BILLY "BIG BANG" BLITZ OF THE SPECIAL ASSAULT BRIGADE FOR REAL EMERGENCIES(S.A.B.R.E) YOUR MISSION IS TO FOIL THE LAWBREAKERS PLAN. TO DO THIS, YOU MUST FIND THE SHORTEST ROUTE TO THE SUMMIT OF DEMONHEAD MOUNTAIN, WHERE THE PROFESSOR IS BEING HELD. RESCUE THE PROFESSOR AND SAVE THE WORLD FROM TOTAL DESTRUCTION. 
THIS IS A "TYPICAL" SIDESCROLLER WITH ROLE PLAYING ELEMENTS. THE VARIOUS ENEMIES YOU MEET WITH LEAVE BEHIND CASH WHICH CAN THEN BE USED TO BUY EQUIPMENT. YOU'LL NEED A DIVING SUIT TO SWIM UNDERWATER, A JETPACK TO GET TO THOSE HARD TO REACH AREAS AND DON'T FORGET THE SHOP CARD THAT CAN BE USED TO CALL THE SHOP NO MATTER WHERE YOU ARE.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vic Tokai</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>311EA019</hash>
		<image>./images/Clash at Demonhead (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Clash at Demonhead (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Clash at Demonhead (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Clash at Demonhead (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="71346" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Duck Tales 2 (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's DuckTales 2</name>
		<desc>TIO PATINHAS ESTÁ NO CAMINHO DA AVENTURA MAIS RICA DE TODAS: PEÇAS DO MAPA DO TESOURO PERDIDO DE MCDUCK FORAM ESPALHADAS PELO MUNDO, E ELE DEVE ENCONTRÁ-LAS ANTES QUE O GANANCIOSO PÃO-DURO MAC MÔNEI AS PEGUE. VAI SER UMA CORRIDA ATÉ O FINAL, POIS AMBOS TENTAM ENCONTRAR O TESOURO E SE TORNAR O PATO MAIS RICO DO MUNDO! JUNTE-SE AOS SEUS SOBRINHOS ENQUANTO EXPLORAM AS ANTIGAS PIRÂMIDES DO EGIPTO E LUTAM CONTRA PIRATAS QUE FAZEM CAMBALHOTAS NO TRIÂNGULO DAS BERMUDAS. AJUDE-OS A PROCURAR OS SALÕES ASSOMBRADOS DE UM ANTIGO CASTELO ESCOCÊS E A ESCALAR AS ALTURAS AQUOSAS DAS CATARATAS DO NIÁGARA. AJUDE PATINHAS EM SUA BUSCA PELO SEGREDO DA ILHA DE MU E VOCÊ OBTERÁ A PISTA FINAL PARA DESVENDAR A LOCALIZAÇÃO OCULTA DO TESOURO PERDIDO DE MCDUCK!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>56FAB695</hash>
		<image>./images/Duck Tales 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Duck Tales 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Duck Tales 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Duck Tales 2 (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1263" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Duck Tales (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's DuckTales</name>
		<desc>DUCK TALES É UM JOGO DE PLATAFORMA TRADICIONAL EM QUE O JOGADOR ASSUME O PAPEL DE GANANCIOSO TIO PATINHAS EM BUSCA DE TESOUROS EM TODO O MUNDO. ELE CONTA COM SEUS TRÊS SOBRINHOS E OUTROS PERSONAGENS DE DUCK TALES PARA AJUDÁ-LO EM SUA BUSCA POR LUGARES INÓSPITOS COMO A FLORESTA AMAZÔNICA, AS MINAS AFRICANAS, O HIMALAIA, A TRANSILVÂNIA (ONDE ELE CONHECE O PATO DRÁCULA) E ATÉ A LUA.

CADA UM DELES RESERVA O VELHO PATO MUITAS AVENTURAS, DIFERENTES INIMIGOS E QUARTOS ESCONDIDOS.

O JOGO APRESENTA UMA JOGABILIDADE DE PLATAFORMA DE ROLAGEM LATERAL 2D MUITO SEMELHANTE AO MEGA MAN. OS GRÁFICOS SÃO COLORIDOS E CARICATURAIS, A MÚSICA LEMBRA OS JOGADORES DA SÉRIE DE TV E OS CONTROLES SÃO MUITO SIMPLES.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19890914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C4BB18CA</hash>
		<image>./images/Duck Tales (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Duck Tales (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Duck Tales (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Duck Tales (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1487" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Little Mermaid, The (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's The Little Mermaid</name>
		<desc>IN THIS VERSION OF DISNEY'S THE LITTLE MERMAID YOU PLAY AS ARIEL THE MERMAID.

ARIEL HAS ALREADY MET ERIC, AND THEY PLAN TO WED, BUT THE SEA-WITCH URSALA HAS TAKEN CONTROL OF THE OCEAN!  SO ARIEL (AFTER EXPLAINING WHAT'S GOING ON TO ERIC) BECOMES A MERMAID ONCE MORE AND SETS OFF TO RESCUE THE SEA.

THE GAME TAKES PLACE FROM A SIDE VIEW AND ARIEL (SWIMMING MOST OF THE TIME, BUT HOPPING AROUND ON THE LAND OCCASIONALLY) CAN SHOOT BUBBLES TO TRAP HER FOES AND CAN THEN THROW THEM AT EACH OTHER.  SHE CAN ALSO DIG THROUGH SAND TO FIND TREASURE AND PICK UP SEA SHELLS TO HELP HER BREAK CHESTS OPEN.

THE TREASURE SHE FINDS IN THE SAND IS USUALLY JUST BONUS POINTS, BUT THE TREASURE YOU FIND IN CHESTS WILL INCREASE YOUR BUBBLE'S POWER AND RANGE.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Little Mermaid, The (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Little Mermaid, The (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Little Mermaid, The (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Little Mermaid, The (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1351" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donkey Kong Jr. (JU) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Jr.</name>
		<desc>NESTE JOGO, QUE É UMA CONTINUAÇÃO DIRETA DE DONKEY KONG, MARIO INTERPRETA O VILÃO, TENDO CAPTURADO DONKEY KONG E O COLOCADO EM UMA JAULA. COMO DONKEY KONG JR., OS JOGADORES TERÃO QUE PERCORRER QUATRO DIFERENTES NÍVEIS (VINES, SPRINGBOARD, CHAINS E MARIO'S HIDEOUT) NA TENTATIVA DE ENCONTRAR CHAVES PARA LIBERTAR O PAI DO PEQUENO MACACO.

AO LONGO DO CAMINHO, MARIO ENVIARÁ SNAPJAWS, PÁSSAROS ROXOS E FAÍSCAS ELÉTRICAS EM UMA TENTATIVA DE PARAR O RESGATE. JUNIOR PODE SE DEFENDER JOGANDO FRUTAS ENCONTRADAS PELO CAMINHO NAS CABEÇAS DE SEUS INIMIGOS. QUANTO MAIS INIMIGOS UM PEDAÇO DE FRUTA ACERTAR EM UMA SEQÜÊNCIA DE QUEDA, MAIS PONTOS SERÃO GANHOS.

JÚNIOR TAMBÉM PODE EVITAR INIMIGOS COM MAIS FACILIDADE, AGARRANDO DUAS CORRENTES OU CORDAS DE CADA VEZ PARA ESCAPAR MAIS RAPIDAMENTE, OU SALTANDO SOBRE SEUS INIMIGOS. NO ENTANTO, QUALQUER QUEDA ALTA OU NA ÁGUA EM CERTOS NÍVEIS SIGNIFICARÁ A PERDER UMA VIDA.

QUANDO TODOS OS QUATRO NÍVEIS FOREM SUPERADOS, OS NÍVEIS RECOMEÇARÃO EM UMA DIFICULDADE MAIOR.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4E27F43B</hash>
		<image>./images/Donkey Kong Jr. (JU) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Donkey Kong Jr. (JU) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Donkey Kong Jr. (JU) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Donkey Kong Jr. (JU) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1306" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donkey Kong (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>DONKEY KONG NÃO FOI APENAS O PRIMEIRO GRANDE SUCESSO DA NINTENDO, MAS MARCOU A INTRODUÇÃO DE DOIS DE SEUS MASCOTES MAIS POPULARES: MARIO (ORIGINALMENTE "JUMPMAN") E DONKEY KONG.

DONKEY KONG É UM JOGO DE AÇÃO DE PLATAFORMA ONDE MARIO ESCALA QUATRO DIFERENTES NÍVEIS INDUSTRIAIS EM UMA TENTATIVA DE SALVAR A DONZELA EM PERIGO, PAULINE, DO GRANDE MACACO ANTES QUE O TEMPO SE ESGOTE.

AO LONGO DO CAMINHO, MARIO DEVE SE ESQUIVAR DE UM FLUXO CONSTANTE DE BARRIS, BOLAS DE FOGO "VIVAS" E MOLAS. EMBORA NÃO SEJA TÃO PODEROSO COMO EM OUTROS JOGOS FUTUROS, MARIO PODE ENCONTRAR UM MARTELO QUE LHE PERMITE, POR UM PERÍODO LIMITADO DE TEMPO, DESTRUIR OS BARRIS E BOLAS DE FOGO. ALÉM DISSO, MARIO TAMBÉM PODE ENCONTRAR O CHAPÉU, A BOLSA E O GUARDA-CHUVA DE PAULINE PARA PONTOS ADICIONAIS.

DONKEY KONG TAMBÉM É NOTÁVEL POR SER UMA DAS PRIMEIRAS NARRATIVAS COMPLETAS EM FORMA DE VIDEOGAME, CONTADAS ATRAVÉS DE CENAS SIMPLES QUE AVANÇAM A HISTÓRIA.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>ECE62B10</hash>
		<image>./images/Donkey Kong (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Donkey Kong (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Donkey Kong (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Donkey Kong (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1379" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon III : The Sacred Stones</name>
		<desc>THE FINAL GAME IN THE TRILOGY.

BILLY AND JIMMY LEE ARE RETURNING FROM MARTIAL ARTS TRAINING WHEN THEIR PATHS CROSS A FORTUNE TELLER. SHE TELLS THEM OF A GREAT EVIL IN EGYPT, THEIR STRONGEST ADVERSARY YET, AND HOW THE ROSETTA STONES CAN AID THEM.

THIS GAME FEATURES WEAPON SHOPS WHERE BILLY AND JIMMY CAN BUY POWER-UPS, TRICKS, ENERGY AND EXTRA LIVES TO AID THEM IN 
THEIR QUEST.

POWER-UPS MAKE BILLY AND JIMMY TWICE THEIR SIZE, INCREASING THEIR DAMAGE DONE AND RANGE OF ATTACK.

THE CHARACTER GRAPHICS HAVE CHANGED, MOVING AWAY FROM CARTOON STYLE GRAPHICS TO MORE REALISTIC LOOKING CHARACTERS.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./images/Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1284" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Double Dragon (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>AMBIENTADO EM UMA NOVA YORK PÓS-APOCALÍPTICA, DOUBLE DRAGON É A HISTÓRIA DE BILLY E JIMMY LEE, IRMÃOS GÊMEOS TREINADOS NO ESTILO DE LUTA DE SOU-SETSU-KEN. JUNTOS, ELES ADMINISTRAM UMA PEQUENA ESCOLA DE TREINAMENTO DE ARTES MARCIAIS, ENSINANDO SEUS ALUNOS EM AUTODEFESA. UM DIA, A NAMORADA DE BILLY, MARIAN, É SEQUESTRADA NA RUA PELOS "BLACK WARRIORS", UMA GANGUE SELVAGEM DE RUA LIDERADA POR UM HOMEM CHAMADO WILLY. OS BLACK WARRIORS EXIGEM QUE OS IRMÃOS LEE DIVULGUEM SEUS SEGREDOS DAS ARTES MARCIAIS EM TROCA DA LIBERDADE DE MARIAN. OS IRMÃOS LEE PARTEM EM UMA MISSÃO DE RESGATE PARA ESMAGAR OS BLACK WARRIORS E SALVAR MARIAN.

USANDO AS TÉCNICAS QUE TÊM À DISPOSIÇÃO, DESDE SOCOS E CHUTES BÁSICOS, ATÉ O GOLPE DE COTOVELO INVULNERÁVEL, BEM COMO QUALQUER ARMA QUE ENTRE EM SUAS MÃOS, OS IRMÃOS LEE DEVEM PERSEGUIR A GANGUE PELA FAVELA DA CIDADE, ÁREA INDUSTRIAL E A FLORESTA, ANTES DE CHEGAR EM SEU SEU ESCONDERIJO PARA ENFRENTAR O GRANDE CHEFE, WILLY.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F3CBEF86</hash>
		<image>./images/Double Dragon (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Double Dragon (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Double Dragon (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Double Dragon (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1561" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Spirit - The New Legend (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Spirit : Aratanaru Densetsu</name>
		<desc>GALDA HAS DECIDED TO ATTACK EARTH AND IT IS UP TO YOU TO STOP HIM.  GALDA HAS TAKEN IRIS, THE SISTER OF LACE CAPTIVE.  YOU ARE LACE WHO, TAKING HIS FATHER'S SWORD, GOES OFF TO DEFEAT GALDA.

YOU HAVE THE ABILITY TO CHANGE INTO A DRAGON AND ARE IN THAT FORM THROUGHOUT THE GAME.  AS A DRAGON, YOU CAN PICK UP POWER-UPS, OR UPGRADES, THAT WILL HELP YOU IN YOUR FIGHT.  UPGRADES CAN INCLUDE EXTRA HEADS ON YOUR DRAGON, HEALTH, FASTER SHOTS, AND MORE.

FLY AROUND AND DESTROY EVERYTHING IN YOUR PATH.  AT THE END OF EACH STAGE, YOU WILL NEED TO DEFEAT A BOSS.  HAVING GOOD UPGRADES THAT ARE NOT LOST FROM BEING HIT BEFORE REACHING THE BOSSES WILL HELP.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7E5A10E7</hash>
		<image>./images/Dragon Spirit - The New Legend (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dragon Spirit - The New Legend (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dragon Spirit - The New Legend (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Spirit - The New Legend (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18652" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Warrior III (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior III</name>
		<desc>DRAGON WARRIOR III IS THE CONCLUDING GAME OF THE FIRST DRAGON QUEST/DRAGON WARRIOR TRILOGY, AND ITS STORY TAKES US BACK TO THE TIME PERIOD OF THE LEGENDARY ERDRICK (ALSO KNOWN AS LOTO), THE ANCESTOR OF THE FIRST GAME'S HERO. YOU ARE THE SON OF A POWERFUL WARRIOR ORTEGA, SKILLFUL IN PHYSICAL COMBAT AND SPELLCASTING. YOUR FATHER WENT OUT TO FIGHT THE EVIL BARAMOS, WHO IS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE APPEARANCE OF MONSTERS IN YOUR REGION, AND NEVER RETURNED. YOU ARE SENT BY THE KING ON A QUEST TO CONTINUE YOUR FATHER'S BRAVE DEEDS AND TO DEFEAT BARAMOS.

DRAGON WARRIOR III IS A TOP-DOWN ROLE-PLAYING GAME WHERE YOU TRAVEL AROUND THE OVERWORLD, CAVES, CASTLES, CITIES AND OTHER LOCATIONS WHILE BATTLING RANDOM ENCOUNTERS, BUYING EQUIPMENT, AND TALKING TO PEOPLE. YOU AND YOUR PARTY MEMBERS RECEIVE EXPERIENCE WHEN THEY BEAT UP MONSTERS AND LEVEL UP WITH ENOUGH EXPERIENCE, INCREASING THEIR STATS. THE GAME FEATURES A DAY/NIGHT CYCLE - AS YOU TRAVEL, DAY SLOWLY CHANGES TO NIGHT AND VICE VERSA; SHOPS ARE TYPICALLY CLOSED AT NIGHT. 

YOU BEGIN WITH CONTROL OF JUST THE MAIN CHARACTER BUT CAN QUICKLY RECRUIT THREE MORE MEMBERS TO YOUR PARTY. DURING THE GAME YOU CAN CHOOSE TO DROP YOUR CURRENT CHARACTERS AND RECRUIT OTHERS AT ANY TIME. THE RECRUITABLE CHARACTERS ARE DIVIDED INTO SIX CLASSES: SOLDIER, FIGHTER, MERCHANT, GOOF-OFF, PILGRIM AND WIZARD.

THE GAME HAS A UNIQUE JOB SYSTEM, GIVING YOU THE ABILITY TO SWITCH YOUR HIRED CHARACTERS' CLASSES AFTER THEY HAVE ACHIEVED AT LEAST LEVEL 20 IN THEIR BASE CLASS. CHARACTERS CAN SWITCH TO THE OTHER BEGINNING CLASSES, AS WELL AS THE SAGE CLASS, WHICH IS NOT AVAILABLE AT THE BEGINNING. WHEN A CHARACTER SWITCHES CLASSES, THEY LOSE ALL EARNED EXPERIENCE POINTS, AND HALF OF THEIR STATS, BUT RETAIN ALL OF THE ABILITIES OF THE PREVIOUS CLASS. IN THIS WAY, YOU CAN CREATE POWERFUL COMBINATION CHARACTERS THAT ARE ABLE TO CAST SPELLS AND FIGHT EFFECTIVELY.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Enix America Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>339508B7</hash>
		<image>./images/Dragon Warrior III (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dragon Warrior III (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dragon Warrior III (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Warrior III (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18650" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Warrior (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior</name>
		<desc>DRAGON WARRIOR IS THE FIRST FAMOUS CONSOLE RPG. YOU ASSUME THE ROLE OF A DESCENDANT OF ERDRICK, A BRAVE WARRIOR OF THE PAST. ONCE UPON A TIME, ERDRICK DEFEATED THE EVIL DRAGONLORD WITH THE HELP OF THE BALL OF LIGHT. NOW, DRAGONLORD STOLE THE BALL OF LIGHT, AND YOUR MISSION IS TO RECOVER IT AND TO RESTORE PEACE IN THE WORLD.

IN DRAGON WARRIOR, YOU MOVE YOUR CHARACTER AROUND IN A TOP-DOWN WORLD. IN CITIES AND PALACES YOU CAN TALK TO PEOPLE, REST IN INNS AND BUY STUFF IN SHOPS. THERE'S A VARIETY OF WEAPONS, EQUIPMENT AND ARMOR TO BUY. 

WHEN WANDERING AROUND IN THE WILDERNESS, YOU OCCASIONALLY ENCOUNTER ENEMIES, AND FIGHT THEM FROM 1ST PERSON PERSPECTIVE. COMBAT IS TURN BASED: YOU SELECT MENU OPTIONS WHILE FIGHTING - YOU CAN ATTACK WITH YOUR WEAPON, CAST A SPELL (USING UP SOME OF YOUR MAGIC ENERGY), USE AND ITEM OR TRY TO RUN. KILLING MONSTERS GIVES YOU EXPERIENCE, AND, AS IS TYPICAL FOR RPGS, YOU LEVEL UP AND IMPROVE YOUR STATS WHEN YOU GAIN ENOUGH EXPERIENCE. 

LIKE IN LATER RPGS, YOU HAVE LIMITED HIT POINTS, LOSE THEM WHEN YOU ARE ATTACKED BY ENEMIES, AND DIE WHEN YOU RUN OUT OF THEM. WHEN YOUR CHARACTER DIES IN A BATTLE, HE IS AUTOMATICALLY RESTORED IN A NEARBY TOWN.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1D8E6A9A</hash>
		<image>./images/Dragon Warrior (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dragon Warrior (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dragon Warrior (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Warrior (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18899" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./The Tower of Druaga (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Druaga no Tou</name>
		<desc>YOU CONTROL A HEROIC KNIGHT, WHO IS ACTUALLY PRINCE GILGAMESH, WHO MUST ATTEMPT TO RESCUE THE MAIDEN FROM THE DEMON DRUAGA. YOU ARE ARMED WITH A SWORD AND SHIELD TO ATTACK AND DEFEND.
YOU MOVE FROM FLOOR TO FLOOR, WHICH ARE CONSTRUCTED AS MAZES, SEARCHING FOR THE KEY, THIS KEY WILL UNLOCK THE STAGE EXIT.
ITEMS CAN BE FOUND BY KILLING (ALL) ENEMIES.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19850806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D09673DA</hash>
		<image>./images/The Tower of Druaga (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/The Tower of Druaga (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/The Tower of Druaga (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/The Tower of Druaga (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1371" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Excitebike (JU) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Excitebike</name>
		<desc>RACE BY YOURSELF AGAINST THE CLOCK OR COMPETE WITH OTHER MOTOCROSS RIDERS ON 5 TRACKS FULL OF LONG STRAIGHTS, LARGE JUMPS AND OBSTACLES TO WIN THE EXCITEBIKE CHAMPIONSHIP.

CREATE YOUR OWN TRACKS BY PLACING JUMPS AND OBSTACLES OF ALL DIFFERENT SIZES AND SHAPES ON THE TRACK AND CHOOSING HOW MANY LAPS EACH RACE WILL HAVE, THEN RACE AGAINST THE CLOCK OR OTHER RIDERS TO SEE HOW YOUR TRACK FARES IN COMPETITION.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19851018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A29D526E</hash>
		<image>./images/Excitebike (JU) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Excitebike (JU) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Excitebike (JU) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Excitebike (JU) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1303" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Faxanadu (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Faxanadu</name>
		<desc>THIS 2D PLATFORMER HAS ELEMENTS OF ROLE-PLAYING AND ADVENTURE IN ADDITION TO SIDE-SCROLLING ACTION.

THE STORY IS A CLASSIC ONE OF GOOD VERSUS EVIL.  DISASTER STRIKES THE ONCE PEACEFUL ELF TOWN OF EOLIS. THE SKY RAINS METEORITES UPON THE WORLD TREE - WILD ANIMALS AND EVIL MONSTERS TERRORIZE THE CITIZENS - THE WATER SUPPLY FROM THE WELLS IS DWINDLING - PLANTS ARE WITHERING - PEOPLE ARE DYING. ONLY YOU CAN RESTORE PEACE TO THE LAND BY CONQUERING THE EVIL ONE, WHO LIVES IN THE EVIL PLACE.

THERE ARE MANY PLACES YOU MUST VISIT DURING YOUR QUEST INCLUDING THE MEDIEVAL TOWN, WHERE YOU BEGIN, COUNTRY VILLAGES, FORTRESSES, CAVES, AND GLOOMY BOGS - EACH WITH ITS OWN AMBIANCE AND MUSICAL SCORE.  YOU WILL BE TALKING WITH THE VILLAGERS, COLLECTING GOLD TO BUY WEAPONS, ARMOR AND OTHER OBJECTS, JUMPING OVER OBSTACLES AND USING ITEMS.  ATTACK ZOMBIES, DWARVES, GIANT SNAKES, WYVERNS, EVIL GNOMES, OR ONE-EYED ONE-FOOTED THINGS WITH A LARGE COLLECTION OF SWORDS AND DAGGERS OR ZAP THEM WITH A MAGIC SPELL. 

AS AREAS ARE COMPLETED BY DEFEATING ENEMIES, YOUR CHARACTER RISES UP IN LEVELS AND ACHIEVES A NEW RANK WHICH IS TIED DIRECTLY TO THE RESTORE PASSWORD (CALLED A MANTRA IN THE GAME). THE HIGHER YOUR RANK, THE MORE GOLD YOU START OUT WITH.  SAVING A GAME CAN ONLY BE DONE IN A SHRINE OR TEMPLE WITH A PRIEST.  THIS IS ALSO WHERE YOU ARE TRANSPORTED WHEN YOU RESTART THE GAME - OR IF YOU DIE.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>68C15C4E</hash>
		<image>./images/Faxanadu (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Faxanadu (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Faxanadu (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Faxanadu (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Felix the Cat Port(U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Felix the Cat Port</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Felix the Cat Port(U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Felix the Cat Port(U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Felix the Cat Port(U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Felix the Cat Port(U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="107882" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fantasy 3 (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<desc>IN A REMOTE VILLAGE OF UR, FOUR ORPHAN BOYS WERE RAISED BY THE PRIEST TOPAPA. ONCE, THE CRYSTAL OF WIND, GUARDED BY THE PEOPLE OF UR, SANK DEEP INTO THE EARTH. THE FOUR BOYS DECIDED TO RETRIEVE IT FROM THERE AND WENT DOWN INTO AN UNDERGROUND CAVE. BUT WHEN THEY FOUND THE CRYSTAL, IT SPOKE TO THEM AND FROM ITS WORDS THEY UNDERSTOOD THEY WERE CHOSEN FOR A MUCH MORE IMPORTANT AND WORLD-EMBRACING MISSION...</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>39473806</hash>
		<image>./images/Final Fantasy 3 (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Final Fantasy 3 (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Final Fantasy 3 (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Final Fantasy 3 (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1252" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fantasy (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy</name>
		<desc>HIRONOBU SAKAGUCHI'S FINAL FANTASY... THE FIRST OF ONE OF THE LONGEST ROLE-PLAYING GAME SERIES KNOWN TO MANKIND. FINAL FANTASY IS THE GAME FOR THE NES CONSOLE THAT STARTED IT ALL.

THE WORLD IS VEILED IN DARKNESS. WINDS DON'T BLOW, THE SEAS ARE STORMY, AND THE EARTH ROTS. ALL PEOPLE CAN HOPE FOR IS THAT THE ANCIENT PROPHECY WILL BE FINALLY FULFILLED. "WHEN THE WORLD IS VEILED IN DARKNESS, FOUR WARRIORS WILL COME..." AND INDEED, THEY COME - THE FOUR CHARACTERS YOU HAVE PREVIOUSLY CHOSEN. THEIR FIRST QUEST IS TO FREE A PRINCESS FROM THE EVIL GARLAND, AND THEN THE REAL JOURNEY BEGINS...

FINAL FANTASY IS PLAYED WITH AN ADVENTURING PARTY RATHER THAN WITH A SINGLE CHARACTER. BEFORE THE GAME STARTS, THE PLAYER CHOOSES FOUR CHARACTERS FROM SIX DIFFERENT CLASSES: FIGHTER, THIEF, BLACK BELT, WHITE MAGE, RED MAGE, AND BLACK MAGE. WHICH FOUR CLASSES THE PLAYER CHOOSES FOR HIS CHARACTERS IS ENTIRELY UP TO HIM. HE ALSO GIVES THE CHARACTERS NAMES. 

IN THE GAME, THE PARTY WALKS AROUND IN A TOP-DOWN WORLD, VISITS CITIES, CAVES, PALACES AND OTHER PLACES TO BUY EQUIPMENT, REST AND GET HINTS AND NEW QUESTS, AND FIGHTS BADDIES WHEN THEY ARE ENCOUNTERED. FINAL FANTASY USES A TURN-BASED COMBAT SYSTEM; THE ATB (ACTIVE-TIME BATTLE) SYSTEM FROM THE LATER INSTALLMENTS IS NOT USED. IN BATTLE, THE PLAYER GIVES EACH CHARACTER IN ORDER A COMMAND (ATTACK A PARTICULAR ENEMY, CAST A SPELL, USE AN ITEM, OR TRY TO RUN.) THEN THE CHARACTERS AND THE ENEMIES ACT IN A RANDOM ORDER. ATTACKED ENEMIES AND PARTY MEMBERS LOSE HIT POINTS, DYING WHEN THEY REACH ZERO HP. WHEN ALL THE ENEMIES ARE DEFEATED, LIVING PARTY MEMBERS RECEIVE EXPERIENCE, EVENTUALLY GAINING A LEVEL AND IMPROVING THEIR STATS WHEN ENOUGH EXPERIENCE IS ACCUMULATED. SLAIN PARTY MEMBERS CAN BE REVIVED IN TOWNS FOR A PRICE. 

SPELLS ARE BOUGHT IN CITIES IN SPECIAL SHOPS. THE SPELLS ARE DIVIDED INTO TWO CATEGORIES - WHITE MAGIC AND BLACK MAGIC. WHITE MAGES CAN ONLY USE WHITE MAGIC, BLACK MAGES CAN ONLY USE BLACK MAGIC, AND RED MAGES CAN USE BOTH. CASTING SPELLS IN BATTLE USES UP MAGIC POINTS, WHICH, LIKE HIT POINTS, CAN BE RESTORED BY RESTING IN INNS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6B736CB8</hash>
		<image>./images/Final Fantasy (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Final Fantasy (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Final Fantasy (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Final Fantasy (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1581" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Frankenstein - The Monster Returns (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Frankenstein : The Monster Returns</name>
		<desc>THE VILLAGERS THOUGHT THEY WERE SAFE. BUT NOW IT IS TIME THEY LEARNED THE TERRIBLE TRUTH... FRANKENSTEIN HAS RISEN, LAID WASTE TO THE LANDS SURROUNDING THE VILLAGE, HAS AMASSED AN EVIL ARMY OF UNHOLY CREATURES AND EVEN GONE SO FAR AS TO CAPTURE A YOUNG GIRL.

FRANKENSTEIN IS A SIDE SCROLLER ADVENTURE AGAINST ALL SORTS OF NIGHTMARISH CREATURES. SOME MIGHT EVEN CALL IT A CLONE OF THE MORE WIDELY KNOWN CASTLEVANIA GAMES OF THE NES. YOU BEGIN THE GAME WITH NOTHING BUT YOUR FISTS... BUT MAY ACQUIRE A MAGICAL CLUB FROM ENEMIES. FINDING ADDITIONAL POWERUPS WITH GIVE THE CLUB THE ABILITY TO TOSS FIREBALLS. THERE ARE TREASURE CHESTS IN VARIOUS ROOMS AS WELL AS CHARACTERS THAT CAN HELP YOU IN YOUR QUEST THROUGH DIALOG HINTS.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9237E579</hash>
		<image>./images/Frankenstein - The Monster Returns (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Frankenstein - The Monster Returns (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Frankenstein - The Monster Returns (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Frankenstein - The Monster Returns (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="71388" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fuzzical Fighter (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Fuzzical Fighter</name>
		<desc>THE WORLD OF FUNNY IS FACING TROUBLED TIMES. THE DIMENSIONAL STONE, WHICH OFFERED PROTECTION TO THIS WORLD, WAS STOLEN. THE KING NEEDS SOMEONE TO LOCATE THE DIMENSIONAL STONE. HE MAKES A REQUEST THAT HIS SUBJECT MARK PILOT THE FLYING CRAFT, CALLED THE FUZ</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910517T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Make Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sigma Enterprises, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>28F88582</hash>
		<image>./images/Fuzzical Fighter (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Fuzzical Fighter (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Fuzzical Fighter (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fuzzical Fighter (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor-Port (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor-Port </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor-Port (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor-Port (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor-Port (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor-Port (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./G.I. Joe (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>G.I. Joe </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/G.I. Joe (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/G.I. Joe (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/G.I. Joe (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/G.I. Joe (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1531" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Galaga (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Galaga</name>
		<desc>GALAGA IS A VERTICAL ARCADE SHOOTER FROM NAMCO.  YOU CONTROL A SPACE FIGHTER AT THE BOTTOM OF THE SCREEN, SCROLLING LEFT AND RIGHT IN ORDER TO AVOID ONCOMING BOMBS AND KAMIKAZE ATTACKS FROM ALIEN INVADERS--AND TO FIRE YOUR OWN MISSILES TO FIGHT BACK!

THERE ARE AN INFINITE NUMBER OF STAGES TO PROGRESS THROUGH.  EVERY THIRD LEVEL IS A "CHALLENGE STAGE" IN WHICH YOU HAVE A FREE CHANCE TO SHOOT AS MANY ALIENS AS POSSIBLE AND RACK UP BONUS POINTS.

CERTAIN ALIENS HAVE TRACTOR BEAMS THEY CAN USE TO CAPTURE ONE OF YOUR SHIPS.  IF THAT WASN'T YOUR LAST "LIFE," YOU CAN TRY TO SHOOT THAT ALIEN DOWN AND RECAPTURE YOUR SHIP, GIVING YOU TWO SHIPS AT ONCE AND DOUBLING YOUR FIREPOWER.

A SUMMARY SCREEN APPEARS WHEN THE GAME IS OVER, GIVING YOU BOTH YOUR FINAL SCORE AND YOU FINAL "HIT RATIO"--THE NUMBER OF MISSILES FIRED, ENEMIES DESTROYED, AND THE PERCENTAGE OF TARGETS HIT.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>A2BDD377</hash>
		<image>./images/Galaga (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Galaga (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Galaga (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Galaga (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1339" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gradius (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Gradius</name>
		<desc>THE PEOPLE OF GRADIUS ARE IN TROUBLE. THE AMEOBOID BACTERIONS HAVE LAUNCHED AN ALL OUT ATTACK AGAINST THE PLANET, AND IT'S UP TO YOU TO FLY INTO BATTLE AND SAVE THEM. ALONG THE WAY YOU'LL BE ABLE TO POWER UP YOUR SHIP WITH HYPER SPEED, FORCE FIELDS, LASERS, MISSILES, DOUBLE BEAM CANNONS AND MORE TO HELP YOU BATTLE. BASED ON THE ARCADE GAME, GRADIUS IS A SIDE SCROLLING SHOOTER. SHOOTING CERTAIN ENEMIES WILL LEAVE A POWER UP POD BEHIND WHICH CAN BE COLLECTED TO ADD MORE POWER TO YOUR SHIP. EACH LEVEL FEATURES A WIDE VARIETY OF ENEMIES TRYING TO STOP YOU, WITH A LARGE BOSS AT THE END. GAMEPLAY IS FOR ONE PLAYER OR TWO PLAYERS ALTERNATING.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19861202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>BB9FD545</hash>
		<image>./images/Gradius (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Gradius (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Gradius (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gradius (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1715" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gun-Nac (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Gun Nac</name>
		<desc>A GALACTIC FEDERATION STARFIGHTER IS SENT OFF TO DESTROY AN ALIEN ARMADA (LED BY GIANT ROBOTIC RABBITS THIS TIME AROUND -- AN UNUSUALLY WHIMSICAL THEME IN KEEPING WITH THE CONTEMPORARY PARODIUS) THREATENING TO COLLAPSE YOUR SYSTEM'S SUN INTO A SUPERNOVA.

GUN-NAC IS A TOP DOWN SHOOTER IN WHICH THE PLAYER CONTROLS THE FEDERATION STARFIGHTER. POWER UPS AND GENRE MECHANICS ARE AS COULD BE EXPECTED FROM A "SHMUP".  NOW WITH COLLECTIBLE MONEY THAT ALLOWS YOU TO SHOP FOR DIFFERENT WEAPONS AND BOMBS TO COMPLEMENT YOUR STANDARD MAIN GUN IN THE INTER-LEVEL WEAPONS MARKET. DIRECTIONAL WEAPONS, ATTACHMENTS AND UP TO FOUR BOMB TYPES CAN ALSO BE BOUGHT TO INCREASE YOUR SURVIVAL CHANCES, FURTHER AIDED BY PLAYER CONTROL OVER THE SPEED AT WHICH YOUR SHIP MOVES THROUGH THE LEVELS. SINGLE PLAYER ONLY.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E9DBD675</hash>
		<image>./images/Gun-Nac (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Gun-Nac (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Gun-Nac (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gun-Nac (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1431" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gun.Smoke (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Gun.Smoke</name>
		<desc>GUN.SMOKE IS A TOP-DOWN SCROLLING SHOOTER THAT CASTS THE GAMER AS A LONE GUNMAN, OUT TO SAVE THE GOLD RUSH TOWN OF HICKSVILLE FROM A FEARSOME GROUP OF BANDITS KNOWN AS THE WINGATES. EACH LEVEL HAS A PARTICULAR TARGET ENEMY, ALTHOUGH HIS OR HER HENCHMEN MUST ALSO BE TAKEN OUT.

ALTHOUGH IT LARGELY TAKES PLACE ON FOOT, THE GAMEPLAY RESEMBLES COMMANDO, WITH ITS TOP-DOWN ACTION. THE SCREEN SCROLLS AT A CONSTANT RATE, AND ENEMIES COME AT YOU FROM THE EDGES, TO BE SHOT OR AVOIDED. YOU CAN GRAB VARIOUS POWER-UPS ALONG THE WAY. FINDING A HORSE WILL ALLOW YOU TO GET HIT TWICE BEFORE YOU DIE RATHER THAN JUST ONCE. THERE ARE SCENES IN WHICH YOU RAFT UP A RIVER AND USE THE TRACKS OF A RAILWAY LINE.

ON THE NES YOU CAN TAP THE A BUTTON TO FIRE UP AND RIGHT, THE B BUTTON TO FIRE UP AND LEFT, OR A AND B SIMULTANEOUSLY TO FIRE STRAIGHT AHEAD. ONE-BUTTON CONTROL SYSTEMS MIMIC ALL THIS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>203C8CAD</hash>
		<image>./images/Gun.Smoke (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Gun.Smoke (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Gun.Smoke (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gun.Smoke (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1615" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gyruss (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Gyruss</name>
		<desc>THE ENTIRE SOLAR SYSTEM IS BEING ATTACKED BY THE VICIOUS GYRUSIANS, AND IT'S UP TO YOU TO SAVE THE DAY! YOU WILL NEED TO FLY YOUR SPACESHIP TO EACH OF THE NINE PLANETS AND THEN CLEAR THREE STAGES OF ENEMIES TO RID THAT PLANET OF THE GYRUSIANS. YOU START THE GAME WITH A SINGLE CANON, AND CAN GAIN A DOUBLE CANON AFTER SHOOTING A POWER UP SATELITE. AFTER CLEARING EACH PLANET, THERE IS ANOTHER BONUS STAGE WHERE ADDITIONAL WEAPONS AND BONUS POINTS CAN BE COLLECTED. GYRUSS IS AN ARCADE ACTION SHOOTER, HOWEVER INSTEAD OF PILOTING YOUR SPACESHIP HORIZONTALLY OR VERTICALLY, YOU MOVE IN A CIRCLE AROUND THE PERIMETER OF THE SCREEN. THE NES VERSION OF GYRUSS ADDS TO THE ORIGINAL ARCADE VERSION ADDITIONAL MUSIC, ADDITIONAL WEAPONS, NEW ENEMIES, AND A LARGE BOSS AT THE END OF EACH LEVEL.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultra</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>01AAEC4A</hash>
		<image>./images/Gyruss (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Gyruss (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Gyruss (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gyruss (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1574" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hudson Hawk (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Hudson Hawk</name>
		<desc>HUDSON HAWK, A CAT BURGLAR, HAS A MISSION: STEAL THREE OF DA VINCI'S WORKS OF ART, WHICH INCLUDE A ROCKING HORSE KNOWN AS "THE SFORZA", HIS SKETCHBOOK THAT HE CALLED "THE CODEX", AND A PRECIOUS CRYSTAL. THE MISSION WILL TAKE HIM THROUGH A MANSION, CASTLES, ROOFTOPS, SUBWAYS, AND THE VATICAN. OF COURSE, GETTING ALL THESE ITEMS WILL NOT BE AS EASY AS IT SOUNDS. NOT ONLY DOES HAWK FACE SECURITY GUARDS, GUARD DOGS, AND OTHERS, BUT HE MUST ALSO AVOID SETTING OFF ALARMS. TO HELP HIM, HAWK CAN EITHER PUNCH ENEMIES, OR THROW A BALL AT THEM.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Special FX Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3F3D215A</hash>
		<image>./images/Hudson Hawk (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Hudson Hawk (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Hudson Hawk (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hudson Hawk (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hudson's Adventure Island II (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Hudson's Adventure Island II </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Hudson's Adventure Island II (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Hudson's Adventure Island II (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Hudson's Adventure Island II (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hudson's Adventure Island II (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1550" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jackal (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Jackal</name>
		<desc>THE ENEMY ARMY HAS CAPTURED TOO MANY OF YOUR FORCES. BEING HELD IN P.O.W. CAMPS, THESE SOLDIERS ARE EFFECTIVELY OUT OF THE WAR... UNLESS SOME KIND OF RESCUE OPERATION CAN BE MOUNTED. HEAVY FORCES ARE TOO SLOW AND VISIBLE TO BE OF ANY USE, BUT PERHAPS SOMETHING SMALLER AND LIGHTER MAY MAKE IT IN WHERE LARGER FORCES WOULD FAIL. A SMALL JEEP, MAYBE TWO, CREWED BY ABOUT 4 PEOPLE.... MINIMAL ENOUGH NOT TO REPRESENT TOO MUCH OF A LOSS AND YET SUITABLE ENOUGH TO AID IN RESCUE. BUT OF COURSE, IF THESE BRAVE MEN WANT TO SUCCEED AND COME BACK ALIVE; THEY'LL NEED TO FIGHT LIKE ANIMALS... THEY'LL NEED TO FIGHT LIKE JACKALS...

JACKAL IS AN OVERHEAD VIEW JEEP GAME FOR UP TO 2 PLAYERS. THE CONTROLLER MOVES IN FOUR DIRECTIONS, BUTTON A FIRES YOUR GERNADES (UPGRADABLE TO BAZOOKA) AND BUTTON B YOUR MACHINE GUN WHICH ALWAYS FIRES TO THE TOP OF THE SCREEN. YOUR MISSION IS TO LOCATE FACILITIES WHERE SOLDIERS ARE BEING HELD PRISONER, RESCUE AS MANY AS POSSIBLE, AND ESCORT THEM TO A SAFE LANDING ZONE WHERE THEY WILL BE AIR TRANSPORTED AWAY. AFTER THAT, YOU'LL NEED TO FIGHT A BOSS BATTLE AGAINST THE ENEMY TO PROGRESS.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>C5193F42</hash>
		<image>./images/Jackal (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Jackal (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Jackal (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jackal (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1484" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Journey to Silius (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Journey To Silius</name>
		<desc>THE YEAR IS 0373 IN THE NEW SPACE AGE CALENDAR. THE EARTH'S POPULATION IS GROWING RAPIDLY, AND PEOPLE ARE NOW FORCED TO START SPACE COLONIES. JAY MCCRAY IS AMONG THOSE LEAVING EARTH AND HEADING TO THE COLONY IN THE SILIUS SOLAR SYSTEM. UNFORTUNATELY, TERRORISTS HAVE DESTROYED A RESEARCH COLONY THERE. JAY'S FATHER WAS KILLED IN THIS ATTACK, AND NOW JAY VOWS TO DESTROY THE TERRORISTS RESPONSIBLE AND TO CONTINUE THE RESEARCH HIS FATHER WAS WORKING ON. JOURNEY TO SILIUS IS A SIDE SCROLLING PLATFORM GAME. ON EACH LEVEL THERE ARE A WIDE VARIETY OF ROBOT ENEMIES GUARDING THE TERRORIST'S FORTRESS, ALONG WITH SEVERAL WEAPONS TO FIND WHICH MAKE YOUR MISSION EASIER. THERE ARE A TOTAL OF SIX STAGES, EACH ENDING WITH A VERY LARGE BOSS.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F4F74046</hash>
		<image>./images/Journey to Silius (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Journey to Silius (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Journey to Silius (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Journey to Silius (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1312" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jurassic Park (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>ONE OF MANY DIFFERENT TITLES BASED ON STEVEN SPIELBERG'S 1993 DINOSAUR THRILLER, THE VERSION FOR NES AND GAME BOY IS A TOP-DOWN ACTION GAME WITH EXPLORATION ELEMENTS.

PLAYING AS DR. ALAN GRANT, THE PLAYER MUST WORK THROUGH SIX LEVELS BY COMPLETING CERTAIN OBJECTIVES INCLUDING RESCUING THE KIDS TIM AND LEX, RESTORING POWER, DESTROYING RAPTOR NESTS AND FINALLY GETTING OFF THE DINOSAUR-INFESTED ISLAND. TO ADVANCE IN A LEVEL, A NUMBER OF DINOSAUR EGGS SCATTERED OVER THE AREA MUST BE COLLECTED OR DESTROYED. THIS WILL REVEAL A PASSCARD USED TO GAIN ENTRY TO BUILDINGS, OR SOME OTHER ITEMS NECESSARY TO COMPLETE THE ASSIGNMENT. THE PARK'S COMPUTER TERMINALS CAN BE USED TO REQUEST HINTS ON WHERE TO GO NEXT.

NATURALLY, THE LEVELS ARE FULL OF HOSTILE DINOSAURS. DR. GRANT CAN FEND THEM OFF WITH HIS GUN. SEVERAL AMMUNITION TYPES ARE AVAILABLE, VARYING IN DAMAGE AND SHOOTING PATTERNS. KILLED DINOSAURS WILL ALWAYS DROP THE MOST BASIC AMMO TYPE, THE OTHERS MUST BE FOUND. NEXT TO AMMO CLIPS, THERE ARE BOXES WITH QUESTION MARKS ON THEM TO BE COLLECTED. THESE MIGHT INCLUDE BENEFICIAL POWERUPS LIKE A HEALTH INCREASE, BUT CAN ALSO BE DANGEROUS AND REVEAL A BOMB.

SOME LEVELS END IN BOSS ENCOUNTERS, INCLUDING A TRICERATOPS STAMPEDE AND A FIGHT AGAINST THE TYRANNOSAURUS REX.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>72941062</hash>
		<image>./images/Jurassic Park (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Jurassic Park (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Jurassic Park (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jurassic Park (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1398" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kabuki - Quantum Fighter (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Kabuki Quantum Fighter</name>
		<desc>IN THIS FUTURISTIC PLATFORM GAME, A COMPUTER VIRUS HAS AFFECTED THE EARTH'S DEFENSE SYSTEMS. A LONE WARRIOR IS TRANSFERRED INTO DIGITAL DATA AND SENT INSIDE THE MAINFRAME, WHERE HE BECOMES A KABUKI WARRIOR. GAMEPLAY IS SIMILAR TO OTHER NINJA-PLATFORMERS (SUCH AS NINJA GAIDEN) BUT WITH SOME INTERESTING MODIFICATIONS, SUCH AS USING YOUR LONG RED HAIR AS A WHIP TO ATTACK ENEMIES!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>27A2C84B</hash>
		<image>./images/Kabuki - Quantum Fighter (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Kabuki - Quantum Fighter (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Kabuki - Quantum Fighter (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kabuki - Quantum Fighter (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1276" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kid Icarus (UE) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Kid Icarus</name>
		<desc>FAR AWAY IN PEACEFUL ANGEL LAND LIVED A YOUNG ANGEL WARRIOR NAMED PIT, WHO HAS BEEN GIVEN THE TASK OF DEFEATING THE MONSTROUS MEDUSA, WHO WISHES TO DESTROY ANGEL LAND AND ALL OF THE PEOPLE, AND SHE HAS STARTED BY KIDNAPPING PALUTENA, THE PRINCESS OF ANGEL LAND.

YOUNG PIT MUST RESCUE THE PRINCESS AND RESTORE PEACE TO ANGEL LAND. HE WILL TRAVEL FROM THE DEEP CAVERNS OF THE UNDERWORLD TO MEDUSA'S PALACE IN THE SKY ON HIS JOURNEY, AND DEADLY MONSTERS WILL ATTACK HIM EVERY STEP OF THE WAY. BUT HE HAS THE POWER OF THE GODS ON HIS SIDE! A POWERFUL BOW AND ARROWS, WATER OF LIFE, AND ANGEL FEATHERS WILL ASSIST PIT ON HIS QUEST TO DESTROY MEDUSA AND SAVE THE PRINCESS!

KID ICARUS IS A PLATFORM GAME WHERE THE PLAYER GOES THROUGH SEVERAL VERTICALLY OUTLAID LEVELS, SHOOTING ENEMIES WITH HIS BOW ON THE WAY AND COLLECTING HEARTS THEY LEAVE BEHIND. PIT'S BOW CAN SHOOT BOTH FORWARD AND UPWARDS. AS PIT CONTINUES UPWARDS, MORE AND MORE OF THE LEVEL ENDS UP BEYOND THE BOTTOM OF THE SCREEN AND IF PIT FALLS DOWN OUT OF THE SCREEN, HE DIES. 

THE LEVELS CONTAIN DOORS WHICH LEAD TO CHAMBERS OF VARIOUS TYPES - SOME CHAMBERS ARE FILLED WITH ENEMIES, SOME ARE TREASURIES WHICH ALLOW PIT TO OBTAIN A POWER-UP, SOME ARE STORES WHERE PIT CAN BUY STUFF, SOME WILL REPLENISH HIS HEALTH, IN SOME PIT WILL BE ABLE TO TAKE A TEST IN HOPES OF GETTING A POWERFUL WEAPON, AND FINALLY SOME CHAMBERS GIVE PIT A CHANCE OF RECEIVING A STRENGTH UPGRADE, THEREFORE INCREASING THE AMOUNT OF DAMAGE HIS ATTACKS DEAL. 

PIT EARNS EXPERIENCE AS HE DEFEATS ENEMIES, AND HE GAINS LEVELS FROM THIS EXPERIENCE. THE MORE LEVELS PIT HAS, THE MORE MAXIMUM HEALTH HE HAS. 

HEARTS TAKEN FROM ENEMIES ARE USED IN SHOPS TO BUY VARIOUS ITEMS AND POWER-UPS. ITEMS INCLUDE A PROTECTIVE SHIELD WHICH HARMS ENEMIES, A MORE POWERFUL BOW, A MALLET WHICH ALLOWS YOU TO SMASH THE POOR PALUTENA'S WARRIORS TURNED TO STONE WHO WILL LATER HELP YOU TO FIGHT A BOSS, A TORCH TO SEE YOURSELF IN DARK AREAS AND OTHERS.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>99412C90</hash>
		<image>./images/Kid Icarus (UE) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Kid Icarus (UE) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Kid Icarus (UE) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kid Icarus (UE) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1322" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kung Fu (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Kung Fu</name>
		<desc>YOU'LL NEED LIGHTNING FAST REACTIONS TO KNOCK OUT THE KNIFE THROWER, STOP THE STICK FIGHTER, AND TRIP UP THE EVIL TOM TOM BROTHERS IN THIS ACTION-PACKED MARTIAL ARTS CONTEST! ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE TOUGH ENOUGH? BECAUSE IT'LL TAKE ALL YOUR STRENGTH AND SKILL TO MASTER THE MOVES IN KUNG FU, BEAT YOUR OPPONENTS, AND RESCUE THE FAIR SYLVIA WHO'S HELD CAPTIVE ON THE TOP FLOOR! THE ACTION IS NON-STOP, AND JUST WHEN YOU THINK YOU'VE GOT YOUR ENEMIES LICKED THERE'S ALWAYS A GIANT, A SNAKE, OR A FIRE-BREATHING DRAGON TO CONTEND WITH IN KUNG FU!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19851002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<hash>55CC5160</hash>
		<image>./images/Kung Fu (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Kung Fu (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Kung Fu (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kung Fu (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1366" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Little Nemo - The Dream Master (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Little Nemo : The Dream Master</name>
		<desc>BASED ON A COMIC STRIP FOR THE 1940'S, NEMO IS A YOUNG BOY FROM LONDON SUMMONED TO THE KINGDOM OF SLUMBERLAND, A FANTASY REALM FILLED WITH STRANGE CREATURES AND DREAM-LIKE LOCATIONS.  YOU SOON LEARN THAT THE KING OF SLUMBERLAND HAS BEEN KIDNAPPED BY THE PRINCE OF NIGHTMARES, AND YOU ARE REQUESTED TO SAVE HIM BY PRINCESS CAMILLE.  USING YOUR ONLY WEAPON, A SACK OF CANDY, YOU STUN ENEMIES AND LULL FRIENDLY ANIMALS INTO HELPING YOU THROUGH LEVELS LIKE THE MUSHROOM FOREST AND TRAIN LAND.  THIS PLATFORMER FEATURED LICENSED CHARACTERS AND ARTWORK FROM THE COMIC, ALONG WITH USING THE ANIMALS, SUCH AS APES AND MOLES, TO TRAVERSE THROUGH THE DIFFERENT TERRAIN.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>68E0C0A5</hash>
		<image>./images/Little Nemo - The Dream Master (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Little Nemo - The Dream Master (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Little Nemo - The Dream Master (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Little Nemo - The Dream Master (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1544" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lode Runner (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Lode Runner</name>
		<desc>THE BUNGELING EMPIRE HAS STOLEN A HUGE CACHE OF GOLD FROM ITS RIGHTFUL OWNERS, AND YOUR MISSION IS TO INFILTRATE ITS TREASURY AND RECAPTURE IT. THIS ENTAILS PROGRESSING THROUGH 150 SCREENS OF PLATFORMS, LADDERS AND ROPES.

THE EMPIRE HAS SENT ROBOTIC GUARDS DOWN TO PROTECT THE GOLD, AND CONTACT WITH ANY OF THESE WILL COST YOU A LIFE. YOUR METHOD OF ESCAPING THEM IS TO PRESS FIRE TO DIG A HOLE IN THEIR LINE OF MOVEMENT, THUS CAUSING THEM TO FALL IN BRIEFLY, ALLOWING YOU TO MOVE ACROSS THE GAP SAFELY. ONCE ALL THE GOLD HAS BEEN COLLECTED, A LADDER ALLOWING YOU TO MOVE ONTO THE NEXT SCREEN IS ADDED. COMPLETING THESE SCREENS OFTEN REQUIRES FORWARD PLANNING AND PRECISION.

THIS WAS ONE OF THE EARLIEST GAMES TO INCLUDE A LEVEL EDITOR, ALLOWING THE CREATION OF NEW LEVEL DESIGNS WITH NO PROGRAMMING SKILL.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19870902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>3C6ABCC2</hash>
		<image>./images/Lode Runner (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Lode Runner (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Lode Runner (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lode Runner (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18808" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lunar Pool (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Lunar Ball</name>
		<desc>THIS IS A FUTURISTIC POOL GAME, IN WHICH THE TABLES ARE DESIGNED IN SEVERAL DIFFERENT SHAPES AND SIZES, WITH POCKETS SOMETIMES SLIGHTLY INWARDS FROM THE CUSHION. THIS MAKES THE GAME MORE SIMILAR TO MINIATURE GOLF THAN CONVENTIONAL POOL. 

YOU CAN SET THE POWER OF EACH SHOT, THOUGH NOT THE SPIN. IN ONE-PLAYER MODE YOU MUST CLEAR THE TABLE WITHOUT MISSING MORE THAN MORE THAN 3 TIMES. THERE ARE 60 DIFFERENT TABLES, AND 255 LEVELS IN TOTAL TO PLAY THROUGH IN SEQUENCE, AND YOU CAN ALSO ALTER THE FRICTION LEVEL. YOU CAN ALSO GO HEAD TO HEAD WITH ANOTHER PLAYER.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19871001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blue Pony, INC|Compile</developer>
		<publisher>FCI</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D6349E3D</hash>
		<image>./images/Lunar Pool (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Lunar Pool (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Lunar Pool (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lunar Pool (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1549" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mach Rider (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Mach Rider</name>
		<desc>MACH RIDER IS A MOTORCYCLE COMBAT GAME SET IN A POST-APOCALYPTIC FUTURE. PLAYERS, REPRESENTED BY MACH RIDER, MUST MAKE THEIR WAY ACROSS TEN SECTORS TO REACH THE CITY BEFORE IT GETS TAKEN OVER BY THE ENEMY. AGGRESSIVE DRIVERS TRY TO FORCE PLAYERS OFF THE ROAD; OBSTACLES, SUCH AS ROCKS, AND THE ROAD'S MANY TURNS ALSO CAN CAUSE PLAYERS TO VEER OFF COURSE. IF DESTROYED, MACH RIDER WILL REFORM HIMSELF SO THAT HE CAN CONTINUE.

THERE ARE THREE DIFFERENT PLAY MODES IN MACH RIDER.

ON THE FIGHTING COURSE, THERE ARE TWO PATHS TO CHOOSE FROM. THE GOAL MUST BE REACHED WHILE SHOOTING DOWN ENEMIES OR FORCING THEM OFF THE ROAD; MORE POINTS ARE REWARDED BY BUMPING OFF ENEMIES. UNLIMITED LIVES ARE AVAILABLE FOR THE FIRST STAGE, BUT REMAINING COURSES MUST BE FINISHED IN THREE LIVES OR LESS.

ON THE ENDURANCE AND SOLO COURSES, THERE IS A CERTAIN DISTANCE THAT MUST BE GONE BEFORE THE TIME RUNS OUT. ENEMIES ARE ON THE ENDURANCE COURSE, BUT THE SOLO COURSE IS DEVOID OF ENEMIES.

THERE IS ALSO A LEVEL EDITOR (SIMILAR TO THE ONE IN EXCITEBIKE) THAT ALLOWS CREATION OF ENDURANCE COURSE TRACKS, WHICH ARE ERASED ONCE THE NES IS TURNED OFF.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19851018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DFCED94E</hash>
		<image>./images/Mach Rider (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mach Rider (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mach Rider (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mach Rider (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1511" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Totally Rad (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Magic John</name>
		<desc>TOTALLY RAD IS AN ACTION-ADVENTURE GAME IN WHICH YOU PLAY JAKE, A MAGICIAN WANNABE BEING TRAINED BY THE MASTER MAGICIAN ZEBEDIAH. ONE DAY, DURING HIS TRAINING, JAKE IS ATTACKED BY SURPRISE BY UNKNOWN FOES WHO KIDNAP ALLISON, HIS GIRLFRIEND. THEN, JAKE HAS TO SAVE HER AND DISCOVER WHAT LIES BEHIND THAT ATTACK.

THIS GAME IS A SIDE-SCROLLING ONE, WITH THE BASIC CONTROLS COMMON TO MANY OF THOSE GAMES THAT FALL IN THE SAME CATEGORY: MOVING, JUMPING AND SHOOTING. YOUR BASIC WEAPON IS SOMETHING LIKE AN ENERGY BALL THAT CAN BE CHARGED BY HOLDING THE BUTTON FOR A FEW SECONDS UNTIL ITS MAXIMUM POWER. ALTHOUGH JAKE IS SUPPOSED TO STILL BE LEARNING HIS MAGIC FROM ZEBEDIAH, FROM THE VERY BEGINNING YOU CAN USE ALL HIS MAGICAL POWERS. YOU CAN SELECT WHICH MAGIC YOU WANT TO USE FROM A LIST, DISPLAYED WHEN YOU PRESS THE START BUTTON. THE MAGICAL POWERS AVAILABLE INCLUDE HEALING, TIME STOPPING, INVINCIBILITY, THE POWER OF THE ELEMENTS (FIRE, WATTER, WIND AND EARTH) AND 3 DIFFERENT METAMORPHOSIS. YOU CAN MORPH INTO A FLYING GUY WHO THROWS SOMETHING LIKE A BOOMERANG (THAT DOESN'T COME BACK), A FISH-LIKE GUY, WHO THROWS SOMETHING LIKE NINJA STARS AND CAN SWIM, AND A FELINE-LIKE GUY, WHO RELEASES ELECTRICAL SHOCKS FROM HIS HANDS AND BECOMES INVINCIBLE WHILE JUMPING. YOU DO NOT EVOLVE DURING THE GAME, AS YOUR HEALTH AND MAGIC BAR DOESN'T GROW.

TOTALLY RAD, AS THE NAME POINTS OUT, IS A GAME FULL OF SLANG, WITH THE CONSTANT USE OF WORDS LIKE TOTALLY, GNARLY, DUDE, EXCELLENT, DECENT, RIGHTEOUS, ETC.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19911102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>83761F42</hash>
		<image>./images/Totally Rad (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Totally Rad (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Totally Rad (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Totally Rad (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1784" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Krion Conquest, The (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Magical Kid's Doropie</name>
		<desc>THE KRION EMPIRE CHOSE THE YEAR 1999 IN WHICH TO STAGE AN INVASION OF EARTH. THE PLANET'S DEFENSES WERE NO MATCH FOR THE ALIEN ROBOT INVADERS. FORTUNATELY, A WITCH NAMED FRANCESCA HAS TAKEN IT UPON HERSELF TO SINGLE-HANDEDLY FREE MANKIND FROM THIS SCOURGE.

THE GAMEPLAY AND ARTISTIC STYLE ARE HEAVILY INFLUENCED BY THE NES MEGA MAN GAMES (SOME CONTEND THE ELEMENTS ARE "BORROWED" OR "STOLEN", IN FACT). THE GAME IS A SIDE SCROLLER IN WHICH THE HEROINE CAN WIELD A VARIETY OF DIFFERENT OFFENSIVE CAPABILITIES (ALL AVAILABLE FROM THE START OF THE GAME), SELECTABLE VIA A SUBSCREEN IN HER QUEST TO WIPE OUT WAVE AFTER WAVE OF ROBOT INVADERS THROUGHOUT THE FOUR LEVELS. YOU ALSO HAVE A LIMITED RANGE BROOMSTICK AT YOUR DISPOSAL FOR RIDING ACROSS CHASMS AND SUCH.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vic Tokai</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>33B7B182</hash>
		<image>./images/Krion Conquest, The (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Krion Conquest, The (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Krion Conquest, The (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Krion Conquest, The (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1785" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mappy (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Mappy</name>
		<desc>YOU CONTROL MAPPY A POLICE-MOUSE WHOSE JOB IS TO COLLECT VALUABLES (CONSUMER ELECTRONICS)FROM A CAT'S HOUSE. YOU ARE BEING PURSUED BY A GANG OF FIVE PINK CATS. DOORS ARE YOUR ONLY DEFENSE AGAINST THE CATS. YOU GET FROM FLOOR TO FLOOR BY JUMPING ON ONE OF THE TRAMPOLINES.
POINTS ARE EARNED BY RECOVERING STOLEN GOODS. OTHER WAYS OF EARNING POINTS ARE BOUNCING ON A TRAMPOLINE, PUTTING CATS IN THE MICROWAVE, STRIKING A CAT WITH A DOOR, STRIKING CATS WITH A BELL, RETRIEVING A TREASURES FROM THE BOSS CAT GORO OR DROPPING CATS THROUGH A HOLE IN THE FLOOR.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>0BD2F3AB</hash>
		<image>./images/Mappy (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mappy (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mappy (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mappy (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1872" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mappy-Land (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Mappy-Land</name>
		<desc>MAPPY THE MOUSE HAS A GIRLFRIEND NAMED MAPICA. IN ORDER TO PLEASE HIS GIRLFRIEND, MAPPY GOES ON A MISSION TO COLLECT GIFTS FOR HIS SIGNIFICANT OTHER. UNFORTUNATELY THE BOSS CAT NYAMCO AND HIS LEGION OF PINK CATS WANT TO TRACK MAPPY DOWN SO THEY CAN MAKE A MEAL OUT OF HIM. THE GOAL OF THE GAME IS TO COLLECT 6 OF 1 ITEM IN EACH STAGE WITHOUT GETTING EATEN BY A CAT. THE ITEMS YOU COLLECT (EITHER PIECES OF CHEESE, WEDDING RINGS, CHRISTMAS TREES, OR BASEBALLS) VARY DEPENDING ON WHAT STAGE YOUR PLAYING.  THERE ARE ALSO STAGE SPECIFIC ITEMS IN THE BACKGROUND THAT WILL HELP YOU DEFEAT YOUR FELINE ADVERSARIES.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19890401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taxan</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3AEE0BC7</hash>
		<image>./images/Mappy-Land (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mappy-Land (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mappy-Land (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mappy-Land (Mr.Magoo) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1274" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rockman (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man</name>
		<desc>NA FUTURA CIDADE DE MONSTEROPOLIS, O USO DO TRABALHO ROBÓTICO AJUDOU A CIVILIZAÇÃO A CRESCER MAIS DO QUE NUNCA. NA VANGUARDA DESSA TECNOLOGIA ESTÁ O DR. LIGHT E SEU ASSISTENTE DR. WILY, QUE SÃO CONTRATADOS PARA CONSTRUIR SEIS ROBÔS PARA LIDAR COM UMA VARIEDADE DE TAREFAS ESPECÍFICAS. ELES SÃO CHAMADOS BOMBMAN, GUTSMAN, ICEMAN, CUTMAN, ELECMAN E FIREMAN EM REFERÊNCIA ÀS SUAS FUNÇÕES PRINCIPAIS INDIVIDUAIS. O DR. WILY, NO ENTANTO, TEM PLANOS MAIORES E OPTA POR ASSUMIR O CONTROLE DOS ROBÔS E PERMITIR A DESTRUIÇÃO EM UMA TENTATIVA DE CONTROLE MUNDIAL. DR. LIGHT LUTA DE VOLTA COM A MELHOR FERRAMENTA QUE ELE TEM, UM ROBÔ HUMANO EXPERIMENTAL, MEGA MAN, QUE FOI TESTADO PARA REALIZAR TAREFAS DE LIMPEZA. AGORA, DEVIDAMENTE ARMADO, CABE A MEGA MAN ENFRENTAR OS ROBÔS REBELDES, LUTAR CONTRA O CASTELO DO DR. WILY E ACABAR COM ESSA LOUCURA.NNNNMEGA MAN É UM JOGO DE PLATAFORMAS DE ROLAGEM LATERAL. O HERÓI A SEU COMANDO TEM A CAPACIDADE DE PULAR E DISPARAR SUA ARMA. ELE DEVE VIAJAR PARA OS NÍVEIS DOS SEIS MESTRES DO ROBÔ E DERROTÁ-LOS EM COMBATE. AO FAZER ISSO, MEGA MAN É CAPAZ DE ADQUIRIR SEU PODER PARA SI MESMO. ESSES PODERES PODEM SER USADOS ??ALTERNADAMENTE COM SUA ARMA PRINCIPAL E DIRECIONAR AS FRAQUEZAS DE CHEFES INIMIGOS ESPECÍFICOS. ALÉM DISSO, ALGUMAS ÁREAS OCULTAS DOS NÍVEIS SÓ PODEM SER ACESSADAS USANDO CERTAS ARMAS DE ROBÔS CAPTURADAS.NNNNVIAJANDO POR TODOS ESSES NÍVEIS, MEGA MAN É CONFRONTADO POR UM EXÉRCITO DE CRIAÇÕES DE ROBÔS MENORES QUE QUANDO DESTRUÍDOS GERALMENTE DERRUBAM CÁPSULAS DE ENERGIA (PARA REABASTECER SUA ENERGIA), CÁPSULAS DE ARMAS (PARA REABASTECER AS ARMAS COLETADAS DE ROBÔS) E VIDAS EXTRAS EM FORMA DE CABEÇA DE MEGA MAN.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19871201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>43456056</hash>
		<image>./images/Rockman (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Rockman (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Rockman (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rockman (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Megaman II (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Megaman II </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Megaman II (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Megaman II (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Megaman II (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Megaman II (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Megaman III (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Megaman III </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Megaman III (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Megaman III (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Megaman III (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Megaman III (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Megaman IV (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Megaman IV </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Megaman IV (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Megaman IV (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Megaman IV (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Megaman IV (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Megaman V (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Megaman V </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Megaman V (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Megaman V (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Megaman V (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Megaman V (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Megaman VI (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Megaman VI </name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Megaman VI (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Megaman VI (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Megaman VI (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Megaman VI (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1280" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Metal Gear (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Gear</name>
		<desc>NEAR THE END OF THE 20TH CENTURY, A SMALL FORTIFIED NATION NAMED OUTER HEAVEN (FOUNDED BY A MYSTERIOUS WAR HERO WHOSE NAME AND IDENTITY ARE SHROUDED IN SECRECY) IS THREATENING THE NATIONS OF THE "WEST" WITH THE DEVELOPMENT OF A NEW PROTOTYPE WEAPON NAMED METAL GEAR, A WALKING TANK WHICH IS CAPABLE OF LAUNCHING NUCLEAR WARHEADS FROM ANYWHERE ON THE GLOBE. AS FOX-HOUND'S (AN ELITE BLACK OPS UNIT) NEWEST RECRUIT, GOING BY THE CODENAME OF SOLID SNAKE, YOUR MISSION IS TO INFILTRATE OUTER HEAVEN AND RESCUE YOUR MISSING COMRADE, GREY FOX (WHO WAS CAPTURED AFTER A FAILED INFILTRATION), WHILE GATHERING INTELLIGENCE ON METAL GEAR. IN ORDER TO FULFILL YOUR OBJECTIVE, YOU MUST COLLECT VARIOUS WEAPONS AND EQUIPMENTS (INCLUDING KEYCARDS FOR FURTHER ACCESS INTO THE FORTRESS), WHILE AVOIDING VISUAL CONTACT WITH THE ENEMY. THE PLAYER MUST ALSO CONFRONT AGAINST BOSSES IN THE FORM OF OUTER HEAVEN'S ELITE MERCENARY FORCE AND RESCUE HOSTAGES HIDDEN WITHIN THE FORTRESS IN ORDER TO INCREASE THEIR RANK, WHICH GIVES THE PLAYER AN EXTENDED LIFE BAR AND INCREASED STORAGE CAPACITY FOR REPLENISHABLE ITEMS AND AMMO. THE PLAYER CAN USE A WIRELESS TRANSCEIVER TO COME IN TOUCH WITH THEIR COMMANDING OFFICER, BIG BOSS, TO LEARN MORE ABOUT THEIR CURRENT MISSION OBJECTIVES OR CONTACT ONE OF THE LOCAL RESISTANCE MEMBERS OPERATING COVERTLY WITHIN THE FORTRESS TO GAIN USEFUL TIPS AND INSIGHTS.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>108FD1AD</hash>
		<image>./images/Metal Gear (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Metal Gear (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Metal Gear (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Metal Gear (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1256" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Metroid (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Metroid</name>
		<desc>NO FUTURO, A FEDERAÇÃO GALÁCTICA E OS PIRATAS DO PLANETA ZEBES ESTÃO EM GUERRA. PIRATAS ROUBARAM UMA FORMA DE VIDA DESCONHECIDA, RECENTEMENTE DESCOBERTA NO PLANETA SR388. A FORMA DE VIDA, DESIGNADA "METROID", ESTÁ EM ESTADO DE ANIMAÇÃO SUSPENSA E, SEGUNDO A ANÁLISE, FOI A CAUSA DA DESTRUIÇÃO COMPLETA DO SR388. SE O METROID SE SOLTASSE, O ALIENÍGENA PODERIA DESTRUIR INÚMEROS OUTROS SISTEMAS. CABE À CAÇADORA DE RECOMPENSAS ESPACIAL SAMUS ARAN POUSAR EM ZEBES E ENCONTRAR SEU CAMINHO ATRAVÉS DOS PERIGOSOS TERRENOS DE BRINSTAR E NORFAIR, DESTRUIR OS PIRATAS, ASSIM COMO SEUS AGENTES ALIENÍGENAS, RIDLEY E KRAID, E LIVRAR O PLANETA DA VIDA ALIENÍGENA. ANTES QUE OS PIRATAS COMPLETEM SEUS PLANOS DE DESTRUIÇÃO MUNDIAL.NNNNUSANDO OS APRIMORAMENTOS CIBERNÉTICOS DE SEU TRAJE DE PODER, SAMUS PODE USAR UMA VARIEDADE DE ARMAS E DEFESAS PARA DESTRUIR O INIMIGO. ELA TAMBÉM PODE ABSORVER PODERES DE INIMIGOS EM SEU TRAJE DE PODER PARA AUMENTAR SUA DEFESA E CHANCES DE SOBREVIVÊNCIA. USANDO SUAS ARMAS E HABILIDADES ESPECIAIS, ELA PRECISA ENCONTRAR O CAMINHO PARA A CÂMARA CENTRAL DE TOURIAN E DESTRUIR A MOTHER BRAIN, A MISTERIOSA LÍDER POR TRÁS DOS PIRATAS ESPACIAIS.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F1F53A80</hash>
		<image>./images/Metroid (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Metroid (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Metroid (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Metroid (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1485" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mighty Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Mighty Final Fight</name>
		<desc>CAPCOM'S ONLY 8-BIT PORT OF THE FINAL FIGHT SERIES, MIGHTY FINAL FIGHT FOLLOWS THE STORYLINE AND CHARACTERS OF THE FIRST FINAL FIGHT GAME. MAYOR OF METRO CITY MIKE HAGGAR, HIS NINJA FRIEND GUY AND HIS DAUGHTER'S BOYFRIEND, CODY LEARN THAT HAGGAR'S DAUGHTER, JESSICA,  HAS BEEN KIDNAPPED BY THE MAD GEAR GANG WHOSE LEADER HAS FALLEN IN LOVE WITH HER, AND ALSO WANTS THE MEDDLING MIKE HAGGAR TO LEAVE TOWN. NOW IT'S PERSONAL! CHOOSING ONE OF THE THREE FIGHTERS, THE PLAYER EMBARKS ON A BEAT-EM-UP QUEST THROUGH THE STREETS OF METRO CITY.

THE GAME IS A SIDE-SCROLLING BEAT 'EM UP AND A ONE-PLAYER ONLY GAME (UNLIKE OTHER FINAL FIGHT PORTS). ALSO EXCLUSIVE TO THIS PARTICULAR FINAL FIGHT GAME IS THE EXPERIENCE SYSTEM WHICH ALLOWS GAINING LEVELS TO LEARN ADDITIONAL MOVES, SIMILAR TO THE FIRST DOUBLE DRAGON GAME. THE CHARACTERS HAVE ALL BEEN SQUISHED DOWN TO SUPER-DEFORMED 8-BIT LIKENESSES.  GRAPHICALLY THIS LOOKS SIMILAR TO RIVER CITY RANSOM. EACH CHARACTER HAS A BUTTON FOR ATTACK AND A BUTTON FOR JUMPING. PRESSING THE TWO TOGETHER UNLEASHES A CHARACTER-SPECIFIC SUPER-MOVE. VARIOUS GRABBING MOVES AND THROWS CAN ALSO BE DONE BY MOVING THE PLAYER NEAR AN ENEMY.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6E6F3630</hash>
		<image>./images/Mighty Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mighty Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mighty Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mighty Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18735" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mitsume ga Tooru (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Mitsume ga Tooru</name>
		<desc>MITSUME GA TOORU (TRANSLATES TO THE THREE-EYED ONE) IS BASED ON THE MANGA AND ANIME OF THE SAME NAME. YOU CONTROL HOSUKE SHARAKU - A BOY WITH A THIRD EYE ON HIS FOREHEAD AND OF TERRIFYING POWER. THIS POWER IS UNLEASHED WHEN HIS THIRD EYE IS OPEN SO HE IS WEARING A BANDAGE TO SEAL HIS POWER AND REMOVE ANY MEMORIES OF HIS TRUE NATURE.

IN THE GAME, ANOTHER THREE-EYED MAN WITH GREAT POWERS APPEARS AND ATTACKS A CITY. HE ALSO KIDNAPS SHARAKUS FRIEND WATO WHO WATCHES UNABLE TO DO ANYTHING. SHARAKU THEN, WITH THE BANDAGE REMOVED, BEGINS HIS QUEST TO SAVE WATO FROM THIS MAN.

THE CHARACTER YOU CONTROL CAN FIRE SHOTS OF ENERGY FROM HIS FOREHEAD EYE TO ATTACK THE ENEMIES THAT INHABIT THE 5 STAGES OF THE GAME. HE CAN ALSO SUMMON THE RED CONDOR  A HARPOON THAT CAN BE USED FOR ATTACKING OR REACHING HIGHER PLACES. ALONG THE WAY YOU WILL FIND PLACES WHERE YOU CAN BUY EXTRA LIVES, DIFFERENT WEAPONS AND AN IMPROVED VERSION OF THE RED CONDOR. MONEY CAN BE GAINED FROM DEFEATING ENEMIES OR BY SHOOTING INVISIBLE CHICKENS THAT CAN BE FOUND IN CERTAIN LEVELS. YOU CAN ALSO INCREASE THE VALUE OF A COIN THAT IS LEFT BEHIND BY AN ENEMY IF YOU SHOOT IT MULTIPLE TIMES.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920717T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Tomy</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7A859EB4</hash>
		<image>./images/Mitsume ga Tooru (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mitsume ga Tooru (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mitsume ga Tooru (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mitsume ga Tooru (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1994" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Monster in my Pocket (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Monster In My Pocket</name>
		<desc>THE EVIL WARLOCK WANTS TO TAKE OVER THE WORLD! HE CALLS HIS FELLOW MONSTERS TO JOIN HIM, BUT SEVERAL REFUSE - AND AFTER CASTING A SHRINKING SPELL THAT BACKFIRES AND SHRINKS DOWN ALL THE MONSTERS AROUND HIM, TRANSPORTING THEM TO DIFFERENT HOMES IN LOS ANGELES.

WARLOCK DIDN'T LET HIS SIZE IMPAIRMENT GET IN THE WAY OF WORLD DOMINATION, HOWEVER, SO IT'S UP TO THE VAMPIRE AND THE MONSTER TO STOP HIM! ALONG THE WAY, BOTH CHARACTERS WILL HAVE TO FIGHT THROUGH WARLOCK'S HENCHMONSTERS THROUGH THE STREETS, SEWERS, A CONSTRUCTION AREA AND EVEN A JAPANESE GARDEN.

THE GAME FEATURES CLASSIC PLATFORMING ACTION. THE PLAYER ONLY HAS ONE ALL-PURPOSE ATTACK AND THEY CAN ALSO DOUBLE JUMP TO AVOID ENEMIES OR REACH HIGH LEDGES. THE PLAYER CAN ALSO PICK UP SMALL OBJECTS AND USE THEM TO ATTACK SEVERAL ENEMIES AT ONCE. IF THERE'S ONLY ONE PLAYER, THEY CAN CHOOSE BETWEEN THE VAMPIRE OR THE MONSTER. OR IF THEY DON'T WANT TO GO ALONE, A FRIEND CAN JOIN IN AND HELP THEM BEAT WARLOCK IN THE TWO PLAYER CO-OP MODE.

THE GAME IS BASED ON THE MONSTER IN MY POCKET TOY FRANCHISE. THE PACKAGE ALSO INCLUDED A LIMITED EDITION MONSTER IN MY POCKET TOY, BLEMMYEA (#81), WHICH WAS ONLY AVAILABLE WITH THIS GAME.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Palcom</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>1A78DD22</hash>
		<image>./images/Monster in my Pocket (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Monster in my Pocket (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Monster in my Pocket (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Monster in my Pocket (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nightmare on Elm Street, A (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Nightmare on Elm Street, A</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Nightmare on Elm Street, A (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Nightmare on Elm Street, A (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Nightmare on Elm Street, A (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nightmare on Elm Street, A (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18921" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ninja Crusaders (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Crusaders</name>
		<desc>IN NINJA CRUSADERS, A FORCE OF ALIEN INVADERS HAS DESCENDED UPON THE EARTH AND HAS WIPED OUT HUMANITY FOR THE MOST PART. SOME NINJAS SURVIVED THE ONSLAUGHT, HOWEVER, AND 2 NINJAS IN PARTICULAR NAMED BLADE AND TALON ARE ASSIGNED TO RID THE EARTH OF THIS ALIEN MENACE.

NINJA CRUSADERS IS A SIDE-SCROLLING ACTION GAME THAT CAN BE PLAYED ALONE OR WITH 2 PLAYERS FIGHTING SIDE BY SIDE. A NINJA PLAYER CAN JUMP QUITE HIGH AND BEGINS THE GAME WITH A NINJA THROWING STAR WEAPON THAT CAN TRAVEL THE LENGTH OF THE SCREEN, ALTHOUGH IT'S NOT VERY POWERFUL. OTHER WEAPONS ARE AVAILABLE FOR THE TAKING THROUGHOUT THE LEVELS, EACH WITH CONSIDERABLY LESS RANGE THAN THE STARS BUT WITH MORE POWER. THESE WEAPONS INCLUDE A CHAIN WHIP, A SWORD, AND A BO STAFF. BATTLE YOUR WAY PAST VISTAS OF A POST-APOCALYPTIC WORLD BUT TRY NOT TO GET HIT BECAUSE ONE ENEMY STRIKE WILL TAKE CARE OF YOUR NINJA.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NMK</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy Studios</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F1DE3F19</hash>
		<image>./images/Ninja Crusaders (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ninja Crusaders (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ninja Crusaders (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ninja Crusaders (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1451" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden 2 - The dark sword of chaos (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden II : The Dark Sword of Chaos</name>
		<desc>A YEAR AFTER THE EVENTS OF THE ORIGINAL NINJA GAIDEN, A NEW VILLAIN NAMED ASHTAR RECEIVES WORD OF JAQUIO'S DEFEAT. ASHTAR USES THIS OPPORTUNITY TO HATCH A NEW PLAN TO PLUNGE THE WORLD INTO DARKNESS. THE NINJA, RYU HAYABUSA, HITS THE TRAIL TO DESTROY ALL.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19900501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>150109E2</hash>
		<image>./images/Ninja Gaiden 2 - The dark sword of chaos (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ninja Gaiden 2 - The dark sword of chaos (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ninja Gaiden 2 - The dark sword of chaos (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ninja Gaiden 2 - The dark sword of chaos (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1414" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden 3 - The Ancient Ship of Doom (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden III : The Ancient Ship of Doom</name>
		<desc>THIS IS THE THIRD ENTRY IN THE SERIES OF FAST-PACED NINJA ACTION GAMES, AND IS THE LAST GAME IN THE SERIES TO BE RELEASED ON THE NINTENDO ENTERTAINMENT SYSTEM.

SOME TIME HAS PASSED SINCE THE DEFEAT OF ASHTAR AND THE RESURRECTED JAQUIO, AND IRENE LEW HAS RECEIVED A NEW MISSION TO COMPLETE. SHE IS TO OBSERVE A STRANGE FACTORY THAT HAS BEEN CONSTRUCTED RECENTLY FOR AN UNKNOWN PURPOSE, AND INVESTIGATE IT. SHE PROCEEDS TO RECONNOITER IT, BUT IS INTERCEPTED AND APPARENTLY ASSASSINATED BY HER FRIEND RYU HAYABUSA...EXCEPT IT ISN'T RYU. IT IS AN IMPOSTER. THE REAL RYU, ANGERED OVER HER DEATH, AND THE SUBSEQUENT FALSE ACCUSATION THAT HE MURDERED HER, CONTINUES HER MISSION AND PROCEEDS TO INVESTIGATE THE FACTORY.

AS STATED, THIS WAS THE LAST GAME IN THE REGULAR SERIES PRODUCED FOR THE NES. IT HAD MANY FEATURES THE PREVIOUS GAMES IN THE SERIES DID NOT, SUCH AS A POWER UP TO EXTEND THE LENGTH OF YOUR SWORD, A NEW VERTICAL "WAVE" ATTACK AND VERTICALLY-SCROLLING LEVELS. THE US VERSION OF THE GAME IS REPUTED TO BE THE HARDEST IN THE SERIES, DUE TO THE EXTRA DAMAGE INCURRED WHEN HIT, SLIGHTLY SHORTER REGULAR SWORD LENGTH, LIMITED CONTINUES AND MORE ENEMIES.

THE LYNX PORT IS THE SECOND NINJA GAIDEN GAME ON THE PLATFORM, THE FIRST BEING A PORT FROM THE ARCADE VERSION. THIS PORT IS IDENTICAL TO THE NES GAME, BUT THE IN-GAME PICTURE IS COMPRESSED FOR THE SMALLER SCREEN OF THE LYNX.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B4C90630</hash>
		<image>./images/Ninja Gaiden 3 - The Ancient Ship of Doom (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ninja Gaiden 3 - The Ancient Ship of Doom (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ninja Gaiden 3 - The Ancient Ship of Doom (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ninja Gaiden 3 - The Ancient Ship of Doom (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18922" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden</name>
		<desc>NINJA GAIDEN BEGINS WITH A CINEMATIC ANIMATION IN WHICH 2 NINJAS DUEL TO THE DEATH; ONE GOES DOWN. IT IS REVEALED THAT THE DOOMED NINJA IS THE FATHER OF RYU HAYABUSA. WHEN RYU LEARNS OF THIS, HE EMBARKS ON A QUEST TO FIND OUT WHO KILLED HIS FATHER AND WHY. THIS QUEST TAKES HIM TO AMERICA TO FIND AN ARCHAEOLOGIST WITH WHOM RYU'S FATHER WAS WORKING. FROM THERE, RYU BECOMES EMBROILED IN AN EVIL, SUPERNATURAL CONSPIRACY INVOLVING A VILLAIN NAMED JAQUIO WHO HAS PLANS TO USE AN ANCIENT CASTLE AND SOME RELICS TO UNLEASH A TERRIFYING EVIL UPON THE WORLD.

NINJA GAIDEN IS A SIDE SCROLLING GAME WHERE RYU THE NINJA CAN RUN, JUMP, AND SLASH WITH HIS NINJA SWORD. HE CAN ALSO ATTACH TO ANY VERTICAL SURFACE. POWERUPS ARE LITTERED THROUGHOUT THE LANDSCAPE THAT ALLOW RYU TO TOSS FIREBALLS AND NINJA STARS, AND PERFORM OTHER FEATS.

RYU WILL BATTLE THROUGH URBAN CITY SETTINGS, FORESTS, JUNGLES, SNOW COVERED CASTLES, UNDERGROUND RAILROADS, AND ANCIENT CASTLES. A MAJOR FEATURE IN NINJA GAIDEN ARE THE CINEMATIC SCENES -- SOMETIMES FULLSCREEN -- THROUGH WHICH THE STORYLINE UNFOLDS.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8182B398</hash>
		<image>./images/Ninja Gaiden (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ninja Gaiden (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ninja Gaiden (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ninja Gaiden (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1577" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Othello (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Othello</name>
		<desc>OTHELLO IS A CONVERSION OF THE BOARD GAME. EACH PLAYER TRIES TO FILL THE GAME BOARD WITH AS MANY DISCS OF HIS COLOR AS POSSIBLE. ON EACH TURN THE PLAYER PLACES A DISC ON THE BOARD BY SELECTING A LOCATION WHERE THE  OPPONENTS DISCS WILL BECOME TRAPPED BETWEEN TWO OF HIS DISCS. THE TRAPPED DISCS ARE FLIPPED OVER TO THE PLAYERS COLOR. THE GAME ENDS WHEN THE BOARD IS FILLED OR TIME RUNS OUT, AND THE PLAYER WITH THE GREATEST NUMBER OF HIS COLOR DISCS ON THE BOARD WINS. TWO PLAYERS CAN PLAY AGAINST EACH OTHER, OR ONE PLAYER AGAINST THE COMPUTER.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19881201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kawada, Co. Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>8D1F22DA</hash>
		<image>./images/Othello (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Othello (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Othello (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Othello (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1806" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./P.O.W. - Prisoners of War (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>P.O.W. - Prisoners of War</name>
		<desc>THE ENEMY IS UNSTOPPABLE. THEY MAINTAIN VIGILANT GUARD OVER THEIR FRONT LINES! THE ONLY WAY TO DEFEAT THEM IS TO GET BEHIND THEIR LINES. BUT HOW? BY ALLOWING A SOLDIER TO GET CAPTURED, PERHAPS HE COULD ESCAPE AND SINGLE-HANDEDLY DEFEAT THE ENEMY FORCES IN HIS WAY. 

IN P.O.W., THE PLAYER IS A SOLDIER WHO HAS BEEN IMPRISONED IN A PRISONER OF WAR CAMP AND MUST ESCAPE. IN ORDER TO ACCOMPLISH THIS, HE MUST DEFEAT A VARIETY OF ENEMIES.  THE FOES WILL ATTACK YOU HAND-TO-HAND, WITH KNIVES, GUNS, AND FROM HELICOPTERS. BOSS ENEMIES WILL GUARD THE END OF EACH LEVEL.

TO FIGHT BACK, YOU CAN USE HAND-TO-HAND, AND PICK UP WEAPON POWER-UPS, FOUND ON THE GROUND, IN ROOMS, OR DROPPED BY ENEMIES. THESE WEAPONS INCLUDE A KNIFE, WHICH CAN BE USED TO STAB OR BE THROWN, GUNS AND GRENADES.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19890901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>76269591</hash>
		<image>./images/P.O.W. - Prisoners of War (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/P.O.W. - Prisoners of War (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/P.O.W. - Prisoners of War (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/P.O.W. - Prisoners of War (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="99384" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pac-Man (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Man</name>
		<desc>THE PLAYER CONTROLS PAC-MAN THROUGH A MAZE, EATING PAC-DOTS. WHEN ALL PAC-DOTS ARE EATEN, PAC-MAN IS TAKEN TO THE NEXT STAGE. BETWEEN SOME STAGES ONE OF THREE INTERMISSION ANIMATIONS PLAYS. FOUR ENEMIES (BLINKY, PINKY, INKY AND CLYDE) ROAM THE MAZE, TRYING TO CATCH PAC-MAN. IF AN ENEMY TOUCHES PAC-MAN, HE LOSES A LIFE. WHENEVER PAC-MAN OCCUPIES THE SAME TILE AS AN ENEMY, HE IS CONSIDERED TO HAVE COLLIDED WITH THAT GHOST. WHEN ALL LIVES HAVE BEEN LOST, THE GAME ENDS. 

NEAR THE CORNERS OF THE MAZE ARE FOUR LARGER, FLASHING DOTS KNOWN AS POWER PELLETS THAT PROVIDE PAC-MAN WITH THE TEMPORARY ABILITY TO EAT THE ENEMIES. THE ENEMIES TURN DEEP BLUE, REVERSE DIRECTION AND USUALLY MOVE MORE SLOWLY. WHEN AN ENEMY IS EATEN, ITS EYES REMAIN AND RETURN TO THE CENTER BOX WHERE IT IS REGENERATED IN ITS NORMAL COLOR. BLUE ENEMIES FLASH WHITE TO SIGNAL THAT THEY ARE ABOUT TO BECOME DANGEROUS AGAIN AND THE LENGTH OF TIME FOR WHICH THE ENEMIES REMAIN VULNERABLE VARIES FROM ONE STAGE TO THE NEXT, GENERALLY BECOMING SHORTER AS THE GAME PROGRESSES. IN LATER STAGES, THE ENEMIES GO STRAIGHT TO FLASHING, BYPASSING BLUE, WHICH MEANS THAT THEY CAN ONLY BE EATEN FOR A SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME, ALTHOUGH THEY STILL REVERSE DIRECTION WHEN A POWER PELLET IS EATEN; IN EVEN LATER STAGES, THE GHOSTS DO NOT BECOME EDIBLE (I.E., THEY DO NOT CHANGE COLOR AND STILL MAKE PAC-MAN LOSE A LIFE ON CONTACT), BUT THEY STILL REVERSE DIRECTION.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>2E99A945</hash>
		<image>./images/Pac-Man (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Pac-Man (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Pac-Man (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pac-Man (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18838" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pipe Dream (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Pipe Dream</name>
		<desc>EACH LEVEL OF THIS ABSTRACT PUZZLER CHALLENGES THE PLAYER TO SET UP A NETWORK OF PIPES TO ALLOW AN UNSPECIFIED SUBSTANCE KNOWN AS 'FLOOZ' TO FLOW THROUGH AS MANY OF THOSE AS POSSIBLE. THE PIECES ARE OFFERED IN RANDOM ORDER, AND THERE ARE SEVEN DIFFERENT TYPES - STRAIGHT LINES GOING HORIZONTALLY OR VERTICALLY, CORNERS ROTATING IN EACH OF THE FOUR DIRECTIONS, AND CROSS-OVER PIECES WHICH CARRY THE FLOOZ STRAIGHT ACROSS HORIZONTALLY AND VERTICALLY. EACH OF THESE CAN BE ENTERED FROM EITHER SIDE. WHEN THE FLOOZ HITS A GAP, OR A PIECE WHICH THE PREVIOUS PIECE CAN'T FLOW INTO, THE PIPE IS FINISHED.

BEFORE THE FLOOZ STARTS FLOWING FROM ITS RANDOMLY-SELECTED STARTING POSITION, THE PLAYER HAS SEVERAL SECONDS TO START PLACING PIECES. THEY CAN BE PUT DOWN ANYWHERE. HOWEVER A SITUATION THAT CAN OFTEN OCCUR IS THERE WILL BE A LONG AND COMPLEX PIPING ARRANGEMENT SET UP, YET A GAP SOMEWHERE REMAINS TO BE FILLED. PLAYERS ARE ABLE TO  REPLACE A PIECE WITH ANOTHER IN THE SAME SQUARE (TO MAKE IT EASIER TO FLOW THE FLOOZ THAT WAY), BUT FOR A SLIGHT SCORING PENALTY.

BONUSES ARE AWARDED FOR LOOPING THE FLOOZ THROUGH BOTH SIDES OF AT LEAST 5 CROSS-OVER PIECES, OR PASSING THE FLOOZ THROUGH EVERY SQUARE ON THE SCREEN. LATER LEVELS HAVE SOME SQUARES ON THE GRID BLOCKED OFF, A FEW GAPS IN THE SIDE-WALL (ALLOWING FLOOZ TO THREAD TO THE OTHER SIDE OF THE SCREEN). AFTER EVERY FOUR LEVELS THERE IS A BONUS GAME FOR POINTS, IN WHICH THE PLAYER CAN ONLY PLACE THE PIECES IN THE LOWEST OPEN SPACE IN EACH COLUMN, SIMILARLY TO THE BOARD GAME OF "CONNECT 4".</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Assembly Line, The</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.|LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F3CC626D</hash>
		<image>./images/Pipe Dream (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Pipe Dream (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Pipe Dream (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pipe Dream (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1817" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pooyan (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Pooyan</name>
		<desc>IN THIS REMAKE OF THE ARCADE GAME POOYAN FROM THE EARLY '80S, YOU PLAY THE ROLE OF A PIG, PROTECTING ITS PIGLETS FROM WOLVES.  

THE FIRST SCREEN TAKES PLACE NEAR THE PIGS' HOME.  MRS. PIG RIDES UP AND DOWN IN A CABLE CAR, SHOOTING AT WOLVES, WHO ARE RIDING BALLOONS DOWNWARD, TOWARDS THE GROUND.  IF THE WOLVES LAND SAFELY ON THE GROUND, THEN THEY CAN CLIMB A LADDER, NEAR THE CABLE-CAR, AND CATCH MRS. PIG.  BUT IF SHE SHOOTS THEIR BALLOONS, THEY SPLAT ON THE GROUND INSTEAD.

THE WOLVES SHOOT ACORNS AT THE PIG.  BUT MRS. PIG HAS A FOOD BASED WEAPON TOO.  IF SHE GETS TO THE TOP, SHE CAN GET MEAT, TO TOSS AT THE WOLVES AND MAKE THEM JUMP OFF THEIR BALLOONS IN PURSUIT.  EACH WOLF TAKEN OUT THIS WAY IS WORTH BONUS POINTS (ON A DOUBLING SCHEME: 400, 800 1600...)

THE SECOND SCENE TAKES PLACE AT THE WOLVES LAIR.  HERE THE WOLVES HAVE REINFORCED BALLOONS--IT TAKES MULTIPLE HITS TO MAKE THEM FALL.  HERE THEY FLOAT UPWARDS TOWARD A BIG ROCK, WHICH THEY PUSH ON TOP OF MRS. PIG, WHEN SEVEN WOLVES ARE PRESENT.  ADDITIONALLY, AN ALPHA WOLF (WOLF LEADER) APPEARS AND SUMMONS WOLVES IN PACKS.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>0F449178</hash>
		<image>./images/Pooyan (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Pooyan (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Pooyan (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pooyan (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1670" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Power Blade 2 (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Power Blade 2</name>
		<desc>CHRISTMAS EVE, 2200.

THE DELTA FOUNDATION HAS JUST FINISHED THE DEVELOPMENT OF A CYBORG UNIT WHICH REPRESENTS A NEW GENERATION OF FIGHTING ROBOTS. THEY WANT TO SELL IT TO THE GOVERNMENT'S DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE AS IT WOULD POSE A THREAT TO THE SECURITY OF THE NATION IF IT IS SOLD TO A FOREIGN COUNTRY. THEY HAVE ASKED THE PRESIDENT, WHO IS ACTUALLY AN ALIEN FROM OUTER SPACE, TO CONSIDER THEIR OFFER AND RESPOND IN ONE WEEK. THE GOVERNMENT TAKES THIS MATTER VERY SERIOUSLY, AND ASSIGNS NOVA TO DESTROY THE DELTA FOUNDATION. UNFORTUNATELY, THE GOVERNMENT CANNOT BE INVOLVED IN THE EVENT THAT SOMETHING MIGHT HAPPEN TO HIM.

POWER BLADE 2 HAS SIX STAGES WHICH INVOLVES YOU RUNNING THROUGH THE LEVEL, WHILE KILLING OFF ENEMIES AND AVOIDING HAZARDS. AT THE START, YOU CAN CHOOSE WHICH STAGE TO START AT, BUT UNLIKE POWER BLADE, ONCE YOU HAVE CHOSEN A STAGE, YOU CAN'T EXIT AND CHOOSE ANOTHER ONE UNTIL YOU HAVE COMPLETED THE CURRENT ONE FIRST. NEARLY EACH STAGE INVOLVES YOU USING YOUR WITS, AS YOU DODGE SPIKES, JUMPING TOWARDS THE TOP OF THE SCREEN TO AVOID FIRE, AND GETTING FANS TO LIFT YOU ONTO PLATFORMS. YOU CAN ALSO SLIDE YOUR WAY THROUGH TIGHT SPOTS, AS LONG AS YOU SLIDE IN THE RIGHT PLACE.

AT THE END OF EACH STAGE, YOU FIGHT A DIFFERENT BOSS. HOWEVER, IN THE END, YOU MUST FIGHT ALL THE BOSSES YOU FOUGHT BEFORE BEFORE YOU GET TO FIGHT THE ALIEN LEADER.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19921002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B3DF7B65</hash>
		<image>./images/Power Blade 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Power Blade 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Power Blade 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Power Blade 2 (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="140547" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Power Blazer (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Power Blazer</name>
		<desc>POWER BLAZER IS AN ACTION/PLATFORM GAME BY TAITO. IN THE 21ST CENTURY, THE WHOLE WORLD IS HANDLED BY A SUPER-COMPUTER CALLED THE BRAIN MASTER. BUT ONE DAY, ALL SYSTEMS START TO INEXPLICABLY SHUT DOWN AT ONCE. HUMANS HAVE TO ACCEPT THE EVIDENCE, BRAIN MASTER HAS TAKEN OVER THE ONCE GLADDENED EARTH AND PLUNGED IT INTO CHAOS. THE PLAYER TAKES CONTROL OF STEVE TREIBER, A HIGHLY TRAINED SOLDIER ON A LONE MISSION BEHIND ENEMY LINES. HE IS THE ONLY ONE CAPABLE OF TAKING BRAIN MASTER OFFLINE AND TO SAVE THE WORLD. OUR YOUNG HERO IS ARMED WITH A POWERFUL COMBAT-BOOMERANG CALLED THE 'POWER BLAZER'. STAGES ARE FAIRLY LARGE AND MOST OF THEM HAVE DIFFERENT ROUTES TO THE FINISH LINE.
THE AMERICAN (AND EUROPEAN) VERSION OF THE GAME, CALLED POWER BLADE, IS SIGNIFICANTLY DIFFERENT THAN THE JAPANESE VERSION.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>EB13A2AE</hash>
		<image>./images/Power Blazer (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Power Blazer (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Power Blazer (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Power Blazer (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1497" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Predator (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Predator</name>
		<desc>PREDATOR: SOON THE HUNT WILL BEGIN IS AN 2D ACTION GAME. THERE ARE 30 STAGES IN THE GAME, AND EACH ONE IS SPLIT UP INTO TWO MODES: JUNGLE MODE, AND BIG MODE. IN JUNGLE MODE, THE OBJECT OF THE GAME IS TO SURVIVE THE DANGERS OF THE JUNGLE WHILE YOU SHOOT DO</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19890402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FF66C761</hash>
		<image>./images/Predator (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Predator (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Predator (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Predator (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1671" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Q-bert (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Q*bert</name>
		<desc>Q*BERT IS A CONVERSION OF THE POPULAR ARCADE GAME. THE GOAL IS TO CHANGE ALL OF THE TILES ON A PYRAMID TO THE TARGET COLOR. TO DO THIS YOU GUIDE Q*BERT AROUND THE PYRAMID, AND EVERY TILE HE HOPS ON WILL CHANGE COLOR. ON EARLY LEVELS, A SINGLE HOP WILL CHANGE THE TILE TO THE DESIRED COLOR, BUT ON LATER LEVELS YOU MAY NEED TO HOP ON A TILE MULTIPLE TIMES OR EVEN AVOID HOPPING ON A TILE MULTIPLE TIMES! TRYING TO STOP Q*BERT ARE MANY DIFFERENT CREATURES WHICH WANDER AROUND THE BOARD, INCLUDING COILY THE SNAKE, SLICK AND SAM, AND FALLING BALLS. ON THE EDGE OF THE BOARD ARE FLOATING DISCS; IF Q*BERT JUMPS ON ONE OF THESE DISCS WHEN THE SNAKE IS IN PURSUIT, THE SNAKE WILL FALL OFF  THE BOARD WHILE Q*BERT IS SAFELY TRANSPORTED TO THE TOP.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultra Software Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>D. Gottlieb &amp; Co.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./images/Q-bert (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Q-bert (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Q-bert (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Q-bert (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1329" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./River City Ransom (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>River City Ransom</name>
		<desc>THE EVIL SLICK HAS KIDNAPPED RYAN'S GIRLFRIEND AND TAKEN OVER THE HIGH SCHOOL. THE PLAYER IS CAST AS EITHER RYAN OR ALEX (SECOND PLAYER) AND HAS TO FIGHT HIS WAY THROUGH RIVER CITY'S MERCILESS GANGS BEFORE CONFRONTING SLICK AND FREEING HIS GIRL. 

RIVER CITY RANSOM IS A SIDE-SCROLLING BEAT-EM-UP SIMILAR TO DOUBLE DRAGON. THE PLAYER, OR PLAYERS, TRAVEL THROUGH THE LOCATIONS OF RIVER CITY, ENCOUNTERING VARIOUS GANGS ALONG THE WAY. GANG MEMBERS CAN BE DEFEATED WITH PUNCHES AND KICKS, OR BEATEN UP WITH OBJECTS SCATTERED AROUND. UPON THEIR DEFEAT, GANG MEMBERS DROP MONEY WHICH ALEX AND RYAN CAN SPEND IN MALLS TO BUY ITEMS THAT RESTORE HEALTH AND IMPROVE THEIR COMBAT ABILITIES. THE MAIN CHARACTERS HAVE RPG-LIKE NUMERICAL STATS THAT CAN BE IMPROVED THIS WAY, AND CAN ALSO BUY BOOKS TO LEARN COMBAT MANOEUVRES. TO FINISH THE GAME, THE PLAYER(S) HAVE TO FIND AND DEFEAT ALL THE BOSSES.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>BFFC541E</hash>
		<image>./images/River City Ransom (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/River City Ransom (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/River City Ransom (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/River City Ransom (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1718" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Road Fighter (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Road Fighter</name>
		<desc>ENTER INTO THE FIERY HEAT OF COMPETITION, AS YOU HEAD FOR THE GLORY AWAITING YOU AT THE FINISH LINE ! YOU'LL NEED ALL YOUR WITS ABOUT YOU AS ENGAGE IN THIS FAST-PACED ROAD FIGHT.

YOU DRIVE A RACING MACHINE AT SPEEDS OF 400 KM/H. AS YOU START, THE SOUND OF YOUR ENGINE ROARS THROUGH THE QUIET RESIDENTIAL AREA. YOU HAVE ENTERED THE TOUGH WORLD OF RACING. IT'S A HECTIC RALLY AS YOUR RIVAL ATTEMPTS TO BLOCK YOUR WAY TO VICTORY. IT IS A RACE OF LIMITED TIME AND FUEL. YOU'LL ENCOUNTER OIL SLICKS ON THE ROAD AND BIG TRACTOR-TRAILERS BLOCKING YOUR PATH. ONLY YOUR DRIVING SKILL CAN GET YOU BY THESE OBSTACLES. IF YOU GO INTO A SPIN, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY CUT THE STEERING WHEEL IN THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION. GETTING A BONUS CAR ALONG THE WAY REPLENISHES YOUR FUEL SUPPLY. GOOD LUCK IN YOUR RACE ACROSS THE BRIDGE, ALONG THE COASTAL HIGHWAY, AND AROUND THE STEEP AND NARROW MOUNTAIN COURSE!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850711T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D27BA35B</hash>
		<image>./images/Road Fighter (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Road Fighter (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Road Fighter (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Road Fighter (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1325" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./RoboCop (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>RoboCop</name>
		<desc>PATROLMAN ALEX MURPHY WAS KILLED ON THE STREETS OF DETROIT. THE MAJOR CORPORATION THERE, OMNI CONSUMER PRODUCTS (OCP) SAW AN OPPORTUNITY TO SELL A NEW KIND OF LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICER TO THE TROUBLED CITY. THEY TOOK WHAT WAS LEFT OF MURPHY, ENCASED IT IN TITANIUM ARMOR, WIPED HIS MEMORY AND CREATED ROBOCOP. NOW IT'S UP TO ROBOCOP TO CLEAN THE STREETS OF DETROIT AND ELIMINATE THE ONE RESPONSIBLE FOR HIS MURDER, CLARENCE BODDICKER. BUT IT LOOKS LIKE CLARENCE MIGHT NOT BE THE KINGPIN OF THIS TOWN...

BASED ON THE 1987 MOVIE OF THE SAME NAME, ROBOCOP ALLOWS THE PLAYER TO CONTROL ROBOCOP. THE MAJORITY OF THE GAME IS A SIDE SCROLLER. ROBOCOP CAN PUNCH UNARMED CITIZENS AND SHOOT ARMED CITIZENS. HE CAN MOVE LEFT, RIGHT AND DUCK BUT CAN NOT JUMP. DIFFERENT WEAPONS CAN BE PICKED UP FROM ENEMIES, AND POWER-UPS TO RESTORE HEALTH AND/OR ENERGY. FOLLOWING LEVELS, ROBOCOP WILL HAVE TO MATCH A CRIMINAL'S FACE TO THE PROPER MUGSHOT AND ENGAGE IN A FIRST-PERSON SHOOTING BONUS ROUND.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5C050228</hash>
		<image>./images/RoboCop (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/RoboCop (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/RoboCop (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/RoboCop (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1857" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rockin' Kats (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Rockin' Kats</name>
		<desc>WILLY IS A YOUNG JAZZ CAT WHO GOES BY THE NAME OF "THE ROCKIN' KAT". HIS GIRLFRIEND, JILL, WAS KIDNAPPED BY MUGSY, THE LOCAL CRIME BOSS.

IN THIS SIDE SCROLLING GAME, YOU MUST HELP ROCKIN' KAT WILLY TO SAVE HIS GIRLFRIEND THROUGH 7 STAGES. EACH STAGE IS A TV SHOW BROADCAST THROUGH DIFFERENT CHANNELS OF A TV SET, AND YOU MUST THUS CHOOSE WHICH CHANNEL YOU WANT TO PLAY. THROUGH THE CHANNELS WILLY IT WILL BE SENT TO DIFFERENT THEMED SHOWS SUCH AS WESTERN MOVIES, GANGSTER MOVIES, ETC, AS WELL AS SOME BONUS CHANNELS.

WILLY CAN WALK AND JUMP AROUND, AND CARRIES AS A WEAPON A SPRING-LOAD SUPER PUNCH GUN, WHICH HE CAN PUT IN DIVERSE USES:

1. KNOCK HIS ENEMIES: BY PRESSING A.
PERFORM HIGHER JUMPS: BY JUMPING (B) AND PRESSING DOWN + A.
SPIN ATTACK: BY GRABBING A LEDGE (A) AND ROTATING WITH THE D-PAD.
SPIN JUMP: BY GRABBING A LEDGE (A), ROTATING WITH THE D-PAD AND JUMPING (B).
CATCH AND TROW: BY HOLDING A, GRABBING AN OBJECT AND RELEASING A.

HE CAN ALSO BUY ATTACHMENTS THAT WILL MAKE HIS GUN MORE POWERFUL, SUCH AS THE BOMBER, THE TWIN BALLS, THE HAMMER PUNCH AND THE JET SNEAKERS. 

ROCKIN' KATS IS SO CARTOONISH THAT YOU MIGHT EXPECT TO SEE IT ON SATURDAY MORNING TV.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19910902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>10FC2003</hash>
		<image>./images/Rockin' Kats (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Rockin' Kats (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Rockin' Kats (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rockin' Kats (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1857" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Todos Contra (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Rockin' Kats</name>
		<desc>WILLY IS A YOUNG JAZZ CAT WHO GOES BY THE NAME OF "THE ROCKIN' KAT". HIS GIRLFRIEND, JILL, WAS KIDNAPPED BY MUGSY, THE LOCAL CRIME BOSS.

IN THIS SIDE SCROLLING GAME, YOU MUST HELP ROCKIN' KAT WILLY TO SAVE HIS GIRLFRIEND THROUGH 7 STAGES. EACH STAGE IS A TV SHOW BROADCAST THROUGH DIFFERENT CHANNELS OF A TV SET, AND YOU MUST THUS CHOOSE WHICH CHANNEL YOU WANT TO PLAY. THROUGH THE CHANNELS WILLY IT WILL BE SENT TO DIFFERENT THEMED SHOWS SUCH AS WESTERN MOVIES, GANGSTER MOVIES, ETC, AS WELL AS SOME BONUS CHANNELS.

WILLY CAN WALK AND JUMP AROUND, AND CARRIES AS A WEAPON A SPRING-LOAD SUPER PUNCH GUN, WHICH HE CAN PUT IN DIVERSE USES:

1. KNOCK HIS ENEMIES: BY PRESSING A.
PERFORM HIGHER JUMPS: BY JUMPING (B) AND PRESSING DOWN + A.
SPIN ATTACK: BY GRABBING A LEDGE (A) AND ROTATING WITH THE D-PAD.
SPIN JUMP: BY GRABBING A LEDGE (A), ROTATING WITH THE D-PAD AND JUMPING (B).
CATCH AND TROW: BY HOLDING A, GRABBING AN OBJECT AND RELEASING A.

HE CAN ALSO BUY ATTACHMENTS THAT WILL MAKE HIS GUN MORE POWERFUL, SUCH AS THE BOMBER, THE TWIN BALLS, THE HAMMER PUNCH AND THE JET SNEAKERS. 

ROCKIN' KATS IS SO CARTOONISH THAT YOU MIGHT EXPECT TO SEE IT ON SATURDAY MORNING TV.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19910902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>81A7AD12</hash>
		<image>./images/Todos Contra (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Todos Contra (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Todos Contra (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Todos Contra (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1793" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rollergames (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Rollergames</name>
		<desc>THIS IS A PLATFORM GAME IN THE SAME FASHION AS TURTLES II, THAT IS THAT IT'S A SIDESCROLLER WERE YOU CAN MOVE UP AND DOWN ON THE SCREEN, BUT YOU GO ON ROLLERSKATES. THIS MAKES THE GAME GO MUCH FASTER THAN ITS COUNTERPART, WHICH ADDS DIFFICULTY AND ALSO A SENSE OF SPEED.

IT INCLUDES A SILLY STORY ABOUT THREE DIFFERENT ROLLER SKATES GANGS (SOMEWHAT LIKE MOTOR CYCLE GANGS) IN A CLOSE FUTURE, WHICH IS MOST AN EXCUSE FOR THE GAME TO EXIST.

YOU CAN CHOOSE BETWEEN THREE DIFFERENT GANGS, ONE IS ALL-AROUND, ONE IS FAST AND WEAK (AND CONSISTS OF WOMEN) AND ONE IS SLOW AND STRONG, YOU GET THE FASHION. THIS ADDS SOME REPLAYABILITY, BUT IN REALITY, THEY ARE KIND OF THE SAME.

THE GAME ALSO SUFFERS FROM TRIAL AND ERROR; YOU MUST LEARN THE COURSES IF YOU WANT TO MASTER THEM. LUCKILY, THE GAME HAS UNLIMITED CONTINUES.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>6767594C</hash>
		<image>./images/Rollergames (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Rollergames (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Rollergames (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rollergames (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1629" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rolling Thunder (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Rolling Thunder</name>
		<desc>ROLLING THUNDER IS THE WORLDS MOST POWERFUL SECRET POLICE FORCE AND YOU ARE ITS BEST AGENT. YOUR MISSION IS TO STOP AN UNDERGROUND CONSPIRACY TO CONQUER THE WORLD AND TO SAVE AGENT LEILA, WHO HAS BEEN CAPTURED. STARTING OUT ARMED ONLY WITH A HANDGUN, YOU HAVE TO MAKE YOUR WAY THROUGH HEAVILY GUARDED HALLWAYS AND SECRET PASSAGES TO FIND LEILA AND STOP THE ENEMY. ROLLING THUNDER FEATURES SIDE SCROLLING ACTION BASED ON THE ARCADE GAME.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tengen</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>947D3916</hash>
		<image>./images/Rolling Thunder (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Rolling Thunder (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Rolling Thunder (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rolling Thunder (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SCAT -Special cibernetic attack team -Port (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>SCAT -Special cibernetic attack team -Port</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/SCAT -Special cibernetic attack team -Port (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/SCAT -Special cibernetic attack team -Port (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/SCAT -Special cibernetic attack team -Port (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/SCAT -Special cibernetic attack team -Port (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1302" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Shadow of the Ninja (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Shadow of the Ninja</name>
		<desc>IN THE 21ST CENTURY, THE EVIL EMPEROR GARUDA HAS TAKEN OVER THE CITY OF NEW YORK, KILLING MANY OF ITS INHABITANTS. YOU PLAY AS EITHER HAYATE OR KAEDE, TWO NINJAS WHO ARE ATTEMPTING TO FREE THE CITY FROM GARUDA'S CONTROL.

SHADOW OF THE NINJA IS A TYPICAL SIDE-SCROLLING ACTION GAME, CONSISTING OF RUNNING, SLASHING AND JUMPING THROUGH 5 LEVELS, EACH WITH 4 SUB-STAGES WITH NUMEROUS AND VARIED FOES, AND A BOSS ENEMY AT THEIR END.

KAEDE AND HAYATE CAN NOT ONLY JUMP; AS NINJAS, THEY CAN HANG FROM PLATFORMS AND MAKE SWIFT SALTOMORTALS BETWEEN FLOORS. SOMETIMES, CANISTERS CONTAINING POWERUPS CAN BE FOUND. TYPICAL POWERUPS EXTEND RANGE OF THE DEFAULT SWORD, OR THEY MAY BE ADDITIONAL WEAPONS SUCH AS THROWING STARS AND A NINJA WEAPON THAT LOOKS LIKE A BIG GRAPPLING HOOK ON A STRING.

THE GAME ALLOWED TWO PLAYERS TO PLAY COOPERATIVELY, A RARE FEATURE FOR ACTION GAMES OUTSIDE OF THE CONTRA SERIES.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>984610E4</hash>
		<image>./images/Shadow of the Ninja (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Shadow of the Ninja (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Shadow of the Ninja (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Shadow of the Ninja (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1546" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Silver Surfer (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Silver Surfer</name>
		<desc>THE SILVER SURFER ROAMS THROUGHOUT SPACE AS HERALD TO GALACTUS, LOOKING FOR NEW PLANETS FOR HIM TO FEED ON. HOWEVER HIS MISSION IS INTERRUPTED BY A SUMMON FROM GALACTUS. SILVER SURFER LEARNS THAT CREATURES FROM THE MAGICK DIMENSION ARE TRYING TO BREAK THROUGH INTO THE UNIVERSE AND THEIR COMING WILL END ALL LIFE. VOWING TO STOP THEM, SILVER SURFER MUST ASSEMBLE THE PIECES OF A MYSTERIOUS COSMIC DEVICE AND USE IT TO PUSH THEM BACK. THE PIECES OF THE DEVICE ARE CURRENTLY IN THE HANDS OF SOME MALICIOUS CREATURES: REPTYL, MEPHISTO, SKRULL EMPEROR, POSSESSOR AND FIRELORD. SILVER SURFER MUST TRAVEL TO THEIR DOMAINS AND DEFEAT THEM IN ORDER TO OBTAIN PIECES OF THE DEVICE.

SILVER SURFER IS A SHOOTER GAME, WITH SOME LEVELS TAKING PLACE VERTICALLY AND SOME HORIZONTALLY. THE SURFER'S ONLY ABILITY IS TO MOVE AROUND ON THE SCREEN AND TO SHOOT DIRECTLY IN FRONT OF HIM. POWER-UPS THAT CAN BE PICKED UP INCLUDE: THE LETTER "F" (FIREPOWER) WHICH WILL INCREASE THE NUMBER AND POWER OF HIS PROJECTILES, SMART BOMBS WHICH DESTROY EVERYTHING ON THE SCREEN, THE LETTER "S" (SPEEDUP) WHICH INCREASES THE SURFER'S MOVEMENT AND ORBS WHICH WILL ALSO FIRE THE SURFER'S WEAPON. ORBS ARE SPECIAL IN THAT TWO CAN BE OBTAINED (ONLY 1 IS SHOWN ON HORIZONTAL SCROLLING LEVELS) AND THEY CAN BE POSITIONED TO FIRE FORWARDS, BACKWARDS OR SIDEWAYS.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19901102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arcadia Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Software Creations</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>47C6DFFC</hash>
		<image>./images/Silver Surfer (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Silver Surfer (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Silver Surfer (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Silver Surfer (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1440" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Soccer (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Soccer</name>
		<desc>SOCCER IS AN ACTION GAME FOR TWO PLAYERS OR ONE PLAYER AGAINST THE COMPUTER. YOU CAN PLAY THE GAME IN ONE OF FIVE SKILL LEVELS, CHOOSE FROM SEVERAL DIFFERENT TEAMS, AND SELECT THE AMOUNT OF TIME THE MATCH WILL TAKE. SOCCER FEATURES THROW-INS, GOAL KICKS, CORNER KICKS, PENALTY KICKS AND AN OVERHEAD VIEW OF THE FIELD WHICH SCROLLS TO FOLLOW THE ACTION.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4E2032D2</hash>
		<image>./images/Soccer (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Soccer (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Soccer (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Soccer (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1494" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spelunker (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Spelunker</name>
		<desc>IN THIS GAME, YOU ARE A SPELUNKER WHO CLIMBS DEEP DOWN MOUNTAIN CAVES IN SEARCH FOR TREASURE. THE LEVELS CONSIST OF MANY PLATFORMS, CONNECTED TO EACH OTHER BY A RIDING CART, LADDERS, ROPES, ETC. YOU'LL HAVE TO TIME YOUR JUMPING WELL, BECAUSE A SLIGHT FALL WILL LEAD TO YOUR DEATH, AND THE ABYSS IS NEAR! YOU SHOULD JUMP OVER VARIOUS OBSTACLES, AVOID GHOST-LIKE ENEMIES, CLIMB ON ROPES, AND USE INVENTORY ITEMS SUCH AS BOMBS TO CREATE LITTLE EXPLOSIONS THAT WILL BRING YOU NEARER TO THE DESIRED TREASURE.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19870901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micro Graphic Image</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3478DAAE</hash>
		<image>./images/Spelunker (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Spelunker (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Spelunker (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Spelunker (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18871" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Voyager (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Star Voyager</name>
		<desc>COSMOSTATION NOAH, LOCATED IN SPIRAL GALAXY IX, IS UNDER SIEGE BY MOLOK WARDRIVERS. NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE PILOT OF THE RH119 TO FEND OFF THE MOLOK WARDRIVERS AND SAVE THE COSMOSTATION.

STAR VOYAGER'S GAMEPLAY REQUIRES THE PLAYER TO VENTURE THROUGH VARIOUS SECTORS OF THE GALAXY IN SEARCH OF DIFFERENT ALIEN FLEETS SO THEY CAN BE DEFEATED. FUEL STATIONS ARE PLACED AROUND SPORADICALLY AND HELP IF FUEL IS RUNNING LOW. THERE ARE SEVERAL DIFFERENT PLANETS THAT ARE EITHER EMPTY OR HAVE PEOPLE THAT CAN UPGRADE THE PLAYER'S EQUIPMENT TO FIGHT OFF THE ENEMY FLEETS. THESE UPGRADES INCLUDE THE SUPER LASER, IMPROVED SHIELDS, AND ENGINES THAT ENHANCE THE SHIP'S WARPING ABILITY. WARPING IS A VITAL PART OF THE GAMEPLAY. IF PLAYERS DO NOT WARP TO DIFFERENT SECTORS WISELY, THEY MIGHT END UP LOST, RUN INTO DANGEROUS SECTORS SUCH AS THE BLACK HOLE OR THE ASTEROID FIELD, OR RUN OUT OF FUEL. THE GAME ENDS IF ENEMY SHIPS DESTROY THE COSMOSTATION NOAH.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19870901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DD0FC751</hash>
		<image>./images/Star Voyager (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Star Voyager (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Star Voyager (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Star Voyager (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1330" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Street Fighter 2010 - The Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter 2010 : The Final Fight</name>
		<desc>THE PLAYER IS KEN, THE HERO OF THE STREET FIGHTER SERIES. IT'S BEEN 25 YEARS SINCE HE LAST PARTICIPATED IN A FIGHTING TOURNAMENT. HE HAS BECOME A SCIENTIST AND HAS DEVELOPED A POWERFUL MEDICINE TOGETHER WITH HIS FRIEND TROY. BUT AN UNKNOWN FIEND BREAKS INTO HIS LABORATORY, KILLS TROY, AND STEALS THE INVENTION. IT'S TIME TO RECALL THE GOOD OLD DAYS AND TO EMBARK ON A QUEST FOR REVENGE!

DESPITE THE US TITLE, THE GAME HAS LITTLE TO DO WITH THE STREET FIGHTER OR THE FINAL FIGHT GAMES. THIS IS AN ACTION PLATFORMER IN WHICH THE PLAYER NAVIGATES KEN AROUND, TRYING TO AVOID OR KILL THE ENEMIES BY SHOOTING AT THEM WITH RANGED WEAPONS, ADJUSTING THE DIRECTION OF THE SHOT, OR KICKING AND PUNCHING THEM. KEN IS VERY AGILE AND CAN JUMP HIGH AND CLIMB WALLS.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C7B1AEB1</hash>
		<image>./images/Street Fighter 2010 - The Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Street Fighter 2010 - The Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Street Fighter 2010 - The Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Street Fighter 2010 - The Final Fight (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1515" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Strider (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Strider</name>
		<desc>THE STRIDERS ARE A GLOBAL ORGANIZATION OF INFILTRATION SPECIALISTS WHO WORK TO COMBAT VILLAINY AND KEEP THE WORLD SAFE. FROM THEIR ORBITAL SPACE STATION, THE BLUE DRAGON, THEY ARE ABLE TO QUICKLY REACH ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.

HIRYU IS ONE OF THE TOP STRIDERS. HE IS GIVEN THE TASK BY VICE-DIRECTOR MATIC, OF FINDING ANOTHER CAPTURED STRIDER, KAIN. BUT RATHER THAN MOUNT A RESCUE, HIRYU IS TOLD HIS ASSIGNMENT IS TO KILL KAIN. HIRYU QUESTIONS THESE ORDERS AND TRAVELS TO KAIN'S LAST KNOWN LOCATION TO TRY TO FIND HIM...

STRIDER IS A PLATFORM GAME WHERE HIRYU MUST FIGHT HIS WAY PAST ENEMIES AND UNCOVER KEYS, CHARACTERS AND DATA DISKS (WHICH CAN BE ANALYSED ABOARD THE BLUE DRAGON) TO FIND OUT WHAT'S GOING ON. HIS PRIMARY WEAPON IS HIS JUMPING ABILITY AND SWORD, THE CYPHER, WHICH HE USES TO STRIKE WITH GREAT SPEED. AT SOME POINT IN THE GAME, THE CYPHER MAY BE MODIFIED TO SHOOT PLASMA ARROWS. HIRYU ALSO HAS A VARIOUS SET OF "SKILLS" WHICH HE LEARNS AS HE GAINS LEVELS. EXAMPLES OF SKILLS ARE A HEALING ABILITY (MEDICAL), A JUMPING ABILITY (JUMP), SOME ADDITIONAL ATTACKS (SPARK, FIRE, SP-BALL) AND THE ABILITY TO LEAVE AN AREA (WARP).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7E98D751</hash>
		<image>./images/Strider (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Strider (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Strider (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Strider (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="18877" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Arabian (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Super Arabian</name>
		<desc>THE OBJECT OF SUPER ARABIAN IS TO COLLECT ALL THE POTS ON THE SCREEN, WHILE AVOIDING PESTS LIKE BIRDS AND WORMS WHO WILL BLOCK YOUR WAY AND EVENTUALLY DESTROY YOU. IF THEY DO THIS, YOU CAN KICK THEIR ARABIAN BUTT AND KNOCK THEM OFF THE SCREEN. IF YOU MANAGE TO KICK TWO OR MORE ENEMIES AT ONCE, SOMETHING WILL HIT YOU THAT WILL MAKE YOU INVINCIBLE FOR A FEW SECONDS.

IT DOESN'T MATTER ABOUT THE ORDER IN WHICH YOU COLLECT THE POTS. HOWEVER, EACH POT HAS A DIFFERENT LETTER ON IT, AND IF YOU COLLECT THE POTS IN THE ORDER THAT THEY APPEAR AT THE TOP-RIGHT OF THE SCREEN, YOU WILL RECEIVE A WHOPPING 5000 POINTS. AFTER YOU COLLECT THE POTS, YOU MOVE ON TO THE NEXT LEVEL.  THERE ARE FOUR LEVELS IN EACH PART (SECTION), AND EACH PART HAS A THEME TO THEM. IN PART 1, LEVEL 1, FOR INSTANCE, YOU HAVE TO COLLECT THE LETTERS THAT MAKE UP THE WORD ANIMAL. IN SUBSEQUENT LEVELS, YOU HAVE TO CREATE WORDS THAT ARE ACTUAL ANIMALS (HORSE, RABBIT, MONKEY). ALSO, IF YOU TAKE TOO LONG TO COMPLETE THE LEVEL, A RED GENIE WILL EMERGE FROM ONE OF THE POTS AND WILL ATTACK YOU.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19850725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sun Electronics Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>171FD6E9</hash>
		<image>./images/Super Arabian (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Super Arabian (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Super Arabian (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Arabian (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Contra-Port (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Super Contra-Port</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Super Contra-Port (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Super Contra-Port (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Super Contra-Port (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Contra-Port (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1248" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. 2 (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 2</name>
		<desc>ONE NIGHT MARIO HAS A STRANGE DREAM, WHERE HE OPENS A DOOR TO ANOTHER WORLD FILLED WITH EVEN STRANGER CREATURES AND LANDS THEN THOSE IN HIS LAST ADVENTURE AGAINST BOWSER. AMAZINGLY, THE NEXT DAY, MARIO, LUIGI, TOAD, AND THE PRINCESS STUMBLE UPON A CAVE, WHICH LEADS TO THE WORLD THAT WAS IN MARIO'S DREAM.

SUBCON, THE LAND OF DREAMS, IS UNDER AN EVIL SPELL THANKS TO WART, SO MARIO AND THE GANG MUST SAVE THE DAY. NEW CREATURES TO DEFEAT AND PLENTY OF NASTY SURPRISES AWAIT.

CHOOSE FROM THE FOUR CHARACTERS, EACH DIFFERING IN SPEED AND JUMPING ABILITY, AND HEAD ON THROUGH 7 LEVELS EACH FILLED WITH PUZZLES, BOSSES, BONUS MONEY, THE ALWAYS HELPFUL MUSHROOM, AND INVINCIBLE STAR, PLUS BOMBS AND MAGIC POTIONS. 
AFTER EACH LEVEL, DEPENDING ON THE COINS YOU COLLECT, YOU CAN USE THEM IN THE BONUS GAME TO COLLECT EXTRA LIVES.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19881028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1672B203</hash>
		<image>./images/Super Mario Bros. 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Super Mario Bros. 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Super Mario Bros. 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Mario Bros. 2 (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1246" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. 3 (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
		<desc>BOWSER IS BACK, AND ALONG WITH THE BOWSER KIDS, HE'S OUT TO SPOIL MARIO'S DAY ONCE AGAIN. 

THIS TIME, ALONG WITH NABBING THE PRINCESS, THE BOWSER CREW HAVE ALSO TAKEN THE MAGIC WANDS FROM THE KINGS OF EACH LAND AND TURNED THEM INTO CREATURES.
IT'S UP TO MARIO AND LUIGI TO GET BACK THE MAGIC WANDS, DEFEAT BOWSER, AND SAVE THE PRINCESS ALL BEFORE THE DAY IS DONE.

OLD AND NEW POWER-UPS ABOUND IN EACH LEVEL FOR THE MARIO BROTHERS, INCLUDING THE RETURN OF THE SUPER MUSHROOM AND FIRE FLOWER, PLUS THE NEW POWER-UPS INCLUDING THE FROG SUIT, THE WARP FLUTE, AND THE MOST IMPORTANT OF ALL, THE LEAF, WHICH ALLOWS THE PLAYER TO FLY AND ATTACK ENEMIES WITH YOUR TAIL.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>79E77B16</hash>
		<image>./images/Super Mario Bros. 3 (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Super Mario Bros. 3 (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Super Mario Bros. 3 (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Mario Bros. 3 (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1993" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sweet Home (J) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Sweet Home</name>
		<desc>"SWEET HOME" SEGUE AS FAÇANHAS DE CINCO MEMBROS DE UM GRUPO DE INVESTIGAÇÃO: KAZUO, AKIKO, TARO, ASUKA E EMI. O FAMOSO PINTOR MAMIYA ICHIROU VIVEU MUITOS ANOS EM UMA MANSÃO ISOLADA, E HÁ RUMORES DE QUE HÁ ALGUNS AFRESCOS VALIOSOS PARA ENCONTRAR LÁ DENTRO. NOSSOS INVESTIGADORES DECIDEM TIRAR ALGUMAS FOTOS DOS AFRESCOS. NO ENTANTO, AO ENTRAR NA MANSÃO, UMA FIGURA FANTASMAGÓRICA DE MAMIYA APARECE E AMEAÇA-OS. DEPOIS DISSO, ELES SE ENCONTRAM PRESOS NA MANSÃO. OS HERÓIS DEVEM AGORA ENCONTRAR UMA SAÍDA, SEM ESQUECER OS AFRESCOS PARA OS QUAIS VIERAM E O DESTINO DE UM GRUPO DE INVESTIGAÇÃO ANTERIOR QUE DESAPARECEU EM CIRCUNSTÂNCIAS MISTERIOSAS.

"SWEET HOME" É TALVEZ O PRIMEIRO EXEMPLO CONHECIDO DE GÊNERO SURVIVAL HORROR, CRIADO PELA MESMA EMPRESA QUE MAIS TARDE FEZ O FAMOSO RESIDENT EVIL. NO ENTANTO, "SWEET HOME" TAMBÉM É UM RPG ESTILO CONSOLE: PERSONAGENS LUTAM CONTRA MONSTROS ALEATÓRIOS EM BATALHAS POR TURNOS, EQUIPAM VÁRIAS ARMAS E SOBEM DE NÍVEL. VOCÊ PODE (E DEVE) FORMAR EQUIPES DIFERENTES DOS CINCO PERSONAGENS DISPONÍVEIS, TANTO PARA BATALHAS QUANTO PARA RESOLVER QUEBRA-CABEÇAS. CADA PERSONAGEM TEM SUA PRÓPRIA HABILIDADE BASEADA EM ITENS: TARO PODE TIRAR FOTOS, EMI PODE DESTRAVAR QUASE QUALQUER PORTA, KAZUO TEM UM ISQUEIRO, AKIKO USA UM ASPIRADOR PARA REMOVER POEIRA E OUTROS OBSTÁCULOS, E ASUKA TEM KITS MÉDICOS.

O JOGO NUNCA FOI LANÇADO FORA DO JAPÃO.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19891215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B78B5FB9</hash>
		<image>./images/Sweet Home (J) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sweet Home (J) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sweet Home (J) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sweet Home (J) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1464" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Trojan (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Tatakai no Banka</name>
		<desc>THE WORLD IS RULED BY A VICIOUS WARLORD NAMED ACHILESS AND HIS HENCHMEN. YOU ARE RYU, THE MASTER OF MARTIAL ARTS AND SWORD-FIGHTING, WHO HAS DECIDED THAT A CONFRONTATION WITH ACHILLES IS IN ORDER TO BRING PEACE AND ORDER BACK TO THE WORLD. YOUR CHARACTER IS EQUIPPED WITH BOTH A SWORD (FOR OFFENSE) AND A SHIELD (FOR DEFENSE). YOU WILL GO THROUGH SIX STAGES STARTING AT A RUINED CITY, EACH WITH TWO BOSS CHARACTERS (IN THE MIDDLE AND AT THE END). SOME ENEMIES ARE SO POWERFUL THAT YOU WILL DIE THE INSTANT YOU FAIL TO BLOCK. YOU ALSO HAVE TO RACE AGAINST TIME AS WELL, WHICH MAKES THE GAME THAT MUCH MORE DIFFICULT.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Romstar</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>63D055EE</hash>
		<image>./images/Trojan (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Trojan (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Trojan (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Trojan (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1253" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</name>
		<desc>WITH APRIL O'NEIL HELD HOSTAGE BY THE SHREDDER'S THUGS, BEBOP AND ROCKSTEADY, ONCE AGAIN, IT'S UP TO THE TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES TO COME TO HER RESCUE!  PLAY AS ALL FOUR OF THE TURTLE HEROES, RESCUE APRIL, AND THEN RESCUE YOUR SENSEI SPLINTER FROM MECHA-TURTLES CLUTCHES THAN GO AFTER THE SHREDDER DEEP IN THE BOWELS OF THE TECHNODROME ITSELF.

TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES IS AN ACTION GAME BASED ON THE LATE EIGHTIES/EARLY NINETIES CARTOON SERIES OF THE SAME NAME. PLAY AS LEONARDO, MICHAELANGELO, DONATELLO AND RAPHAEL (ONE TURTLE ONLY, BUT THE ABILITY TO SWAP BETWEEN TURTLES AT ANY TIME) AS YOU SAVE YOUR FRIENDS AND BATTLE THE SHREDDER AND HIS CRONIES. THERE ARE NO 'LIVES', AS SUCH - WHEN YOU LOSE A TURTLE, HE BECOMES 'CAPTURED', AND YOU CANNOT USE HIM AGAIN UNTIL YOU RESCUE HIM FROM A PLACE HIDDEN IN THE OVERWORLD.

GAMEPLAY TAKES PLACE IN TWO PERSPECTIVES: A TOP-DOWN VIEW, WHICH LETS YOU RUN AROUND AND EXPLORE BUILDINGS, SEWERS AND OTHER PLACES. WHEN ENTERING PLACES FROM THE TOP-DOWN VIEW, THE PERSPECTIVE SHIFTS TO A SIDE-SCROLLING VIEW, WHERE MOST OF THE BATTLING TAKES PLACE. IN ADDITION TO EACH TURTLE'S MAIN WEAPON, SUB-WEAPONS (SUCH AS SHURIKEN) CAN BE ACQUIRED, TO USE AT FOES - THESE HAVE A LIMITED USE.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19890602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2C1D98B2</hash>
		<image>./images/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18893" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Terminator 2 - Judgment Day (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Terminator 2: Judgment Day</name>
		<desc>TERMINATOR 2: JUDGMENT DAY IS BASED ON THE MOVIE OF THE SAME NAME. THE PLAYER TAKES THE ROLE OF THE T-800 TERMINATOR AND HAS TO PROTECT JOHN CONNOR FROM BEING TERMINATED BY THE T-1000 TERMINATOR. 

THE GAME IS SET OVER FIVE LEVELS WITH THE FOLLOWING GOALS:

1. LEVEL 1: ACQUIRE A WEAPON.
LEVEL 2: AN ISOMETRIC RACING COURSE ON A MOTORCYCLE IN WHICH THE PLAYER NEEDS TO OUT-RUN A TANKER TRUCK THAT IS CHASING THEM. THIS STAGE WAS OMITTED FROM THE GAME GEAR VERSION.
LEVEL 3: LOCATE AND RESCUE SARAH CONNOR FROM THE PESCADERO ASYLUM.
LEVEL 4: PLANT EXPLOSIVE CHARGES TO DESTROY THE CYBERDYNE BUILDING.
LEVEL 5: DEFEAT THE T-1000 WITHIN THE STEEL MILL.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>LJN, Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3AC3C2A2</hash>
		<image>./images/Terminator 2 - Judgment Day (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Terminator 2 - Judgment Day (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Terminator 2 - Judgment Day (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Terminator 2 - Judgment Day (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1291" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tetris (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc>THIS VERSION OF TETRIS IS ONE OF MANY CONVERSIONS OF THE FAMOUS BLOCK-STACKING GAME, AS WELL AS THE BEST-KNOWN (BUT NOT THE ONLY) VERSION ON NINTENDO'S FIRST HOME CONSOLE. THE GOAL IS TO PLACE PIECES MADE UP OF FOUR TILES IN A TEN-BY-TWENTY WELL, ORGANIZING THEM INTO COMPLETE ROWS, WHICH DISAPPEAR. AS ROWS ARE CLEARED, THE PACE OF THE GAME INCREASES, AND THE GAME ENDS IF THE STACK REACHES THE TOP OF THE WELL.

THE GAME OFFERS TWO DIFFERENT MODES OF PLAY, "TYPE A" AND "TYPE B". "TYPE A" IS A STANDARD ENDLESS MODE, WHERE THE SPEED OF THE GAME INCREASES EVERY TEN LINES, WITH AN OPTION FOR THE STARTING LEVEL WHEN BEGINNING THE GAME. "TYPE B", ON THE OTHER HAND, IS A RACE TO CLEAR 25 LINES, WITH OPTIONS FOR BOTH DROP SPEED AND STARTING GARBAGE. IN BOTH MODES, SUCCESSFUL PLAY IS REWARDED WITH CUTE ANIMATIONS. THERE ARE ALSO THREE DIFFERENT BACKGROUND SONGS TO CHOOSE FROM.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19891101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hi-Tech</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>05C998AE</hash>
		<image>./images/Tetris (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Tetris (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Tetris (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tetris (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="1417" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Addams Family, The (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>The Addams Family</name>
		<desc>THE ADDAMS FAMILY É UM JOGO DE PLATAFORMA BASEADO NO FILME DE MESMO NOME. O JOGADOR ASSUME O PAPEL DE GOMEZ, QUE PROCURA POR SEUS FAMILIARES DESAPARECIDOS. PARA ENCONTRÁ-LOS, ELE PRECISA EXPLORAR SEIS PARTES DIFERENTES DA MANSÃO. A MECÂNICA É SIMPLES: O JOGADOR SE MOVE DA ESQUERDA PARA A DIREITA ENQUANTO SALTA E EVITA INIMIGOS. ALGUNS DELES PODEM SER DERROTADOS PULANDO EM SUAS CABEÇAS.

A PRINCIPAL DIFERENÇA PARA AS OUTRAS VERSÕES DESTE JOGO É UM DESIGN DE NÍVEL ÚNICO. HÁ TAMBÉM UM MEDIDOR DE VIDA QUE PERMITE SER ATINGIDO COM MAIS FREQÜÊNCIA ANTES DE MORRER.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3DB484D4</hash>
		<image>./images/Addams Family, The (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Addams Family, The (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Addams Family, The (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Addams Family, The (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./The Adventures of Captain Comic (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>The Adventures of Captain Comic</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/The Adventures of Captain Comic (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/The Adventures of Captain Comic (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/The Adventures of Captain Comic (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/The Adventures of Captain Comic (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1348" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Immortal, The (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>The Immortal</name>
		<desc>THE IMMORTAL IS AN ISOMETRIC ACTION-ADVENTURE GAME.

YOUR OLD MENTOR MORDAMIR HAS DISAPPEARED. PROBABLY KIDNAPPED. YOU'RE NOT TOO SURE WHERE HE MIGHT BE, BUT A DUNGEON IS ALWAYS A GOOD PLACE TO LOOK, SO YOU SEEK OUT THE NEAREST ONE AND PLUNGE INTO ITS DEPTHS. BEWARE: 8 LEVELS OF 
ISOMETRIC DEATH AWAIT.

THE IMMORTAL IS THE PROTOTYPE OF A TRIAL-AND-ERROR GAME. PROGRESS IS MADE BY ENCOUNTERING A HAZARD, DYING, SOLVING THE PROBLEM, ENCOUNTERING THE NEXT HAZARD. TO SOLVE A LEVEL, YOU HAVE TO KNOW ITS TRAPS AND THEIR PATTERNS BY HEART. AS FRUSTRATING AS THIS MAY SOUND (IT IS), THE IMMORTAL QUITE CLEVERLY BALANCES ANNOYANCE WITH CURIOSITY AND GRAPHICAL REWARDS. IN SHORT: YOU WANT TO SEE WHAT CHALLENGE LIES IN THE NEXT ROOM.

THE PUZZLES RANGE FROM SIMPLE AVOIDANCE OF TRAPS TO THE CORRECT USE OF ITEMS; YOU COLLECT OBJECTS IN AN INVENTORY. EVERY NOW AND THEN, THE IMMORTAL SURPRISES WITH A SPECIAL CHALLENGE. FOR EXAMPLE, YOU'VE GOT TO RIDE A MAGIC CARPET THROUGH A HALLWAY FULL OF FIRE TRAPS, OR RIDE A BARREL ON AN UNDERGROUND RIVER. THE DUNGEON ISN'T EMPTY: SOME FRIEDLIES MAY HAVE VALUABLE INFORMATION OR TRADE ITEMS, THE NASTY SORT OF GUYS WILL ATTACK. COMBAT IS FOUGHT MAN-TO-MAN ON A SPECIAL SCREEN. YOUR ADVERSARY INDICATES HIS NEXT ATTACK A FEW SECONDS BEFORE HE EXECUTES IT, SO YOU'VE GOT TIME TO REACT APPROPRIATELY. YOU CAN DODGE TO THE LEFT OR THE RIGHT, AS WELL AS ATTACK FROM THESE TWO DIRECTIONS. THERE IS NO SAVE OPTION IN THE GAME, OF COURSE, BUT YOU MAY RESTART EACH LEVEL AS OFTEN AS YOU LIKE. LEVELS CAN BE SKIPPED BY ENTERING PASSWORDS.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sandcastle</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F6364CED</hash>
		<image>./images/Immortal, The (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Immortal, The (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Immortal, The (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Immortal, The (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./The Jetsons - Cogswell's Caper (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>The Jetsons - Cogswell's Caper</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/The Jetsons - Cogswell's Caper (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/The Jetsons - Cogswell's Caper (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/The Jetsons - Cogswell's Caper (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/The Jetsons - Cogswell's Caper (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./The Legend of Zelda 2 - The Adventure Of Link (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda 2 - The Adventure Of Link</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/The Legend of Zelda 2 - The Adventure Of Link (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/The Legend of Zelda 2 - The Adventure Of Link (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/The Legend of Zelda 2 - The Adventure Of Link (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/The Legend of Zelda 2 - The Adventure Of Link (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1587" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Astyanax (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>The Lord of King</name>
		<desc>YOU ARE ASTYANAX, A SIXTEEN YEAR OLD BOY THAT HAS THE SAME DREAM NIGHT AFTER NIGHT: A PRINCESS, CALLING FOR HELP. ONE AFTERNOON, YOU ARE SUMMONED TO THE WORLD OF REMNIA BY CUTIE, A PIXIE, TO SAVE THE REALM'S PRINCESS. YOU ARE THE CHOSEN ONE MENTIONED BY THEIR PROPHECIES!

YES, THIS IS YOUR TYPICAL FANTASY STORY SETTING. YOU MUST SAVE THE REALM FROM BLACKHORN'S EVIL HORDE! ALONG THE WAY YOU'LL FIND POWERUPS THAT WILL MAKE YOU STRONGER, AND UPGRADE YOUR WEAPON; AND YOU CAN ALSO UNLEASH MAGICAL ATTACKS THAT HIT ALL ENEMIES ON THE SCREEN.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0D57DBDF</hash>
		<image>./images/Astyanax (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Astyanax (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Astyanax (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Astyanax (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1537" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Time Lord (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Time Lord</name>
		<desc>IN THIS GAME YOU PLAY THE ROLE OF A TIME LORD WHO HAS TO TRAVEL THROUGH TIME IN ORDER TO STOP TIME TRAVELLING ALIENS FROM CHANGING THE EARTHS HISTORY. THE GAME PLAY INVOLVES YOU FIGHTING OFF ALIENS WHO ARE DRESSED LIKE THE PEOPLE FROM THE VARIOUS TIME PERIOD THAT YOU ARE IN. THE WEAPONS AT YOUR DISPOSAL VARY DEPENDING ON WHAT POINT IN TIME YOU ARE IN. IN ORDER TO TRAVEL TO ANOTHER TIME ZONE YOU MUST FIND 5 ORBS WHICH ARE CAREFULLY HIDDEN AROUND EACH LEVEL AND REQUIRE SOME PUZZLE SOLVING AND PLATFORM JUMPING TO GET TO. TIME IN THIS GAME RUNS BY VERY FAST AND YOU INLY HAVE UNTIL THE YEAR 3000 TO COMPLETE THE GAME OTHERWISE THE WORLD WILL BE BLOWN UP.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Milton Bradley</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FAE9F9E9</hash>
		<image>./images/Time Lord (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Time Lord (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Time Lord (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Time Lord (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="107884" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures</name>
		<desc>THESE TINY TOONS HAVE BIG PROBLEMS. THAT'S RIGHT. THE ARCH ENEMY OF ACME ACRES, MONTANA MAX, HAS KIDNAPPED THE EVER-SO-POPULAR BABS BUNNY. NOW THE FURRY FEMALE'S FATE RESTS IN THE PAWS OF BUSTER BUNNY AND HIS CRIME FIGHTING PALS - DIZZY DEVIL, FURRBALL AND PLUCKY DUCK. FOUR KOOKY BUDDIES WITH THEIR OWN SPECIAL TALENT. BUSTER CAN BOUNCE OVER BAD GUYS WITH THE BEST OF THEM. FURRBALL USES HIS FELINE CLAWS TO CLIMB WALLS. DIZZY DEVIL PREFERS TO SPIN THROUGH THEM. AND PLUCKY CAN GLIDE THROUGH THE AIR AND SWIM LIKE A FISH. CHOOSE WHICH PARTNER YOU WANT AT THE BEGINNING OF EACH LEVEL BEFORE YOU FACE-OFF AGAINST TIME AND GOOFBALLS GONE BAD IN 6 ZANY WONDERLANDS. SO YOU BETTER GET JUMPING OR IT WILL BE CURTAINS FOR OUR PLAYFUL PALS!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0E4071C0</hash>
		<image>./images/Tiny Toon Adventures (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Tiny Toon Adventures (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Tiny Toon Adventures (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tiny Toon Adventures (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1341" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Toki (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Toki</name>
		<desc>THE HERO OF THE GAME IS A YOUNG JUNGLE-MAN NAMED TOKI. ONE DAY THE EVIL WIZARD DR. STARK KIDNAPS HIS GIRLFRIEND WANDA. WHEN TOKI TRIES TO SAVE HER, HE IS TURNED INTO A MONKEY! NOW TOKI HAS TO FIND DR. STARK IN HIS PALACE, TO RESCUE WANDA, AND TO BECOME A HUMAN BEING AGAIN!

IT IS A PLATFORM GAME WITH A LOT OF VARIOUS LEVELS: JUNGLE, UNDERWATER, VOLCANIC CAVES, ON THE ICE... TOKI'S ONLY WEAPONS ARE SPITTING ON THE ENEMIES OR JUMPING ON THEM AND CRASHING THEM. THERE ARE MANY POSSIBILITIES TO UPGRADE HIS SPITTING "WEAPON";  FOR EXAMPLE, IF HE FINDS AN UPGRADE, HE CAN SPIT FIREBALLS. 

THIS GAME IS PORTED FROM AN OLDER ARCADE VERSION.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tad Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2E71C7C5</hash>
		<image>./images/Toki (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Toki (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Toki (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Toki (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Track &amp; Field 2 (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Track &amp; Field 2</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Track &amp; Field 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Track &amp; Field 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Track &amp; Field 2 (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Track &amp; Field 2 (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1573" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Track &amp; Field (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Track &amp; Field</name>
		<desc>TRACK &amp; FIELD IS A SPORTS GAME THAT ALLOWS THE PLAYER TO HAVE AN EXPERIENCE BASED AROUND THE SUMMER OLYMPIC GAMES. IT IS BASED ON AN ARCADE GAME OF THE SAME NAME. EVENTS INCLUDE 100 METER DASH, HAMMER THROW, THE LONG JUMP AND THE 110 METER HURDLES.

THE MSX VERSION REPLACES THE HURDLES WITH A 400 METER DASH.

THE NES VERSION ADDS SKEET SHOOTING, TRIPLE JUMP, JAVELIN THROW, HIGH JUMP, AND ARCHERY AS EVENTS BUT LOSES THE HAMMER THROW EVENT. THE NES VERSION ALSO KEEPS THE 110 METER HURDLES AND FORGOES THE 400 METER DASH.

IF YOU WANT TO GO TO THE NEXT EVENT OR ROUND THEN YOU WILL HAVE TO QUALIFY, BY BEATING INCREASINGLY DIFFICULT MAXIMUM TIMES OR MINIMUM DISTANCES. THIS GAME CONTAINS A TWO PLAYER OPTION, IN WHICH THE PLAYERS TAKE IT IN TURNS.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>67C2C8FC</hash>
		<image>./images/Track &amp; Field (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Track &amp; Field (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Track &amp; Field (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Track &amp; Field (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Turtle Ninja 2  - The Arcade Game (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Turtle Ninja 2  - The Arcade Game</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Turtle Ninja 2  - The Arcade Game (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Turtle Ninja 2  - The Arcade Game (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Turtle Ninja 2  - The Arcade Game (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Turtle Ninja 2  - The Arcade Game (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Turtle Ninja 3  - The Manhattan Proj (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Turtle Ninja 3  - The Manhattan Project</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Turtle Ninja 3  - The Manhattan Proj (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Turtle Ninja 3  - The Manhattan Proj (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Turtle Ninja 3  - The Manhattan Proj (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Turtle Ninja 3  - The Manhattan Proj (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1557" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Volleyball (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Volleyball</name>
		<desc>SLAM THE PERFECT SERVE. SPIKE THE GAME-WINNING POINT. MAKE THE SAVE THAT SAVES THE GAME! IT'S ALL UP TO YOU. BECAUSE YOU CALL THE SHOTS IN NINTENDO VOLLEYBALL. YOU'LL START BY SELECTING A TEAM FROM THE COUNTRY OF YOUR CHOICE. AS CAPTAIN, YOU'LL LEAD YOUR TEAM THROUGH A FAST-PACED WARM-UP ROUND, THEN QUICKLY MOVE INTO THE HEAT OF REAL VOLLEYBALL COMPETITION. YOU'LL DECIDE WHEN TO SPIKE, WHEN TO LOB, WHEN TO MAKE A DIVING SAVE - EVERYTHING JUST LIKE THE CAPTAIN OF A REAL VOLLEYBALL TEAM! PLAY AGAINST A FRIEND OR CHALLENGE THE COMPUTER. EITHER WAY, NINTENDO'S TRUE-TO-LIFE GRAPHICS AND REALISTIC GAME PLAY WILL BRING ALL THE FUN AND EXCITEMENT OF VOLEYBALL RIGHT INTO YOUR HOME!</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19870301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>0E5FAB84</hash>
		<image>./images/Volleyball (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Volleyball (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Volleyball (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Volleyball (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18914" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Werewolf - The Last Warrior (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Werewolf: The Last Warrior</name>
		<desc>AN EVIL LEADER AND HIS GANG OF BIO-ENGINEERED MONSTERS HAS TAKEN OVER THE LAND AND ONLY ONE MAN STANDS IN THEIR WAY. ONLY HE'S NOT A MAN, HE IS A LYCANTHROPE, A PERSON ABLE TO TRANSFORM INTO A TERRIBLE WEREWOLF TO LET LOOSE HIS ANGER.

YOU START THE GAME IN HUMAN FORM. THE HUMAN CAN PUNCH, JUMP, MOVE AND SHOOT A POWERED UP SHOT WHICH MOVES HORIZONTALLY ACROSS THE SCREEN.  BY FINDING A RED "W" ICON, THE HUMAN IS ABLE TO TRANSFORM INTO A MIGHTY WEREWOLF CREATURE. ACCIDENTALLY GRABBING A BLUE "W" ICON OR LOSING TOO MUCH ENERGY WILL CHANGE YOU BACK INTO A MERE HUMAN BEING. THE WEREWOLF FORM OFFERS HIGHER JUMPS, QUICKER SPEED, GREATER STRENGTH, A SHOCKWAVE ATTACK AND THE ABILITY TO CLIMB WALLS, SO NATURALLY YOU'LL WANT THIS FORM WHENEVER POSSIBLE.  ADDITIONALLY THE WEREWOLF FORM HAS AN ANGER METER THAT IS AUGMENTED BY COLLECTING ORBS. AFTER 5 SUCH ORBS, THE WEREWOLF WILL TRANSFORM YET AGAIN INTO A SUPER WEREWOLF WITH EVEN GREATER STRENGTH, SPEED AND PARTIAL INVINCIBILITY.

THERE ARE 5 STAGES IN ALL. EACH WITH A BOSS WHO MOVES IN A DISTINCT PATTERN.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East USA, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>9FB47FC0</hash>
		<image>./images/Werewolf - The Last Warrior (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Werewolf - The Last Warrior (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Werewolf - The Last Warrior (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Werewolf - The Last Warrior (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1479" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Willow (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Willow</name>
		<desc>WILLOW IS AN ACTION RPG BASED ON THE MOVIE WITH THE SAME NAME. THE PLAYER ASSUMES THE ROLE OF WILLOW, THE CHOSEN ONE WHO MUST RESTORE HUMAN FORM TO THE BENEVOLENT SORCERESS FIN RAZIEL AND DESTROY THE EVIL SORCERESS, BAVMORDA. WHILE THE GAME FOLLOWS THE MOVIE'S PLOT SOMEWHAT MOST OF THE TIME, IT ALSO EXPANDS ON IT AND INTRODUCES CHARACTERS, RACES AND ENEMIES NOT FOUND IN THE MOVIE.

GAMEPLAY IS SIMILAR TO OTHER ACTION RPGS AND THE LEGEND OF ZELDA. WILLOW IS SEEN FROM A TOP DOWN PERSPECTIVE AND ALL ENEMIES ARE VISIBLE ON SCREEN. SLAYING ENEMIES WILL GIVE WILLOW EXPERIENCE POINTS, WHICH WILL EVENTUALLY LEAD TO HIM INCREASING HIS STATS AUTOMATICALLY. NEW WEAPONS, SHIELDS AND MAGIC ITEMS ARE FOUND IN VARIOUS TREASURE CHESTS SCATTERED ACROSS THE LAND OR GIVEN TO WILLOW AS PART OF THE PLOT. ASIDE FROM BATTLING MINOR ENEMIES WILLOW WILL ALSO FACE OFF AGAINST SEVERAL BOSS MONSTERS AS WELL AS CHARACTERS FROM THE MOVIE.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1025CBF8</hash>
		<image>./images/Willow (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Willow (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Willow (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Willow (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18781" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wolverine (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Wolverine</name>
		<desc>IN THIS SIDE-SCROLLING ACTION GAME, YOU PLAY AS WOLVERINE, STRANDED ON A REMOTE ISLAND BY SABRETOOTH AND MAGNETO, AND MUST FIGHT YOUR WAY THROUGH NINE MISSIONS, ULTIMATELY CONCLUDING WITH BATTLES AGAINST SABRETOOTH AND MAGNETO. ALONG THE WAY, FELLOW X-MEN HAVOK, PSYLOCKE AND JUBILEE CAN BE CALLED UPON TO AID WOLVERINE IN CERTAIN SITUATIONS. OF COURSE, YOU CAN ALWAYS UTILIZE YOUR ADAMANTIUM CLAWS AND HEALING FACTOR WHEN THE GOING GETS TOUGH.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19911001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>LJN, Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3596EC4C</hash>
		<image>./images/Wolverine (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Wolverine (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Wolverine (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wolverine (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1547" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Yo! Noid (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Yo! Noid</name>
		<desc>OR, HOW A YO-YO SAVED NEW YOIK!

WHO'S GOT FLOPPY EARS, A FURRY SUIT, AND A TOOTHY, HILARIOUS GRIN? IT'S YO!NOID, THE YO-YOING, PIZZA-CHOMPING FUNNYMAN FROM THOSE WACKY DOMINO'S PIZZA TV COMMERCIALS. HE'LL NEED EVERY TRICK IN HIS FUZZY HAT TO OUT-PRANK THE SCAMPS WHO ARE OVERRUNNING NEW YORK WITH MONKEYSHRINES AND SHENANIGANS!

YO!NOID SKIPS, SKATES, AND SCALES THE SKYSCRAPERS, BONKING OUT AN EVER-CHANGING GANG OF RASCALS! A MYSTERIOUS NOID LOOK-ALIKE IS BEHIND THE TOMFOOLERY, AND THE REAL NOID'S GOT TO STOP HIM! WHAT COULD MAKE THE ROLLICKING NOID GET SO SERIOUS? THE REWARD IS A LIFETIME SUPPLY OF HIS FAVORITE FOOD!

-14 ROMPING LEVELS OF FUN!
-INCREDIBLE INVENTIONS WHIZ THE NOID AROUND NEW YORK!
-GOBBLE YOUR WAY THROUGH PIZZA-EATING CONTESTS!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Now Production Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7EECDBB1</hash>
		<image>./images/Yo! Noid (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Yo! Noid (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Yo! Noid (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Yo! Noid (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1721" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Zanac (U) (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Zanac</name>
		<desc>ZANAC A.I. IS A 2D SHOOT THEM UP GAME. YOU ARE FLYING FIGHTER MODEL ZANAC, A SHIP BUILT BY 256 RIOT FLEET AS MAN'S LAST HOPE AGAINST TOTAL ANNIHILATION. ON BOARD ARE SPECIAL WEAPONS TO HELP YOU BLAST YOUR WAY THROUGH TWELVE SCREENS OF ENEMY CREATURES AND DESTROY THE SYSTEM'S HOME BASE. ZANAC IS DIVIDED INTO 12 "AREAS", WHICH LOOK LIKE PLANETS. THE VARIOUS LOCATIONS RANGE FROM DESERTS TO JUNGLES AND FROM OCEANS TO INDUSTRIAL ZONES, FEATURING MANY DIFFERENT TYPES OF ENEMIES.

ZANAC'S UNIQUE ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE PROGRAM CAN INTENSIFY THE ACTION BASED UPON YOUR LEVEL OF SKILL. THE BETTER YOU ARE, THE MORE POWERFUL "THE SYSTEM". EXAMPLES OF THE A.I. (BUT NOT LIMITED TO) IN THIS GAME: THE ENEMIES ARE GENERALLY COMING RANDOMLY WITH THEIR BEHAVIOR BASED ON FACTORS LIKE THE POSITION YOUR SHIP IN THE SCREEN, THE PLACE YOU LAST DIED; THE SHOOT SPEED OF THE ENEMIES AND BOSSES DO ALSO VARY.

AT THE END OF EACH AREA (LEVEL) YOU'LL HAVE TO FIGHT THE AREA BOSS. AREA BOSSES ARE MAINLY BASED AROUND HUGE, SCREEN-FILLING BUNKER BASES CONSISTING OF GUN TURRETS AND A "CORE". YOU HAVE LIMITED TIME FOR FIGHTING AGAINST THE AREA BOSS - A TIME OUT COULD MEAN FAILURE IN ENTERING THE NEXT STAGE, AND WITH THE TIME RUNNING, MORE AND MORE ENEMIES WERE ATTACKING AS PENALTY.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19871201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B8C979A4</hash>
		<image>./images/Zanac (U) (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Zanac (U) (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Zanac (U) (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Zanac (U) (PT-BR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1250" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./The Legend of Zelda (PT-BR).zip</path>
		<name>Zelda no Densetsu 1 : The Hyrule Fantasy</name>
		<desc>IN ONE OF THE DARKEST TIMES IN THE KINGDOM OF HYRULE, A YOUNG, POINTY-EARED BOY NAMED LINK TAKES ON AN EPIC QUEST TO RESTORE THE FRAGMENTED TRIFORCE OF WISDOM AND SAVE THE PRINCESS ZELDA FROM THE CLUTCHES OF THE EVIL, POWER-HUNGRY GANON.

THE LEGEND OF ZELDA FOR THE NES MARKS THE FIRST ACTION-ADVENTURE TITLE OF THE POPULAR NINTENDO SERIES. PLAYERS MUST MAKE THEIR WAY THROUGH THE VARIOUS FORESTS, GRAVEYARDS, PLAINS, AND DESERTS OF THE OVERWORLD TO FIND THE SECRET ENTRANCES OF THE EIGHT DUNGEONS IN AN ATTEMPT TO PIECE TOGETHER THE BROKEN TRIFORCE. ONCE ALL PIECES ARE JOINED, LINK WILL BE ABLE TO GAIN ENTRY TO DEATH MOUNTAIN, HOME OF GANON, AND PRISON OF PRINCESS ZELDA.

THE GAME IS DRAWN IN A TOP-DOWN PERSPECTIVE. LINK BEGINS HIS QUEST IN THE OVERWORLD, WHICH FEATURES FORESTS, MOUNTAINS AND LAKES AND IS DIVIDED INTO SEVERAL SCREENS. LINK CAN EXPLORE THE OVERWORLD FREELY, THOUGH WHEN HE ENTERS A SCREEN, HE WILL ENCOUNTER SEVERAL ENEMIES. HE CAN ATTACK THEM WITH HIS SWORD. IF LINK IS AT FULL HEALTH, HE CAN TOSS HIS SWORD TO ATTACK ENEMIES FROM AFAR, BUT WHEN HE IS HURT, EVEN SLIGHTLY, HE CAN ONLY FIGHT IN MELEE RANGE. 

LINK'S HEALTH IS REPRESENTED BY HEARTS; INITIALLY HE CAN HAVE A MAXIMUM OF THREE HEARTS, BUT AS HE PROGRESSES IN THE GAME, HE WILL FIND HEART CONTAINERS THAT INCREASE HIS MAXIMUM HEALTH. THE ENEMIES ARE VARIED - SOME ATTACK FROM UP CLOSE, SOME SHOOT PROJECTILES. WHEN KILLED, THEY OFTEN LEAVE BEHIND AN ITEM - A HEART TO RESTORE ENERGY, RUPEES THAT FUNCTION AS MONEY (AND CAN BE USED TO BUY STUFF IN VARIOUS SHOPS IN THE OVERWORLD), OR BOMBS WHICH CAN BE PICKED UP AND SET DOWN TO ATTACK ENEMIES OR DESTROY SOME WALLS. WHEN ENEMIES ARE KILLED, THEY STAY DEAD AND WILL NOT RE-APPEAR ONCE THE SCREEN IS ENTERED AGAIN. 

THERE ARE OTHER ITEMS TO FIND IN THE GAME; SOME FUNCTION AS WEAPONS, WHILE OTHERS ARE USED TO SOLVE PUZZLES. 

TO FIND THE TRIFORCE PIECES, LINK MUST EXPLORE DUNGEONS. ONCE HE FINDS AN ENTRANCE TO THE DUNGEON AND GOES IN, HE MUST EXPLORE THE ROOMS, FIGHT ENEMIES AND COLLECT KEYS UNTIL HE FINDS THE BOSS MONSTER HE MUST DEFEAT. HE WILL THEN BE ABLE TO PICK UP A TRIFORCE PIECE. ONCE HE DOES SO, HOWEVER, ALL THE MONSTERS IN THE OVERWORLD COME BACK TO LIFE. 

IF LINK DIES ON HIS QUEST, HE CAN CONTINUE IT; HE WILL GO BACK TO HIS START POSITION IN THE OVERWORLD, BUT WITH THE ITEMS HE MANAGED TO COLLECT SO FAR. WHEN LINK FINISHES HIS QUEST, THE PL;AYER CAN CHOOSE TO PLAY THE "2ND QUEST", WHICH IS ESSENTIALLY A HARDER VERSION OF THE GAME. 

THE LEGEND OF ZELDA IS KNOWN FOR SEVERAL FACTORS THAT WERE REVOLUTIONARY AT THE TIME: A FULL WORLD THAT COULD BE FREELY EXPLORED, POWER-UPS THAT WOULD PERMANENTLY ENHANCE YOUR CHARACTER'S ABILITIES, AND A BATTERY BACK-UP SAVE FEATURE THAT ALLOWED PLAYERS TO RETAIN THEIR PROGRESS INSTEAD OF HAVING TO START OVER. THE GAMEPLAY BALANCED OUT FREQUENT ACTION SEQUENCES WITH DISCOVERY, SECRETS, AND EXPLORATION.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5BD29CD3</hash>
		<image>./images/The Legend of Zelda (PT-BR).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/The Legend of Zelda (PT-BR).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/The Legend of Zelda (PT-BR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/The Legend of Zelda (PT-BR).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
</gameList>