<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<game id="12769" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./After Burner III (USA).chd</path>
		<name>After Burner III</name>
		<desc>O TERCEIRO NA SÉRIE DE SIMULADORES DE VÔO ARCADE DA SEGA. AFTER BURNER III LEVA VOCÊ DE VOLTA A UM F-14 TOMCAT, PARA ENFRENTAR O MAIOR NÚMERO POSSÍVEL DE AVIÕES TERRORISTAS COM SEU ARSENAL DE MÍSSEIS E SEU FIEL CANHÃO VULCANO. 
EXCLUSIVO PARA O SEGA CD, O TÍTULO É NA VERDADE UMA VERSÃO DO STRIKE FIGHTER, UM ARCADE LANÇADO NO JAPÃO QUE TENTOU MISTURAR A JOGABILIDADE "FÁCIL" DO G-LOC AIR BATTLE COM OS TRUQUES DE AFTER BURNER. O JOGO APRESENTA CAMERA INTERNA E EXTERNA, OU SEJA, VOCÊ TEM A CAPACIDADE DE JOGAR COM A VISÃO INTERNA DA AERONAVE (COCKPIT), OU NA VERSÃO CLÁSSICA DO LADO DE FORA DO AVIÃO.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/After Burner III (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/After Burner III (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/After Burner III (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/After Burner III (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12802" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./AH-3 Thunderstrike (USA).chd</path>
		<name>AH-3 Thunderstrike</name>
		<desc>THUNDERHAWK É UM JOGO DE AÇÃO PARA O SEGA-CD QUE LHE DÁ O CONTROLE DE UM HELICÓPTERO DE COMBATE EM UMA SÉRIE DE SEIS CAMPANHAS FUTURISTAS. A VERSÃO ORIGINAL INCLUI UM TOTAL DE 60 OPERAÇÕES COM VÁRIOS OBJETIVOS. ANTES DE VOAR NO CÉU, O JOGADOR PODE ADAPTAR O ARSENAL EMBARCADO PARA SE ADEQUAR A ELE. A PILOTAGEM É TÉCNICA, MAS ACESSÍVEL, SEM SER TÃO COMPLEXA QUANTO OUTRAS SIMULAÇÕES DISPONÍVEIS EM 1993.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JVC</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E6D2439E</hash>
		<image>./images/AH-3 Thunderstrike (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/AH-3 Thunderstrike (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/AH-3 Thunderstrike (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/AH-3 Thunderstrike (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12760" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./AX-101 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>AX-101</name>
		<desc>O JOGO É UM SHOOTER ON-RAILS, COM UMA JOGABILIDADE VISTA A PARTIR DE UMA PERSPECTIVA DE CABINE DE PRIMEIRA PESSOA. A NAVE DO JOGADOR SE MOVE AUTOMATICAMENTE ATRAVÉS DE AMBIENTES PLANETÁRIOS E PRÉ-RENDERIZADOS, E APENAS O ALVO PODE SER MOVIDO LIVREMENTE. CANHÕES DE LASER E OGIVAS DE FUSÃO ESTÃO DISPONÍVEIS PARA ACERTAR OS INÚMEROS INIMIGOS. OS LASERS TÊM MUNIÇÃO ILIMITADA, MAS PRECISAM DE ALGUNS MOMENTOS PARA RECARREGAR. AS OGIVAS FUNCIONAM COMO BOMBAS INTELIGENTES E LIMPAM A TELA DOS INIMIGOS, MAS ESTÃO DISPONÍVEIS APENAS EM QUANTIDADE LIMITADA. ELES SÃO REABASTECIDOS AO ATINGIR UMA DETERMINADA PONTUAÇÃO. O ESCUDO DE ENERGIA DO NAVIO FUNCIONA COMO UMA BARRA DE VIDA.

ENTRE OS NÍVEIS DE DISPARO, HÁ CENAS DE TRANSIÇÃO, PRÉ-RENDERIZADAS DA MESMA MANEIRA QUE A JOGABILIDADE REAL.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<hash>3B4F68D0</hash>
		<image>./images/AX-101 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/AX-101 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/AX-101 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/AX-101 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12716" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Batman Returns (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Batman Returns</name>
		<desc>BATMAN RETURNS NO CD DA SEGA É UMA VERSÃO MELHORADA DA ADAPTAÇÃO DO FILME PARA SEGA GENESIS. INCLUI A TOTALIDADE DO JOGO DE PLATAFORMA ORIGINAL, MAS ADICIONA NÍVEIS DE CONDUÇÃO TOTALMENTE NOVOS.

O JOGO PODE SER JOGADO DE TRÊS MANEIRAS: COMO APENAS O JOGO DE PLATAFORMA, APENAS O JOGO DE CORRIDA, OU UMA COMBINAÇÃO DE AMBOS. CADA OPÇÃO APRESENTA UMA SEQUÊNCIA FINAL EXCLUSIVA.

PARA CADA UM DOS CINCO NÍVEIS DE PLATAFORMA DA VERSÃO ORIGINAL, HÁ UMA SEÇÃO DE DIREÇÃO RELACIONADA NA QUAL O JOGADOR CONTROLA O BATMÓVEL OU O BATSKIBOAT. TANTO EM PERSPECTIVA QUANTO EM JOGABILIDADE, ESSAS SEÇÕES SÃO REMANESCENTES DE TÍTULOS DE ARCADE COMO OUTRUN. VISTO DE CIMA E DE TRÁS, O VEÍCULO DO JOGADOR DEVE ALCANÇAR OS PONTOS DE CHECAGEM ANTES QUE O CRONÔMETRO ACABE, RECEBENDO PONTOS DE BÔNUS POR QUAISQUER SEGUNDOS EXCEDENTES. O HARDWARE DO SISTEMA DE CD É USADO PARA DIMENSIONAMENTO DE SPRITES E OUTROS TRUQUES, OBTENDO UM EFEITO 3D.

SENDO O JOGO BASEADO EM UM FILME CHEIO DE AÇÃO, NÃO É SÓ DIRIGIR, MAS TAMBÉM ATIRAR: TANTO O CARRO QUANTO O BARCO ESTÃO ARMADOS COM METRALHADORAS E MÍSSEIS DE BUSCA DE CALOR (COM MUNIÇÃO LIMITADA). ALÉM DAS ESTRADAS ESTAREM CHEIAS DE INIMIGOS EM GERAL, CADA NÍVEL TAMBÉM TERMINA EM UMA LUTA CONTRA UM GRANDE VEÍCULO (E GERALMENTE FORTEMENTE ARMADO).

O JOGO APRESENTA FAIXAS DE ÁUDIO BASEADAS EM CD, SUBSTITUINDO AS DO ORIGINAL.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Malibu Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9FAC4044</hash>
		<image>./images/Batman Returns (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Batman Returns (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Batman Returns (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Batman Returns (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12790" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Battlecorps (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Battlecorps</name>
		<desc>BATTLECORPS É UM JOGO MECH GIGANTE QUE OCORRE EM UM PLANETA DE MINERAÇÃO CONHECIDO COMO O MUNDO DE MANDLEBROT. O SUPERCOMPUTADOR DA COLÔNIA FOI INFECTADO POR UM VÍRUS, E AGORA AS GIGANTESCAS MÁQUINAS DO PLANETA ESTÃO SE VOLTANDO CONTRA AS PESSOAS QUE AS CRIARAM. VOCÊ DEVE PILOTAR SUA MÁQUINA DE ATAQUE BÍPEDE ATRAVÉS DE 12 MISSÕES PARA REINICIAR O COMPUTADOR.

OS GRÁFICOS NESTE JOGO USAM SPRITES DIMENSIONADOS E GIRADOS PARA ALCANÇAR UM AMBIENTE 3D. O EFEITO É SEMELHANTE A OUTROS JOGOS DA CORE DESIGN PARA O SEGA CD.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2CB17CA0</hash>
		<image>./images/Battlecorps (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Battlecorps (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Battlecorps (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Battlecorps (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12797" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./BC Racers (USA).chd</path>
		<name>BC Racers</name>
		<desc>BC RACERS É UM JOGO DE CORRIDA DE KART COM PERSONAGENS DA SÉRIE DE JOGOS CHUCK ROCK DA CORE DESIGN.

CADA UM DOS PILOTOS NESTE JOGO PILOTA UMA MOTO PRÉ-HISTÓRICA COM UM SIDE CAR. EM CADA EQUIPE DE DOIS PERSONAGENS, UMA PESSOA DIRIGE A MOTOCICLETA, E A OUTRA LUTA CONTRA OS ADVERSÁRIOS USANDO PAULADAS, SOCOS, CHUTES, ETC.

OS GRÁFICOS EM BC RACERS CONSISTEM EM UMA PAISAGEM PLANA DECORADA COM SPRITES EM ROTAÇÃO E ESCALA PARA COMPOR A PISTA E O CENÁRIO.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>8A19418E</hash>
		<image>./images/BC Racers (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/BC Racers (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/BC Racers (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/BC Racers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12849" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bill Walsh College Football (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bill Walsh College Football</name>
		<desc>O JOGO APRESENTA 24 TIMES UNIVERSITÁRIOS DE FUTEBOL DA TEMPORADA DE 1993 E 24 DAS EQUIPES UNIVERSITÁRIAS DE TODOS OS TEMPOS DESDE 1978. MODOS DE JOGO INCLUEM EXIBIÇÃO, PLAYOFFS E PLAYOFFS DE TODOS OS TEMPOS.

AS TÁTICAS CONSISTEM EM 56 JOGADAS OFENSIVAS E 52 JOGADAS DEFENSIVAS.
NA OFENSIVA, OS RUNNING BACKS PODEM MERGULHAR, GIRAR E ATROPELAR. ALÉM DISSO, A PASSAGEM É TRATADA TENDO OS RECEPTORES EM SUAS PRÓPRIAS CAIXAS COM JANELAS. QUANDO NA DEFESA, OS DEFENSORES PODEM MERGULHAR NO SUPORTE DA BOLA E LEVANTAR AS MÃOS PARA BLOQUEAR CHUTES OU INTERCEPTAR PASSES.

O JOGO TAMBÉM APRESENTA QUATRO CONDIÇÕES METEOROLÓGICAS (TEMPO BOM, VENTOSO, CHUVOSO E NEVE) E TRÊS TEMPOS DE QUARTOS DIFERENTES (20, 40 E 60 MINUTOS).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Visual Concepts</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>3A58175B</hash>
		<image>./images/Bill Walsh College Football (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bill Walsh College Football (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bill Walsh College Football (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bill Walsh College Football (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12770" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Black Hole Assault (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Blackhole Assault</name>
		<desc>BLACK HOLE ASSAULT DO MEGA CD É UM JOGO DE LUTA FUTURISTA. A AÇÃO OCORRE DURANTE O SÉCULO 22, QUANTO A EXPLORAÇÃO DO SISTEMA SOLAR NÃO É APENAS POSSÍVEL, MAS NECESSÁRIA PARA A SOBREVIVÊNCIA DA HUMANIDADE. INCORPORE UMA DAS MÁQUINAS DE SUA ESCOLHA E LUTE CONTRA ALIENÍGENAS EM UM DOS 10 PLANETAS E LUAS DISPONÍVEIS.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micronet</developer>
		<publisher>Micronet</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F92E809C</hash>
		<image>./images/Black Hole Assault (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Black Hole Assault (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Black Hole Assault (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Black Hole Assault (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12818" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bouncers (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bouncers</name>
		<desc>UM ARCADE DE BASQUETE ONDE VOCÊ É A BOLA. VOCÊ NÃO PODE PULAR ALTO O SUFICIENTE POR CONTA PRÓPRIA PARA PASSAR PELO ARO, ENTÃO VOCÊ DEVE RICOCHETEAR COM OUTROS JOGADORES. SUPORTA ATÉ QUATRO JOGADORES SIMULTÂNEOS.

EXISTEM OITO PERSONAGENS PARA ESCOLHER, POWERUPS (E POWERDOWNS) QUE AFETAM SUA VELOCIDADE E CAPACIDADE DE PULO.

OS JOGOS PODEM SE TRANSFORMAR EM COMBATES, JÁ QUE OS JOGADORES PODEM CHUTAR UNS AOS OUTROS PARA COLOCAR SEU OPONENTE NO AR. COM A PRÁTICA, VOCÊ PODE APRENDER A CHUTAR DE TRÊS PONTOS E SE ENTERRAR NA CESTA.

AS QUADRAS VARIAM DA CIDADE PADRÃO A UMA QUADRA LUNAR SUBAQUÁTICA E DE BAIXA GRAVIDADE.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Dynamix</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>A876259E</hash>
		<image>./images/Bouncers (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bouncers (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bouncers (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bouncers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58712" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Brutal - Paws of Fury (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Brutal: Paws of Fury</name>
		<desc>ACROSS THE WORLD, INVITATIONS WERE DELIVERED. UNDER THE WATCHFUL EYE OF THE GREAT MASTER DALI LLAMA, THE WORLDS GREATEST MARTIAL ARTISTS WOULD RETURN TO A PLACE THEY KNEW WELL.. BRUTAL ISLAND. EACH WILL USE THEIR OWN UNIQUE MENTAL AND PHYSICAL MARTIAL ARTS STYLE AND TRAINING IN A TOURNAMENT TO PROVE THE WORLDS ONE TRUE CHAMPION.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GameTek</developer>
		<publisher>GameTek</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>AF90BF1F</hash>
		<image>./images/Brutal - Paws of Fury (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Brutal - Paws of Fury (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Brutal - Paws of Fury (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Brutal - Paws of Fury (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58731" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cadillacs and Dinosaurs - The Second Cataclysm (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cadillacs and Dinosaurs: The Second Cataclysm</name>
		<desc>CADILLACS AND DINOSAURS: THE SECOND CATACLYSM IS A SEGA MEGA-CD (AND DOS) GAME BASED ON THE COMIC BOOK SERIES XENOZOIC TALES, AND THE TV SHOW OF THE SAME NAME. IT IS NOT TO BE CONFUSED WITH THE ARCADE BEAT-'EM-UP, CADILLACS AND DINOSAURS BY CAPCOM. THE MEGA-CD GAME WAS ONLY RELEASED IN NORTH AMERICA AND BRAZIL.NNNNSET IN THE "XENOZOIC AGE", WHICH OCCURS AFTER A DISASTER IN THE YEAR 2020 CAUSING ALL OF EARTH'S PREVIOUS INHABITANTS TO SHARE THE PLANET AT ONCE. IN ORDER TO MAINTAIN BALANCE DISRUPTED BY A MUTANT-LIKE RACE KNOWN AS THE GIRTH, YOU SET OUT IN A 1953 CADILLAC WITH MACHINE GUNS.NNNNIT IS AN ON-THE-RAILS FMV GAME, WHERE YOU SPEND MOST OF THE TIME AVOIDING OBSTACLES AND SHOOTING ENEMIES.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rocket Science Games</developer>
		<publisher>Rocket Science Games</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>3D5B58FD</hash>
		<image>./images/Cadillacs and Dinosaurs - The Second Cataclysm (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Cadillacs and Dinosaurs - The Second Cataclysm (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Cadillacs and Dinosaurs - The Second Cataclysm (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cadillacs and Dinosaurs - The Second Cataclysm (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12814" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Championship Soccer '94 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Championship Soccer '94</name>
		<desc>SENSIBLE SOCCER ON MEGA-CD INCLUDES THE PLAYERS NAMES PRESENT IN EUROPEAN CLUBS DURING THE SEASON 92/93. YOU CAN ALSO TAKE PART IN QUALIFYING FOR THE WORLD CUP 94. ONE OF THE MAIN ARGUMENTS OF THE GAME WHEN IT WAS RELEASED, WAS THE TAKING INTO ACCOUNT OF THE FAULTS AND CARDS.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renegade Kid</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>C0192275</hash>
		<image>./images/Championship Soccer '94 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Championship Soccer '94 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Championship Soccer '94 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Championship Soccer '94 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12732" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Chuck Rock II - Son of Chuck (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Chuck Rock II: Son of Chuck</name>
		<desc>AS YOU MAY REMEMBER, CHUCK ROCK HAD TO RESCUE HIS GIRL, OPHELIA FROM THE BAD DUDE GARY GRITTER.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E6CABECA</hash>
		<image>./images/Chuck Rock II - Son of Chuck (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Chuck Rock II - Son of Chuck (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Chuck Rock II - Son of Chuck (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Chuck Rock II - Son of Chuck (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12743" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Chuck Rock (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Chuck Rock</name>
		<desc>CHUCK ROCK É O TÍPICO HOMEM DAS CAVERNAS. ELE GOSTA DE PASSAR AS TARDES DE DOMINGO ASSISTINDO FUTEBOL E BEBENDO CERVEJA. INFELIZMENTE, SUA PACÍFICA EXISTÊNCIA É INTERROMPIDA QUANDO SUA ESPOSA, OPHELIA ROCK, É SEQUESTRADA PELO ESQUISITO DA ALDEIA, GARY GRITTER. ENTÃO, CHUCK ESTÁ BASTANTE CHATEADO COM TODA ESSA SITUAÇÃO E VOCÊ TEM QUE AJUDÁ-LO A FAZER A COISA CERTA. O JOGO É ESTILO PLATAFORMA. CHUCK LUTA COM UMA VARIEDADE DE DINOSSAUROS USANDO SEU ATAQUE DE BARRIGA E UM CHUTE COM PULO. OCASIONALMENTE ELE TEM QUE PEGAR E JOGAR PEDRAS PARA DERROTAR OS INIMIGOS E PERMITIR QUE ELE PULE PARA ALTURAS MAIORES.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B4821FAB</hash>
		<image>./images/Chuck Rock (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Chuck Rock (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Chuck Rock (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Chuck Rock (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12811" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cliffhanger (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cliffhanger</name>
		<desc>UM SIDE-SCROLL DE LUTA PADRÃO BASEADO NO FILME DE STALLONE DE MESMO NOME. SLY DEVE LUTAR CONTRA BANDIDOS E OS ELEMENTOS ENQUANTO ELE RASTREIA AS MALAS DE DINHEIRO ROUBADAS QUE CAEM AO REDOR DOS PICOS DAS MONTANHAS ROCHOSAS. O COMBATE SEGUE O PADRÃO FINAL FIGHT, QUEBRADO POR ALGUMAS ESCALADAS DE MONTANHA E CORRIDAS (OU SNOWBOARD 3D NO SEGA CD) DE AVALANCHES.NNNNOS INIMIGOS SÃO BANDIDOS BRAWLERS, OCASIONALMENTE CARREGANDO ARMAS E FACAS QUE O JOGADOR PODE PEGAR. O JOGO TENDE A SEGUIR UM PADRÃO DE TER QUE LIDAR COM UM PERIGO NATURAL (ESCALAR UM PENHASCO, SALTAR SOBRE AS LACUNAS), TRAVAR A TELA PARA UM SEGMENTO DE COMBATE, NATUREZA NOVAMENTE, LUTAR NOVAMENTE, ETC. OS MOVIMENTOS DE LUTA DISPONÍVEIS SÃO LIMITADOS, EM COMPARAÇÃO COM OUTROS JOGOS DESSE TIPO, E A CAPACIDADE DE ACERTAR UM PERSONAGEM INIMIGO É VISIVELMENTE MENOS PRECISA.NNNNO ENREDO É IDÊNTICO AO FILME, COM NÍVEIS BASEADOS OU INSPIRADOS EM CENAS DO FILME. AS CENAS ANIMADAS MOVEM A HISTÓRIA NOS SISTEMAS DE CARTUCHO, ENQUANTO CLIPES CURTOS DO FILME TOCAM ENTRE OS NÍVEIS NO CD SEGA.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Malibu Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Cliffhanger (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Cliffhanger (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Cliffhanger (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cliffhanger (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12783" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cobra Command (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cobra Command</name>
		<desc>COBRA COMMAND IS AN ARCADE CONVERSION OF A HELICOPTER SHOOTING GAME FROM DATA EAST.  IT IS AN "ON RAILS" STYLE SHOOTER WITH THE PLAYER CONTROLLING ONLY THE AIMING OF THE SHOOTING BUT NOT THE DIRECTION OF THE HELICOPTER.  

YOUR JOB IS TO SHOOT DOWN THE ENEMIES AS YOU ARE FLOWN THROUGH FOOTAGE OF NEW YORK STREETS, THE STATUE OF LIBERTY, THE ATLANTIC OCEAN, ITALY, THE GRAND CANYON AND FINALLY, THE TREACHEROUS CORNERS AND RETURN FIRE OF THE ENEMY'S STRONGHOLD ON EASTER ISLAND.

THERE IS NO BACKGROUND MUSIC TO GO ALONG WITH THE SOUND EFFECTS.  THE LEVELS ARE FAIRLY SHORT WITH A TOTAL GAME RUN THROUGH POSSIBLE IN ABOUT 20 MINUTES.</desc>
		<rating>0.15</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>EBA3D9BC</hash>
		<image>./images/Cobra Command (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Cobra Command (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Cobra Command (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cobra Command (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="102823" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Compton's Interactive Encyclopedia (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Compton's Interactive Encyclopedia</name>
		<desc>COMPTON'S INTERACTIVE ENCYCLOPEDIA IS, OF COURSE, AN MULTIMEDIA ENCYCLOPEDIA LICENSED FROM THE COMPTON'S SERIES OF PRINT ENCYCLOPEDIAS, SPORTING A COMPARATIVELY IMPRESSIVE 34,000 SUBJECTS, 5,000 PICTURES, AND 30 VIDEO ARTICLES FROM THE AMERICAN LIBRARY ACCOCIATION. IT IS PART OF A SIZEABLE SERIES THAT PRESUMABLY STARTED IN 1989 AND HAD A NUMBER OF ENTRIES THROUGHOUT THE '90S; A POSSIBLE RELATION BETWEEN THIS MEGA-CD PRODUCT AND THE SIMILARLY TITLED 1992 CD-I PRODUCT IS UNKNOWN.

A "VERSION 2.10" EXISTS; DIFFERENCES ARE UNKNOWN.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Learning Company</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2E995213</hash>
		<image>./images/Compton's Interactive Encyclopedia (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Compton's Interactive Encyclopedia (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Compton's Interactive Encyclopedia (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Compton's Interactive Encyclopedia (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12775" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Corpse Killer (32X) (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Corpse Killer (32X)</name>
		<desc>CORPSE KILLER IS A FULL-MOTION VIDEO SHOOT-'EM UP.  YOU PLAY AS AN ELITE SPECIAL FORCES SOLDIER, WHO PARACHUTES ONTO A REMOTE TROPICAL ISLAND.  IT SEEMS THE EVIL GENIUS DR. HELLMAN HAS FOUND A WAY TO RAISE THE DEAD, AND CREATED AN ISLAND OF ZOMBIES.  IT'S UP TO YOU TO SHOOT YOUR WAY THROUGH THE UNDEAD HORDES AND STOP DR. HELLMAN.

THE GAME IS PLAYED FROM A FIRST-PERSON PERSPECTIVE.  VARIOUS ZOMBIES POP UP IN FRONT OF A VIDEO BACKGROUND, AND YOU SHOOT THEM DOWN BY MOVING A CURSOR ON SCREEN OR BY USING A LIGHT GUN.  THE SATURN VERSION HAS A FEW DIFFERENT FEATURES INCLUDING EXTRA POWER-UPS AS WELL AS ADDED FOOTAGE OF ENEMIES.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9AF32AE2</hash>
		<image>./images/Corpse Killer (32X) (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Corpse Killer (32X) (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Corpse Killer (32X) (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Corpse Killer (32X) (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12775" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Corpse Killer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Corpse Killer</name>
		<desc>CORPSE KILLER IS A FULL-MOTION VIDEO SHOOT-'EM UP.  YOU PLAY AS AN ELITE SPECIAL FORCES SOLDIER, WHO PARACHUTES ONTO A REMOTE TROPICAL ISLAND.  IT SEEMS THE EVIL GENIUS DR. HELLMAN HAS FOUND A WAY TO RAISE THE DEAD, AND CREATED AN ISLAND OF ZOMBIES.  IT'S UP TO YOU TO SHOOT YOUR WAY THROUGH THE UNDEAD HORDES AND STOP DR. HELLMAN.

THE GAME IS PLAYED FROM A FIRST-PERSON PERSPECTIVE.  VARIOUS ZOMBIES POP UP IN FRONT OF A VIDEO BACKGROUND, AND YOU SHOOT THEM DOWN BY MOVING A CURSOR ON SCREEN OR BY USING A LIGHT GUN.  THE SATURN VERSION HAS A FEW DIFFERENT FEATURES INCLUDING EXTRA POWER-UPS AS WELL AS ADDED FOOTAGE OF ENEMIES.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C48BA887</hash>
		<image>./images/Corpse Killer (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Corpse Killer (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Corpse Killer (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Corpse Killer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97349" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crime Patrol (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crime Patrol</name>
		<desc>THIS MULTI-LEVEL LIVE ACTION THRILLER CHALLENGES THE PLAYER TO PROGRESS THROUGH POLICE RANKS BATTLING A VARIETY OF CRIMINAL ELEMENTS. AS A ROOKIE, THE PLAYER TAKES ON GANG MEMBERS, ARMED ROBBERS AND OTHER STREET CRIMINALS. PROMOTION TO DETECTIVE WILL MEAN WORKING UNDERCOVER AGAINST DRUG DEALERS AND CAR THIEF RINGS. BE PREPARED TO CONFRONT BANK ROBBERS AND TERRORISTS ONCE YOU'RE SELECTED FOR SWAT TEAM ASSIGNMENT. ONLY THE BETTER PLAYER WILL BE ABLE TO REACH DELTA FORCE AND TANGLE WITH A CRIMINAL ELEMENT THREATENING NATIONAL SECURITY.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>American Laser Games</developer>
		<publisher>American Laser Games</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>448FD302</hash>
		<image>./images/Crime Patrol (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Crime Patrol (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Crime Patrol (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Crime Patrol (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12829" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dark Wizard (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dark Wizard</name>
		<desc>300 ANOS ATRÁS, O SUMO SACERDOTE DO REINO DE CHESHIRE TENTOU PERTURBAR O EQUILÍBRIO ENTRE O BEM E O MAL CONVOCANDO O DEUS DAS TREVAS ARLIMAN. SABRINA, DEUSA DA LUZ, SALVOU O REINO DANDO GRANDES PODERES A DOIS DOS LÍDERES DE CHESHIRE QUE DERROTARAM O SUMO SACERDOTE E AJUDARAM O GRANDE MAGO DO REI A PRENDER ARLIMAN EM UMA JÓIA MÁGICA. VELONESE, O APRENDIZ DE ALTO FEITICEIRO, RECEBEU A TAREFA DE PROTEGER O PRISIONEIRO ARLIMAN NA ILHA DE RAVEN. AO LONGO DOS ANOS, SUA RAIVA EM RELAÇÃO AO REINO CRESCEU E AGORA ELE ESTÁ COMANDANDO QUATRO GENERAIS PARA CONQUISTAR CHESHIRE ENQUANTO ELE ESTÁ TENTANDO LIBERTAR ARLIMAN. VOCÊ ASSUME O PAPEL DE UM DOS QUATRO PERSONAGENS PRINCIPAIS E DEVE RECONQUISTAR A TERRA QUE JÁ CAIU NAS MÃOS DE VELONESE, ENCONTRAR UMA MANEIRA DE DERROTÁ-LO E EVITAR A RESSURREIÇÃO DE ARLIMAN. O JOGO POSSUI COMBATE TÁTICO POR TURNOS. DURANTE ESTAS BATALHAS SEU PERSONAGEM PRINCIPAL - DESDE QUE ELE ESTEJA EM UM CAMPO DE CASTELO - PODE INVOCAR VÁRIOS MONSTROS OU CONTRATAR TROPAS HUMANAS. MONSTROS PRECISAM DE PONTOS MÁGICOS PARA SEREM INVOCADOS, ENQUANTO HUMANOS PRECISAM SER PAGOS COM DINHEIRO DOS IMPOSTOS. DEPENDENDO DO PERSONAGEM QUE VOCÊ ESCOLHEU, SUA QUANTIDADE DE DINHEIRO E IMPOSTOS VARIA, ASSIM COMO OS TIPOS DE MONSTROS QUE VOCÊ PODERÁ CONVOCAR. SUAS UNIDADES TAMBÉM PODEM ENTRAR EM CIDADES DURANTE BATALHAS, COMPRAR ARMAS E ITENS, OUVIR AS ÚLTIMAS FOFOCAS E TALVEZ ATÉ DESCOBRIR UMA MISSÃO PARALELA. ENTRE AS BATALHAS, VOCÊ PODE EQUIPAR SUAS TROPAS, ENVIAR GRUPOS DE BUSCA E ALOCAR TROPAS PARA DIFERENTES CIDADES, POIS ELAS PODEM SER RECONQUISTADAS PELO INIMIGO.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>17D34419</hash>
		<image>./images/Dark Wizard (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dark Wizard (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dark Wizard (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dark Wizard (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12729" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Demolition Man (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Demolition Man</name>
		<desc>DEMOLITION MAN IS A GAME BASED ON THE 1993 MOVIE BY THE SAME NAME. AS WITH THE MOVIE, THE GAME TAKES PLACE IN A DYSTOPIAN LOS ANGELES, IN 1996. JOHN SPARTAN IS THE COUNTRY´S MOST FEARSOME COP AND HUNTS HIS NEMESIS, SIMON PHOENIX. HOWEVER IN DOING SO, HE KILLS SEVERAL INNOCENT CIVILIANS AND BOTH CHARACTERS ARE SENTENCED TO CRYOSTASIS REHABILITATION WHERE THEY WILL BE BRAINWASHED FOR 30 YEARS. HOWEVER THE BRAINWASHING DOES NOT GO AS PLANNED AND UPON WAKING UP, PHOENIX GOES ON A NEW CRIME SPREE. HOWEVER IN 30 YEARS THE WORLD HAS ALSO CHANGED AND LOS ANGELES HAS BECOME SAN ANGELES, A UTOPIAN AND VIOLENCE-FREE SOCIETY. AS A REMNANT OF A MORE VIOLENT PAST, POLICE OFFICER JOHN SPARTAN IS ONCE AGAIN SENT TO CAPTURE PHOENIX.

DEMOLITION MAN IS A FAST-PACED PLATFORM GAME, WITH SOME LEVELS TAKING PLACE IN AN OVERHEAD PERSPECTIVE (SIMILAR TO SMASH TV). AS JOHN SPARTAN, THE PLAYER WILL SPEND MOST OF HIS TIME SHOOTING ENDLESS WAVES OF "CRYOCONS" RELEASED UPON THE ANTISEPTIC WORLD OF THE FUTURE. THE STANDARD WEAPON CAN BE UPGRADED WITH A SHOTGUN AND MAGNUM, BOTH WITH LIMITED AMMO. ADDITIONALLY, VARIOUS TYPES OF GRENADES CAN BE COLLECTED, WHICH ARE THROWN INDEPENDENTLY OF THE FIREARM. SIMON PHOENIX APPEARS AS A BOSS CHARACTER AT THE END OF EVERY LEVEL THAT IS DIRECTLY TIED IN WITH THE MOVIE.

THE SEGA CD VERSION OF THE GAME RETAINS IDENTICAL LEVELS AND GAMEPLAY, BUT ADDS DIGITIZED CLIPS FROM THE FILM TO INTRODUCE LEVELS AND ADVANCE THE PLOT.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alexandria, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3D9C929F</hash>
		<image>./images/Demolition Man (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Demolition Man (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Demolition Man (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Demolition Man (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12827" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Double Switch (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Double Switch</name>
		<desc>DOUBLE SWITCH IS ONE OF DIGITAL PICTURES' MANY FULL-MOTION VIDEO GAMES FROM THE MID 90S.  IN THIS "CINEMATIC MYSTERY" YOU MUST WATCH YOUR SERVEILANCE CAMERAS IN ORDER TO TRAP INTRUDERS IN THE EDWARD ARMS MANSION.

DOUBLE SWITCH STARS COREY HAIM AND DEBORAH HARRY, AND FEATURES A MUSICAL SCORE BY THOMAS DOLBY.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>EE33DE8F</hash>
		<image>./images/Double Switch (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Double Switch (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Double Switch (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Double Switch (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58733" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Dracula Unleashed (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>DRACULA UNLEASHED IS AN INTERACTIVE MOVIE IN THE SAME VEIN AS SHERLOCK HOLMES: CONSULTING DETECTIVE. BASICALLY, YOU CAN CHOOSE FROM SEVERAL LOCATIONS TO GO TO, AND AT EACH LOCATION YOU ARE SHOWN DIFFERENT EVENTS THROUGH LIVE-ACTION VIDEO CLIPS. CLUES IN THE VIDEOS WILL POINT YOU TO WHERE YOU SHOULD GO NEXT. YOU ALSO HAVE AN "INVENTORY" WHICH YOU CAN USE TO AFFECT THE OUTCOME OF CERTAIN CLIPS (FOR EXAMPLE, IF YOU ENTER AN ASYLUM WITH THE BLACKJACK YOU'LL BE ABLE TO DEFEND YOURSELF AGAINST ANY ESCAPED INMATES, BUT IF YOU DON'T BRING THE BLACKJACK WITH YOU YOU'LL BE KILLED). TIME IS CONSTANTLY MOVING AND NEW EVENTS WILL POP UP AT DIFFERENT TIMES OF THE DAY.

IN DRACULA UNLEASHED IT IS THE YEAR 1899, TEN YEARS AFTER THE DESTRUCTION OF COUNT DRACULA CHRONICLED IN BRAM STOKER'S NOVEL. YOU TAKE THE ROLE OF ALEXANDER MORRIS, THE YOUNGER BROTHER OF TEXAN QUINCEY MORRIS WHO DIED DEFEATING DRACULA. ALEXANDER HAS COME TO LONDON TO INVESTIGATE THE CIRCUMSTANCES OF HIS BROTHER'S DEATH, BUT BECAME SIDETRACKED WHEN HE FELL IN LOVE WITH AND PROPOSED TO A LOCAL GIRL NAMED ANNISETTE.

NOW, THE DAWN OF A NEW MILLENNIUM APPROACHES AND AN EVIL FORCE IS STALKING THE STREETS OF LONDON, DRAINING VICTIMS OF THEIR BLOOD AND TRANSFORMING INNOCENT WOMEN INTO BLOODTHIRSTY VAMPIRESSES. WITH THE AIDE OF YOUR BROTHER'S OLD FRIENDS, THE SURVIVORS OF DRACULA'S EVIL, YOU MUST UNCOVER THE IDENTITY OF THIS NEW VAMPIRE AND PREVENT HIM FROM TRANSFORMING ANNISETTE INTO HIS QUEEN OF THE NIGHT. DO NOT FAIL HER, OR SHE WILL PERSONALLY RIP YOUR THROAT OUT.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C00C3684</hash>
		<image>./images/Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58733" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Dracula Unleashed (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>DRACULA UNLEASHED IS AN INTERACTIVE MOVIE IN THE SAME VEIN AS SHERLOCK HOLMES: CONSULTING DETECTIVE. BASICALLY, YOU CAN CHOOSE FROM SEVERAL LOCATIONS TO GO TO, AND AT EACH LOCATION YOU ARE SHOWN DIFFERENT EVENTS THROUGH LIVE-ACTION VIDEO CLIPS. CLUES IN THE VIDEOS WILL POINT YOU TO WHERE YOU SHOULD GO NEXT. YOU ALSO HAVE AN "INVENTORY" WHICH YOU CAN USE TO AFFECT THE OUTCOME OF CERTAIN CLIPS (FOR EXAMPLE, IF YOU ENTER AN ASYLUM WITH THE BLACKJACK YOU'LL BE ABLE TO DEFEND YOURSELF AGAINST ANY ESCAPED INMATES, BUT IF YOU DON'T BRING THE BLACKJACK WITH YOU YOU'LL BE KILLED). TIME IS CONSTANTLY MOVING AND NEW EVENTS WILL POP UP AT DIFFERENT TIMES OF THE DAY.

IN DRACULA UNLEASHED IT IS THE YEAR 1899, TEN YEARS AFTER THE DESTRUCTION OF COUNT DRACULA CHRONICLED IN BRAM STOKER'S NOVEL. YOU TAKE THE ROLE OF ALEXANDER MORRIS, THE YOUNGER BROTHER OF TEXAN QUINCEY MORRIS WHO DIED DEFEATING DRACULA. ALEXANDER HAS COME TO LONDON TO INVESTIGATE THE CIRCUMSTANCES OF HIS BROTHER'S DEATH, BUT BECAME SIDETRACKED WHEN HE FELL IN LOVE WITH AND PROPOSED TO A LOCAL GIRL NAMED ANNISETTE.

NOW, THE DAWN OF A NEW MILLENNIUM APPROACHES AND AN EVIL FORCE IS STALKING THE STREETS OF LONDON, DRAINING VICTIMS OF THEIR BLOOD AND TRANSFORMING INNOCENT WOMEN INTO BLOODTHIRSTY VAMPIRESSES. WITH THE AIDE OF YOUR BROTHER'S OLD FRIENDS, THE SURVIVORS OF DRACULA'S EVIL, YOU MUST UNCOVER THE IDENTITY OF THIS NEW VAMPIRE AND PREVENT HIM FROM TRANSFORMING ANNISETTE INTO HIS QUEEN OF THE NIGHT. DO NOT FAIL HER, OR SHE WILL PERSONALLY RIP YOUR THROAT OUT.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DA13B95D</hash>
		<image>./images/Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dracula Unleashed (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12719" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon's Lair (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon's Lair</name>
		<desc>A CONVERSION OF THE 1983 DON BLUTH COIN OP CARTOON GAME.  PLAYERS CONTROL DIRK THE DARING AS HE STRUGGLES HIS WAY THROUGH A DUNGEON TO FIGHT SINGE, THE DRAGON, AND RESCUE THE BEAUTIFUL PRINCESS DAPHNE.  WITH LIMITED MOVEMENT ALLOWED, THE GAME'S MAIN EMPHASIS IS ON ITS HEART-STOPPING GRAPHICS.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ReadySoft Incorporated</developer>
		<publisher>ReadySoft Incorporated</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Dragon's Lair (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dragon's Lair (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dragon's Lair (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon's Lair (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12706" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dune (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dune</name>
		<desc>BASED ON THE LEGENDARY FRANK HERBERT NOVEL OF THE SAME NAME AND VISUALLY INSPIRED BY THE 1984 DAVID LYNCH MOVIE, DUNE IS A STRATEGY-ADVENTURE HYBRID WHERE THE PLAYER TAKES THE ROLE OF YOUNG PAUL ATREIDES, THE SON OF DUKE LETO. THE EMPEROR SHADDAM CORRINO IV HAS GIVEN THE ATREIDES HOUSE THE RIGHTS TO MANAGE THE EXTRACTION OF THE MOST PRECIOUS SUBSTANCE IN THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE - THE MELANGE, COMMONLY KNOWN AS SPICE IN THE DESOLATE DESERT PLANET ARRAKIS (DUNE), THE ONLY PLACE IN THE UNIVERSE CAPABLE OF PRODUCING THE SUBSTANCE. WHILE EVERYTHING INDICATES THE OFFER IS A TRAP ORCHESTRATED BY THEIR ENEMIES THE HARKONNEN, THE ATREIDES FAMILY AGREES ON MOVING, AS HE WHO CONTROLS THE SPICE, CONTROLS THE UNIVERSE.

THE PLAYER ARRIVES IN ARRAKIS WITH THE MISSION OF CONTACTING AND CONVINCING THE FREMEN TRIBES RESIDING IN SIETCHES (DESERT SETTLEMENTS) NEAR THE ATREIDES PALACE TO HARVEST THE SPICE. HARVESTING IS THE MOST IMPORTANT PART OF THE GAME, REQUIRED TO PURCHASE EQUIPMENT FROM THE SMUGGLERS AND APPEASE THE EMPEROR. TO SPEED UP THE PROCESS OF HARVESTING, THE PLAYER CAN EQUIP THE TRIBES WITH HARVESTERS TO INCREASE PRODUCTION AND ORNIS TO PROTECT THEM FROM THE GIGANTIC PROTECTORS OF THE PLANET: SHAI-HULUD - THE SANDWORMS. 

HOWEVER, THE SPICE DOESN'T LAST FOREVER AND NEW SIETCHES MUST BE PROSPECTED BEFORE HAVING A MINING CREW ASSIGNED, BUT THE PLAYER CANNOT RUN SOUTHWARDS FOREVER, AS THE HARKONNEN ENEMY CONTROLS THE NORTH OF THE PLANET, DANGEROUSLY CLOSE TO THE ATREIDES PALACE. SOON AFTER THE INITIAL BATCHES ARE SENT TO THE EMPEROR, THE PLAYER WILL HAVE TO ACTIVELY DEAL WITH THE HARKONNEN, WHO WILL TRY TO TAKE CONTROL OF PLAYER SIETCHES. FOR THOSE, FREMEN TRIBES CAN BE ASSIGNED TO MILITARY TRAINING WITH GURNEY HALLECK, BUT BEFORE DOING SUCH WORK PAUL MUST HAVE A CERTAIN REPUTATION, GAINED BY THE CONTROL OF ARRAKIS.

AS THE GAME ADVANCES, THE PLAYER WILL UNTAP PAUL'S LATENT POWERS, AS WELL AS MEETING OTHER CHARACTERS FROM THE DUNE UNIVERSE, SUCH AS DUKE LETO, JESSICA, THUFIR HAWAT, DUNCAN IDAHO, HARAH, CHANI, STILGAR AND LIET KYNES, THE MASTERMIND BEHIND THE ECOLOGICAL PLANS ON DUNE - THE ULTIMATE GOAL.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Avalon Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Cryo Interactive</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8B98DAFD</hash>
		<image>./images/Dune (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dune (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dune (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dune (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12724" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dungeon Explorer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dungeon Explorer</name>
		<desc>A DEUSA DA AMBIÇÃO ESTÁ TRANCADA NOS CALABOUÇOS DA TORRE DARKLING. DIZ A LENDA QUE ELA CONCEDERÁ QUALQUER DESEJO A QUEM A LIBERTAR. UM GRUPO DE HERÓIS PRESOS EM OUTRO MUNDO TEM A MISSÃO DE RESGATAR A CRIATURA DIVINA E USAR SEUS PODERES PARA VOLTAREM PARA SEU MUNDO.

DUNGEON EXPLORER É UM CLONE DO GAUNTLET. COMO ESSE JOGO CLÁSSICO, É UM HÍBRIDO ENTRE UM SHOOTER ARCADE E UM RPG TRADICIONAL. SUPORTA ATÉ 4 JOGADORES COM UMA ESCOLHA DE 6 PERSONAGENS / CLASSES DIFERENTES: MONGE, CAVALEIRO, ELFO, MAGO, FERA E NINJA. NO LADO DIREITO DA TELA HÁ UMA BARRA COM OS SEGUINTES PONTOS: EXPERIÊNCIA, ESTATÍSTICAS E EQUIPAMENTOS. O BOTÃO C DISPARA A ARMA EQUIPADA E O BOTÃO B USA A HABILIDADE ESPECIAL DO PERSONAGEM.

O JOGO COMEÇA NA ÁREA EM TORNO DE UM PONTO DE SALVAGUARDA. ESTA ÁREA FUNCIONA COMO UM HUB CENTRAL PARA ACESSAR TODAS AS 6 MASMORRAS. SE UM PERSONAGEM SAIR, O CONTADOR DE ALIMENTOS COMEÇARÁ A DIMINUIR. SE CHEGAR A ZERO, OS PONTOS DE VIDA COMEÇAM A DIMINUIR ATÉ QUE O PERSONAGEM MORRA. A COMIDA PODE SER ENCONTRADA COMO POÇÕES OU POTES AO REDOR DOS LABIRINTOS. RETORNANDO O PERSONAGEM PARA A ÁREA DO PONTO DE SALVAMENTO E TODAS AS CONDIÇÕES (COMO ENVENENAMENTO E CONFUSÃO). AO NORTE HÁ DOIS EDIFÍCIOS, UMA LOJA DE ARMAS E UMA TAVERNA. O OURO COLETADO NO JOGO ESTÁ NOS UPGRADES DE EQUIPAMENTOS NA LOJA DE ARMAS. A TAVERNA (CHAMADA JOJO'S BAR) PERMITE AO JOGADOR TROCAR DE PERSONAGEM.

OS PERSONAGENS TRAZEM OS PONTOS DE EXPERIÊNCIA NECESSÁRIOS. UMA VEZ QUE O CHEFE DA MASMORRA É DERROTADO, A MASMORRA É BLOQUEADA E O JOGADOR NÃO PODE RETORNAR A ELA. O JOGO TEM QUATRO SLOTS DE SALVAMENTO, CADA UM PARA UM JOGO INDIVIDUAL.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>7F6963C8</hash>
		<image>./images/Dungeon Explorer (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dungeon Explorer (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dungeon Explorer (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dungeon Explorer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dungeon Master 2 - Skullkeep (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dungeon Master 2 - Skullkeep (USA)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Dungeon Master 2 - Skullkeep (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Dungeon Master 2 - Skullkeep (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Dungeon Master 2 - Skullkeep (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dungeon Master 2 - Skullkeep (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12711" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Earthworm Jim - Special Edition (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Earthworm Jim: Special Edition</name>
		<desc>ESTA EDIÇÃO ESPECIAL INCLUI: UM SISTEMA DE SENHA, UM NOVO MUNDO E NOVAS ÁREAS OCULTAS, UMA NOVA ARMA, MAIS DE 1000 QUADROS ADICIONAIS DE ANIMAÇÃO. TODA A NOVA TRILHA SONORA COM QUALIDADE DE CD, FINAIS TOTALMENTE NOVOS EM DOIS DOS MUNDOS, TODAS AS IDÉIAS EXTRAS E RECURSOS ESPECIAIS QUE A SHINY NÃO CONSEGUIU ENCAIXAR NO CARTUCHO ESTÃO NESTA EDIÇÃO.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shiny Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Earthworm Jim - Special Edition (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Earthworm Jim - Special Edition (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Earthworm Jim - Special Edition (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Earthworm Jim - Special Edition (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12718" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ecco the Dolphin (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ecco the Dolphin</name>
		<desc>TRAVEL THROUGH TIME ALONG WITH ECCO THE DOLPHIN, IN THE ONLY GAME THAT COULD CALL ITSELF A "DOLPHIN SIMULATOR". INDEED, YOU CAN DO PRETTY MUCH EVERYTHING A TYPICAL DOLPHIN DOES, INCLUDING EATING FISH, SURFACING IN ORDER TO BREATHE, USING YOUR BIOLOGICAL SONAR AND OF COURSE, JUMPING OUT OF THE WATER TO AMAZE YOUR FRIENDS.

THE STORYLINE IS ACTUALLY DEEPER THAT ONE MAY THINK BY LOOKING AT THE BOX ILLUSTRATION. AS ECCO, YOU ARE THE ONLY DOLPHIN WHO MANAGED TO ESCAPE FROM A GIANT WHIRLPOOL WHICH SUCKED DOWN YOUR ENTIRE POD. THE FIVE SHINING STARS ON YOUR FOREHEAD SHOW THAT YOU ARE THE CHOSEN ONE TO SAVE THEM. BUT THAT TASK WILL BE NOT BE AN EASY ONE, AS YOU WILL HAVE TO TRAVEL THROUGH TIME AND SPACE WITH THE ATLANTEAN TIME MACHINE, AND MEET THE MYSTICAL ASTERITE IN ORDER TO DEFEAT THE VORTEX QUEEN.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Novotrade International</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Ecco the Dolphin (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ecco the Dolphin (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ecco the Dolphin (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ecco the Dolphin (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12754" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ecco - The Tides of Time (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ecco: The Tides of Time</name>
		<desc>A CONTINUAÇÃO DE ECCO THE DOLPHIN, NO QUAL A ECCO DESTRUIU COM SUCESSO O VORTEX. INFELIZMENTE, ACONTECE QUE A RAINHA VORTEX A SEGUIU ATÉ A TERRA E ACABOU DESTRUINDO O ASTERITA. TODOS OS OCEANOS DO MUNDO ESTÃO AMEAÇADOS E, NA VERDADE, JÁ ESTÃO CONDENADOS. A FIM DE RESTAURAR O ASTERITA E FINALMENTE DERROTAR A RAINHA VORTEX, ECCO TERÁ QUE ENFRENTAR MAIS UMA VEZ AS MARÉS DO TEMPO, QUE SE DIVIDIRAM EM DOIS FUTUROS POSSÍVEIS, O REGULAR E O ESCURO DOMINADO PELA RAINHA VORTEX. ECCO: THE TIDES OF TIME APRESENTA GRÁFICOS AINDA MELHORES DO QUE O SEU ANTECESSOR E INTRODUZ UM NOVO MODO DE JOGO NO QUAL A CÂMERA SEGUE O GOLFINHO POR TRÁS, EM VEZ DE PELO LADO.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Novotrade International</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Ecco - The Tides of Time (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ecco - The Tides of Time (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ecco - The Tides of Time (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ecco - The Tides of Time (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12839" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ESPN Baseball Tonight (USA).chd</path>
		<name>ESPN Baseball Tonight</name>
		<desc>ESPN BASEBALL TONIGHT IS A BASEBALL GAME WITH BOTH EXHIBITION AND PLAYOFF MODES. OTHER MODES INCLUDED ARE BOTH PRACTICE (BOTH PITCHING AND BATTING) AND HOME RUN DERBY MODES. THE GAME CONTAINS 28 REAL MLB TEAMS BUT NO ACTUAL PLAYERS. GAMEPLAY OPTIONS INCLUDE BEING ABLE TO TURN ERRORS ON OR OFF AND TO HAVE ASSISTED FIELDING ON OR OFF.

GAMEPLAY HAS THE BEHIND THE BATTER VIEWPOINT, WHETHER PITCHING OR BATTING. ONE THING TO NOTE WHEN FIELDING, THE PLAYER MUST MANUALLY THROW THE BALL BACK TO THE PITCHER FOR THE GAME TO CONTINUE.

THE SEGA CD VERSION IS AN UPDATE WHICH INCLUDES THE OPTION FOR AN 162 GAME SEASON AND HAS OVER 10 MINUTES OF VIDEO HIGHLIGHTS.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Stormfront Studios</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>10F63032</hash>
		<image>./images/ESPN Baseball Tonight (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/ESPN Baseball Tonight (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/ESPN Baseball Tonight (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ESPN Baseball Tonight (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12840" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ESPN National Hockey Night (USA).chd</path>
		<name>ESPN National Hockey Night</name>
		<desc>ESPN NATIONAL HOCKEY NIGHT WAS ONE OF THE MANY HOCKEY GAMES RELEASED BACK IN THE DAY.  THIS ONE FEATURED ALL THE NHL TEAMS FOR ITS TIME, BUT LACKED AN OFFICIAL PLAYERS LICENSE.

IT HAD FOUR GAME MODES TO CHOOSE FROM: EXHIBITION, CHALLENGE, PLAYOFF, AND SEASON.  THE GAME ALSO FEATURES BOTH A HORIZONTAL AND VERTICAL PERSPECTIVE OF THE ICE, BATTERY BACKUP TO SAVE PROGRESS AND ALSO FEATURED THE VOICE OF BILL CLEMENT FOR PLAY-BY-PLAY COMMENTARY.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Stormfront Studios</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>900BB7DE</hash>
		<image>./images/ESPN National Hockey Night (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/ESPN National Hockey Night (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/ESPN National Hockey Night (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ESPN National Hockey Night (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12765" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ESPN NBA Hangtime '95 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>ESPN NBA Hangtime '95</name>
		<desc>NBA HANGTIME '95 TAKES IT TO THE HOOP WITH THE ULTIMATE IN 2-ON-2 HALF-COURT ACTION. CHOOSE FROM 81 OF THE HOTTEST PLAYERS IN THE NBA FROM ALL 27 TEAMS. SPECIAL BUTTON COMBOS LET YOU UNLEASH AWESOME PLAYER MOVES - TWO HANDED POWER DUNKS BY HAKEEM OLAJUWON, REVERSE DUNKS BY CHRIS WEBBER, SPIN MOVES BY SCOTTIE PIPPEN AND MORE! THEN FOR SOMETHING COMPLETELY DIFFERENT, PLAY ESPN 2-ON-2 WORLD TOUR MODE WITH STREETBALL PLAYERS FROM AROUND THE WORLD. NBA HANGTIME '95, EVERYTHING ELSE IS JUST PRACTICE.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>SCEE Studio Cambridge</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>5A4E787C</hash>
		<image>./images/ESPN NBA Hangtime '95 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/ESPN NBA Hangtime '95 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/ESPN NBA Hangtime '95 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ESPN NBA Hangtime '95 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97353" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ESPN Sunday Night NFL (USA).chd</path>
		<name>ESPN Sunday Night NFL</name>
		<desc>ESPN SUNDAY NIGHT NFL WAS ONE OF THE MANY FOOTBALL GAMES RELEASED BACK IN THE DAY. IT FEATURES ALL 28 OFFICIAL NFL TEAMS AND THEIR RESPECTIVE LOGOS, BUT DOESN'T FEATURE A LICENSE FROM THE NFLPA, SO THERE ARE NO ACTUAL PLAYERS NAMES IN THE GAME.

THERE ARE FOUR DIFFERENT GAME MODES TO CHOOSE FROM: PLAYOFFS, SINGLE GAME, SEASON AND ANOTHER SEASON MODE THAT LETS THE PLAYER ACT OUT THE 1994 NFL SEASON SCHEDULE.  IT ALSO HAD VARIABLE WEATHER CONDITIONS THAT THE PLAYERS ON THE FIELD WOULD REACT TO AND A BATTERY BACK-UP TO SAVE GAMES.  IT ALSO FEATURED CHRIS BERMAN, WHO NOT ONLY GRACED THE FRONT COVER BUT ALSO GIVES COMMENTARY AS WELL.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ringler Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>C967310C</hash>
		<image>./images/ESPN Sunday Night NFL (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/ESPN Sunday Night NFL (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/ESPN Sunday Night NFL (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ESPN Sunday Night NFL (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12735" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Eternal Champions - Challenge from the Dark Side (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Eternal Champions: Challenge from the Dark Side</name>
		<desc>LIKE THE PREQUEL THE GAME FOLLOWS THE SAME PATTERN EXCEPT WITH WHAT HAPPENS NEXT. THE FOLLOWING IS AN EXACT DUPLICATION OF THE STORYLINE VIEWED IN THE "ACCESS INFO" OPTION ON THE GAME'S MAIN MENU:</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Deep Water</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>B86B6DDC</hash>
		<image>./images/Eternal Champions - Challenge from the Dark Side (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Eternal Champions - Challenge from the Dark Side (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Eternal Champions - Challenge from the Dark Side (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Eternal Champions - Challenge from the Dark Side (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12739" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Eye of the Beholder (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Eye of the Beholder</name>
		<desc>SOMETHING EVIL IS LURKING BELOW THE CITY OF WATERDEEP. THE LORDS OF WATERDEEP SUMMON A GROUP OF HEROES TO INVESTIGATE, BUT SOMEONE OR SOMETHING HAS BEEN WATCHING THE PROCEEDINGS. AFTER THE HEROES ENTER THE SEWERS, THE CEILING COLLAPSES BEHIND THEM. THE ONLY WAY OUT IS THE WAY DOWN, INTO A DUNGEON FILLED WITH MONSTERS, TRAPS AND PUZZLES.

EYE OF THE BEHOLDER IS A DUNGEON CRAWLER RPG WITH A FIRST-PERSON PERSPECTIVE BASED ON THE 2ND EDITION AD&amp;D RULES. THE STARTING PARTY CONSISTS OF FOUR CHARACTERS AND UP TO TWO NPCS CAN JOIN LATER. COMBAT AND MAGIC HAPPEN IN REAL TIME. FIGHT OVER A DOZEN DIFFERENT MONSTER VARIETIES AND CAST OVER 40 SPELLS. A POINT-AND-CLICK INTERFACE MAKES EXPLORING, FIGHTING, SPELLCASTING AND HANDLING OBJECTS EASY.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SSI</developer>
		<publisher>Westwood Studios</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>38E20701</hash>
		<image>./images/Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Eye of the Beholder (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Eye of the Beholder (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Eye of the Beholder (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Eye of the Beholder (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12766" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Fahrenheit (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>FAHRENHEIT IS AN INTERACTIVE MOVIE THAT PUTS PLAYERS INTO THE FLAME-RESISTANT SUIT OF A FIREFIGHTER. YOU ARE THE NEW GUY IN THE FIREHOUSE.  LAST WEEK, YOU SAVED THREE LIVES. BUT NOW, YOU'RE ON A NEW SQUAD, AND HAVE TO PROVE YOURSELF TO THEM.

LIKE MOST INTERACTIVE MOVIES, FAHRENHEIT IS PLAYED ENTIRELY WHILE WATCHING A DIGITIZED VIDEO. AT CERTAIN CRITICAL POINTS IN THE VIDEO, PLAYERS MUST PRESS CERTAIN DIRECTIONS ON THE CONTROL PAD OR ACTION BUTTONS IN ORDER TO PROGRESS IN THE GAME. FAHRENHEIT TAKES THIS A STEP FURTHER BY PROVIDING SEVERAL BUILDINGS IN WHICH THE PLAYER HAS THE ABILITY TO MOVE FROM ROOM TO ROOM IN IN A NON-LINEAR FASHION. AS PLAYERS MOVE FROM ROOM TO ROOM, THEY HAVE TO LOCATE VICTIMS AND NEUTRALIZE FIRE HAZARDS.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A4F0D330</hash>
		<image>./images/Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12766" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 2) (32X).chd</path>
		<name>Fahrenheit (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>FAHRENHEIT IS AN INTERACTIVE MOVIE THAT PUTS PLAYERS INTO THE FLAME-RESISTANT SUIT OF A FIREFIGHTER. YOU ARE THE NEW GUY IN THE FIREHOUSE.  LAST WEEK, YOU SAVED THREE LIVES. BUT NOW, YOU'RE ON A NEW SQUAD, AND HAVE TO PROVE YOURSELF TO THEM.

LIKE MOST INTERACTIVE MOVIES, FAHRENHEIT IS PLAYED ENTIRELY WHILE WATCHING A DIGITIZED VIDEO. AT CERTAIN CRITICAL POINTS IN THE VIDEO, PLAYERS MUST PRESS CERTAIN DIRECTIONS ON THE CONTROL PAD OR ACTION BUTTONS IN ORDER TO PROGRESS IN THE GAME. FAHRENHEIT TAKES THIS A STEP FURTHER BY PROVIDING SEVERAL BUILDINGS IN WHICH THE PLAYER HAS THE ABILITY TO MOVE FROM ROOM TO ROOM IN IN A NON-LINEAR FASHION. AS PLAYERS MOVE FROM ROOM TO ROOM, THEY HAVE TO LOCATE VICTIMS AND NEUTRALIZE FIRE HAZARDS.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>EE8FF01C</hash>
		<image>./images/Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 2) (32X).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 2) (32X).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 2) (32X).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fahrenheit (USA) (Disc 2) (32X).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12736" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fatal Fury Special (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury Special</name>
		<desc>FATAL FURY SPECIAL É UMA VERSÃO MELHORADA DO FATAL FURY 2. O OBJETIVO AINDA É VENCER O TORNEIO, DERROTANDO TODOS OS OUTROS LUTADORES, INCLUINDO O CHEFE FINAL WOLFGANG KRAUSER. FATAL FURY SPECIAL APRESENTA UMA SELEÇÃO RAZOAVELMENTE GRANDE DE LUTADORES QUE INCLUI: OS OITO LUTADORES REGULARES E OS QUATRO CHEFES DE FATAL FURY 2 E TRÊS PERSONAGENS RETORNANDO DO PRIMEIRO FATAL FURY. OUTRAS MELHORIAS INCLUEM: UM NOVO MODO DE CONTAGEM REGRESSIVA (DERROTAR TANTOS ADVERSÁRIOS QUANTO POSSÍVEL EM 3 MINUTOS). ESQUEMA EXTRA DE CORES PARA CADA PERSONAGEM. NOVOS E MELHORADOS GRÁFICOS DE FUNDO. FATAL FURY SPECIAL AINDA APRESENTA O MOVIMENTO PSEUDO-3D, MARCA REGISTRADA DA SÉRIE AO LONGO DE DOIS PLANOS.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JVC</developer>
		<publisher>JVC</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>E9F1A85C</hash>
		<image>./images/Fatal Fury Special (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Fatal Fury Special (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Fatal Fury Special (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fatal Fury Special (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12748" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./FIFA International Soccer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>FIFA International Soccer</name>
		<desc>THE GAME THAT STARTED THE BEST-SELLING SERIES LICENSED BY FOOTBALL'S WORLD GOVERNING BODY, THIS FIRST INSTALLMENT IN THE LONG RUNNING SERIES USED A DIMETRIC (COLLOQUIALLY KNOWN AS "ISOMETRIC") VIEWPOINT, PREVIOUSLY UNUSUAL IN FOOTBALL GAMES BUT QUICKLY IMITATED BY SEVERAL TITLES. THE TELEVISUAL PRESENTATION, ONE OF THE UNIQUE POINTS OF THE EARLY EA SPORTS TITLES, WITH HOSTS INTRODUCING THE MATCHES, WAS ANOTHER THING MAKING THE GAME STAND OUT FROM A MARKET DOMINATED BY SENSIBLE SOCCER AND KICK OFF GAMES.

BASED ON INTERNATIONAL TEAMS (WITH FICTIONAL PLAYER NAMES), THEIR ABILITIES IN EACH SKILL AREA RATED OUT OF 10 TO GIVE THE PLAYER AN OVERALL IMPRESSION OF HOW GOOD THEY ARE. THE OPTIONS AVAILABLE FOLLOW THE STANDARD SET: FOULS AND OFFSIDES CAN BE TOGGLED ON AND OFF, THE MATCH LENGTH CAN BE SET, AND IF THE TIMER OPERATES  CONTINUOUSLY, OR ONLY WHILE THE BALL IS IN PLAY. GAMEPLAY PRIVILEGES QUICK RUNS, SHORT PASSES AND BLISTERING SHOTS OUTSIDE THE PENALTY BOX, AND SET PIECES ARE CONTROLLED BY MOVING A BOX INTO THE TARGET AREA FOR THE BALL, AND THEN PASSED, LOBBED OR KICKED DIRECTLY. ON THE TACTICAL SIDE, FORMATIONS CAN BE SELECTED, WITH 5 DIFFERENT STRATEGIES ALSO AVAILABLE (ALTHOUGH NOT ALL OF THESE COMBINATIONS MAKE SENSE) AS CAN THE TEAM COVERAGE - THE AREAS WHICH DEFENDERS, MIDFIELDERS AND STRIKERS COVER.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Extended Play Productions</developer>
		<publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>EE57AAF3</hash>
		<image>./images/FIFA International Soccer (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/FIFA International Soccer (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/FIFA International Soccer (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/FIFA International Soccer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12708" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fight CD (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fight CD</name>
		<desc>TUDO COMEÇA NA CIDADE DE METRO CITY, UMA CIDADE QUE É DOMINADA HÁ VÁRIOS ANOS PELO CRIME E VIOLÊNCIA. O RECÉM-ELEITO PREFEITO MIKE HAGGAR RESOLVEU COLOCAR UM PONTO FINAL NESSA VIOLÊNCIA. COM ISSO ELE ACABOU MEXENDO COM A MAIS CRUEL GANGUE DA CIDADE, CHAMADA MAD GEAR, QUE AO SABER DOS PLANOS DE HAGGAR, RAPTA SUA FILHA JESSICA, PARA ASSIM PODER CHANTAGEÁ-LO. HAGGAR ENTÃO LARGA A BUROCRACIA DO ESCRITÓRIO, ARREGAÇA AS MANGAS (POR UM ACASO ELE É EX-CAMPEÃO DE LUTA-LIVRE) E VAI PARA AS RUAS ESPANCAR OS BANDIDOS E SALVAR A FILHA, COM A AJUDA DO NAMORADO DELA, CODY E O AMIGO GUY. AJUDE OS TRÊS VIGILANTES A SALVAREM JESSICA E ACABAR COM O TERRÍVEL GRUPO CRIMINOSO QUE A RAPTOU.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>69BBBEF6</hash>
		<image>./images/Final Fight CD (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Final Fight CD (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Final Fight CD (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Final Fight CD (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12710" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Flashback - The Quest for Identity (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Flashback: The Quest for Identity</name>
		<desc>A HISTÓRIA SE PASSA NO ANO DE 2142 E GIRA EM TORNO DE CONRAD B. HART, UM AGENTE DA GALÁXIA BUREAU, QUE DESCOBRIU UMA CONSPIRAÇÃO DE ALIENÍGENAS INFILTRADOS NA NOSSA SOCIEDADE PARA DOMINAR A TERRA. A INTRODUÇÃO DO GAME MOSTRA CONRAD FUGINDO EM UMA MOTO ESPACIAL, PERSEGUIDO POR UMA NAVE QUE O DERRUBA NUMA SELVA (NA LUA DE JÚPITER, TITÃ). AO ACORDAR, ELE PERCEBE QUE PERDEU A SUA MEMÓRIA, MAS GRAÇAS A UMA GRAVAÇÃO DE SI MESMO NUM HOLOCUBE, ELE SABE QUE DEVE IR PARA NOVA WASHINGTON (TAMBÉM EM TITÃ) ENCONTRAR O SEU AMIGO IAN PARA RESTAURAR SUA MEMÓRIA, E ASSIM SALVAR O MUNDO. ESTE É APENAS O INÍCIO DE UMA TRAMA ENVOLVENTE, RECHEADA DE AÇÃO, SUSPENSE E ESPIONAGEM. A VERSÃO DE SEGA CD CONTA COM ALGUNS QUADROS DE ANIMAÇÃO A MAIS, TEVE AS CUTSCENES REFEITAS EM ANIMAÇÕES FMV PRÉ-RENDERIZADAS, DIÁLOGOS DUBLADOS E UMA EXCELENTE TRILHA SONORA EXCLUSIVA, COM QUALIDADE DE CD.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
		<publisher>Delphine Software International</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>07C6C984</hash>
		<image>./images/Flashback - The Quest for Identity (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Flashback - The Quest for Identity (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Flashback - The Quest for Identity (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Flashback - The Quest for Identity (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12725" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Flink (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Flink</name>
		<desc>THE MISADVENTURES OF FLINK É UM JOGO DE PLATAFORMA AMBIENTADO NO MUNDO DE FANTASIA. O MAGO MALIGNO WICKED WAINWRIGHT CAPTUROU OS QUATRO ANCIÃOS E CABE A FLINK, UM APRENDIZ DE MAGO, LIBERTÁ-LOS E DERROTAR WICKED WAINWRIGHT. ALÉM DOS ELEMENTOS USUAIS DE PLATAFORMAS, O JOGO TEM UMA CARACTERÍSTICA ÚNICA: A HABILIDADE DE FLINK DE CRIAR FEITIÇOS. SEMPRE QUE O JOGO É PAUSADO, O FLINK PODE COMBINAR TRÊS INGREDIENTES PARA CRIAR UM FEITIÇO. INGREDIENTES PODEM SER COLETADOS AO LONGO DO JOGO. ELES SÃO GERALMENTE CARREGADOS POR UM CERTO TIPO DE INIMIGO OU ESCONDIDOS EM BAÚS DE TESOURO. EXISTEM DEZ MAGIAS DIFERENTES, AS "RECEITAS" QUE ESTÃO CONTIDAS EM PERGAMINHOS QUE SÃO DADAS A FLINK POR ANCIÃOS RESGATADOS OU ENCONTRADAS DENTRO DE CERTOS NÍVEIS. AS MAGIAS INCLUEM DIFERENTES FEITIÇOS DE ATAQUE (POR EXEMPLO, UM DEMÔNIO QUE ACOMPANHA FLINK E ATACA SEUS INIMIGOS), UM FEITIÇO DE ESCUDO, UM FEITIÇO DE ENCOLHIMENTO, UM FEITIÇO DE CRESCIMENTO RÁPIDO QUE PERMITE QUE CERTAS PLANTAS CRESÇAM PARA QUE FLINK ALCANCE NOVAS ÁREAS DE UM NÍVEL, CHAVES MÁGICAS QUE ABREM BAÚS DE TESOURO TRANCADOS E MUITO MAIS. FEITIÇOS DE CONJURAÇÃO USAM ENERGIA MÁGICA QUE PODE SER REPOSTA COLETANDO GARRAFAS MÁGICAS OU DERROTANDO INIMIGOS. SEMELHANTE AOS JOGOS DO SONIC, QUANDO FLINK É ATINGIDO, ELE PERDE TODA A SUA ENERGIA MÁGICA E TEM TEMPO LIMITADO PARA PEGÁ-LO NOVAMENTE. SE ELE FOR ATINGIDO SEM TER ENERGIA MÁGICA, ELE PERDE UMA VIDA.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7D336B56</hash>
		<image>./images/Flink (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Flink (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Flink (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Flink (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12763" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Formula One World Championship - Beyond the Limit (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Formula One World Championship: Beyond the Limit</name>
		<desc>BEYOND THE LIMIT IS A RACING SIM BASED ON FORMULA ONE CIRCA 1993. IT FEATURES REAL-LIFE CARS, TRACKS, AND DRIVERS FROM THE WORLD OF F1.THE GRAPHICS IN BEYOND THE LIMIT ARE CREATED FROM SCALED AND ROTATED SPRITES THAT CREATE A 3D EFFECT. IT ALSO FEATURES A</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>589260BE</hash>
		<image>./images/Formula One World Championship - Beyond the Limit (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Formula One World Championship - Beyond the Limit (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Formula One World Championship - Beyond the Limit (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Formula One World Championship - Beyond the Limit (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12749" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Ground Zero Texas (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>SPACE ALIENS ARE INFILTRATING THE U.S. FROM A SLEEPY LITTLE TOWN ON THE TEXAS/MEXICO BORDER, SNATCHING BODIES AND PAVING THE WAY FOR A GREATER INVASION. THOSE THEY ABDUCT RETURN AS POD PEOPLE-LIKE DRONES, NORMAL IN APPEARANCE UNTIL THEY REVEAL THEMSELVES. THE GOVERNMENT'S RESPONSE IS YOU - A TECHNICIAN DRIVING CUSTOM-BUILT GUN CAMERAS MOUNTED AROUND THE TOWN. SIMILAR TO NIGHT TRAP OR DOUBLE SWITCH, YOU MUST MONITOR THE TOWN FOR ALIEN ACTIVITY, AND RESPOND TO PROTECT THE LIVES OF THE CITIZENS AND YOUR AGENTS.

THE GAME IS PLAYED ENTIRELY THROUGH FOUR CAMERA FEEDS FROM LOCATIONS AROUND THE TOWN. THEY MOSTLY SHOW LOOPS OF BANAL ACTIVITY, BUT INDICATORS WILL ALERT YOU WHEN IMPORTANT ACTION IS OCCURRING AT THAT LOCATION. SWITCHING TO THAT CAMERA WILL ALLOW YOU TO WATCH CRUCIAL PLOT CLIPS, OR DEFEND THAT CAMERA FROM ALIENS IN A SINGLE-SCREEN SHOOTING GALLERY. AS CAMERAS TAKE MORE DAMAGE, THE PICTURE FROM THAT FEED DEGRADES UNTIL THE CAMERA ITSELF IS DESTROYED.

THE GOAL IS PRETTY MUCH TO JUGGLE BETWEEN CAMERAS SO AS NOT TO MISS AN IMPORTANT PLOT POINT, WHILE DEFENDING THEM FROM ATTACKERS OR SAVING CITIZENS FROM BEING ABDUCTED. IN A NEAT TWIST, CITIZENS WHO YOU FAILED TO SAVE MAY APPEAR LATER AS DISGUISED ALIENS THEMSELVES.

AS THE GAME PROGRESSES, THE INVASION INCREASES AND BECOMES MORE VIOLENT, BUT THE BASIC CONCEPT OF SWITCHING BETWEEN CAMERAS AND ENGAGING IN VIDEO SHOOTING GALLERIES REMAINS UNCHANGED.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Santa Monica Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Polyphony Digital</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>453C0ED2</hash>
		<image>./images/Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12749" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Ground Zero Texas (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>SPACE ALIENS ARE INFILTRATING THE U.S. FROM A SLEEPY LITTLE TOWN ON THE TEXAS/MEXICO BORDER, SNATCHING BODIES AND PAVING THE WAY FOR A GREATER INVASION. THOSE THEY ABDUCT RETURN AS POD PEOPLE-LIKE DRONES, NORMAL IN APPEARANCE UNTIL THEY REVEAL THEMSELVES. THE GOVERNMENT'S RESPONSE IS YOU - A TECHNICIAN DRIVING CUSTOM-BUILT GUN CAMERAS MOUNTED AROUND THE TOWN. SIMILAR TO NIGHT TRAP OR DOUBLE SWITCH, YOU MUST MONITOR THE TOWN FOR ALIEN ACTIVITY, AND RESPOND TO PROTECT THE LIVES OF THE CITIZENS AND YOUR AGENTS.

THE GAME IS PLAYED ENTIRELY THROUGH FOUR CAMERA FEEDS FROM LOCATIONS AROUND THE TOWN. THEY MOSTLY SHOW LOOPS OF BANAL ACTIVITY, BUT INDICATORS WILL ALERT YOU WHEN IMPORTANT ACTION IS OCCURRING AT THAT LOCATION. SWITCHING TO THAT CAMERA WILL ALLOW YOU TO WATCH CRUCIAL PLOT CLIPS, OR DEFEND THAT CAMERA FROM ALIENS IN A SINGLE-SCREEN SHOOTING GALLERY. AS CAMERAS TAKE MORE DAMAGE, THE PICTURE FROM THAT FEED DEGRADES UNTIL THE CAMERA ITSELF IS DESTROYED.

THE GOAL IS PRETTY MUCH TO JUGGLE BETWEEN CAMERAS SO AS NOT TO MISS AN IMPORTANT PLOT POINT, WHILE DEFENDING THEM FROM ATTACKERS OR SAVING CITIZENS FROM BEING ABDUCTED. IN A NEAT TWIST, CITIZENS WHO YOU FAILED TO SAVE MAY APPEAR LATER AS DISGUISED ALIENS THEMSELVES.

AS THE GAME PROGRESSES, THE INVASION INCREASES AND BECOMES MORE VIOLENT, BUT THE BASIC CONCEPT OF SWITCHING BETWEEN CAMERAS AND ENGAGING IN VIDEO SHOOTING GALLERIES REMAINS UNCHANGED.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Santa Monica Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Polyphony Digital</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8B50B18A</hash>
		<image>./images/Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ground Zero Texas (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12715" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Heart of the Alien - Out of This World Parts I and II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Heart of the Alien: Out of this World Parts I and II</name>
		<desc>HEART OF THE ALIEN IS A CINEMATIC PLATFORMER VIDEO GAME DEVELOPED BY INTERPLAY ENTERTAINMENT AND VIRGIN INTERACTIVE AND WAS RELEASED BY VIRGIN INTERACTIVE IN 1994 FOR THE SEGA CD EXCLUSIVELY IN NORTH AMERICA. IT IS A SEQUEL TO ANOTHER WORLD AND CONTINUES THE STORY DIRECTLY FROM WHERE THE ORIGINAL ENDED. THE GAME SWITCHES THE PLAYER'S ROLE FROM ANOTHER WORLD; THIS TIME THE PLAYER TAKES CONTROL OF BUDDY, THE MAIN CHARACTER'S ALIEN ALLY FROM THE PREVIOUS GAME.

THE STORY PICKS UP IMMEDIATELY AFTER THE END OF ANOTHER WORLD. BUDDY LANDS THE PTERODACTYL IN THE RUINS OF HIS VILLAGE, LAYS LESTER DOWN ON A COT TO REST AND WALKS THROUGH THE VILLAGE, THINKING OF HIS PAST. THIS SEQUENCE CONTAINS MANY FLASHBACKS OF EVENTS THAT LEAD UP TO BUDDY'S CAPTURE AND HIS AND LESTER'S ESCAPE FROM PRISON. IN THE GAME, BUDDY IS SEARCHING FOR THE RED-EYED ALIEN RESPONSIBLE FOR THE DESTRUCTION OF HIS VILLAGE AND THE IMPRISONMENT OF HIS PEOPLE. BUDDY ENTERS AGAIN THE PRISON IN SEARCH OF THE RED-EYED ALIEN.

NEAR THE END OF THE GAME, LESTER WHO WAKES BACK UP, HELPS BUDDY OUT, BUT THEN DIES IN THE PROCESS. BUDDY THEN GOES TO FIND AGAIN THE RED-EYED ALIEN IN A FORTRESS. EVENTUALLY, HE IS ABLE TO FIND HIM AND TRAPS HIM IN A CAGE WITH A BEAST THAT KILLS HIM. AT THE END OF THE GAME, BUDDY GIVES LESTER'S BODY A CEREMONIAL CREMATION. IT IS SHOWN LATER HOW BUDDY'S VILLAGE IS REBUILT WITH ITS CITIZENS LIVING AGAIN IN HARMONY.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Avalon Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Delphine Software International</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>AB4539A5</hash>
		<image>./images/Heart of the Alien - Out of This World Parts I and II (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Heart of the Alien - Out of This World Parts I and II (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Heart of the Alien - Out of This World Parts I and II (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Heart of the Alien - Out of This World Parts I and II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12745" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Heimdall (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Heimdall</name>
		<desc>VOCÊ JOGA COMO HEIMDALL, UM SEMIDEUS BASEADO NA MITOLOGIA NÓRDICA. O TRABALHO DE HEIMDALL É PROTEGER A ENTRADA DE ASGARD, A CASA DOS DEUSES, DE TODO O MAL, INCLUINDO O TERRÍVEL RAGNAROK, QUANDO TODAS AS FORÇAS DO MAL SE UNEM PARA TENTAR DESTRUIR OS DEUSES E, FINALMENTE, TUDO. INFELIZMENTE RAGNAROK ESTÁ A CAMINHO E SE ISSO NÃO BASTASSE, LOKI, DEUS DO MAL, ESCONDEU O MARTELO DE THOR, A ESPADA DE ODIN E A LANÇA DE FREY EM TRÊS MUNDOS. VOCÊ, COMO O RECÉM MORTALIZADO HEIMDALL, DEVE VISITAR CADA UM DESSES MUNDOS PARA COLETAR AS ARMAS DOS DEUSES. A PRIMEIRA É MIDGARD (OU TERRA), A SEGUNDA É UTGARD (O MUNDO DOS GIGANTES) E A TERCEIRA É A PRÓPRIA ASGARD, A CASA DOS DEUSES. CADA MUNDO TEM CERCA DE 15 ILHAS E CADA ILHA TEM INÚMEROS QUARTOS. QUANDO VOCÊ INICIA SUA MISSÃO, RECEBE TRÊS SUB-JOGOS PARA COMPLETAR. QUÃO BEM VOCÊ CONCLUI ESSES JOGOS DETERMINA AS ESTATÍSTICAS DE HEIMDALL (FORÇA, AGILIDADE, ETC.), BEM COMO QUANTAS PESSOAS ELE PODE ESCOLHER PARA COMPOR SUA EQUIPE. SE VOCÊ NÃO SE SAIR BEM, VOCÊ NÃO TERÁ 30 CARACTERES COMPLETOS PARA ESCOLHER E ALGUNS DOS MELHORES NÃO ESTARÃO DISPONÍVEIS PARA VOCÊ.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JVC</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9E82EC35</hash>
		<image>./images/Heimdall (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Heimdall (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Heimdall (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Heimdall (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12751" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hook (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Hook</name>
		<desc>IN THIS VIDEO GAME ADAPTION OF THE STEVEN SPIELBERG FILM HOOK, THE PLAYER TAKES THE ROLE OF A GROWN-UP PETER PAN, WHOSE KIDS HAVE BEEN KIDNAPPED BY CAPTAIN HOOK. TINKER BELL TAKES PETER BACK TO NEVERLAND WHERE HE MUST AGAIN BECOME PAN AND RECLAIM HIS CHILDREN.

THIS PARTICULAR INTERPRETATION IS A SIDE-SCROLLING ACTION GAME, IN WHICH PLAYERS MUST HACK THEIR WAY PAST HOOK'S DENIZENS THROUGH 11 LEVELS.  THESE INCLUDE FORESTS, ICY REGIONS, AND TOWNS WHICH PETER WILL HAVE TO JUMP, CLIMB, AND SWIM THROUGH. MAGIC ITEMS SUCH AS APPLES AND PIXIE DUST CAN BE COLLECTED FOR SPECIAL POWERS. WHEN ENEMIES ARE ATTACKED, THEY SIMPLY PUT THEIR HANDS UP IN SURRENDER RATHER THAN DYING, SO AS TO MAKE THE GAME MORE CHILD-FRIENDLY.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E764E2B6</hash>
		<image>./images/Hook (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Hook (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Hook (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hook (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58739" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Iron Helix (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Iron Helix</name>
		<desc>A ROGUE NAVY SHIP, JEREMIAH OBRIAN, THREATENS TO START A WAR. A VIRUS HAS WIPED OUT ITS CREW, BUT THE THREAT OF IT FIRING ITS IRON HELIX DOOMSDAY WEAPON IS STILL THERE. YOU MUST REMOTELY PILOT AN UNARMED SCIENCE ROBOT TO EXPLORE THE SHIP AND WORK OUT HOW TO SHUT THE WEAPON DOWN.

THE GAME USES INTERACTIVE QUARTER-SCREEN FOOTAGE TO DISPLAY THE SHIP'S INTERIORS. THE MAIN CHALLENGE IS THAT AN AUTOMATED SECURITY DEVICE IS CHASING YOU DOWN, AND MUST BE AVOIDED AND ULTIMATELY DESTROYED. A DELAY BETWEEN YOUR COMMANDS AND THE ROBOT'S RECEIPT OF THEM FORCES YOU TO PAY CLOSE ATTENTION TO THE SECURITY DRONE AND PLAN SEVERAL STEPS AHEAD.

AS YOU EXPLORE THE SHIP, YOU WILL FIND DATA PORTS, WHICH CAN BE JACKED INTO TO GAIN INFORMATION OR TO OPEN DOORWAYS. TO ACCESS MOST OF THESE, YOU WILL NEED TO FIND AND COLLECT A DNA SAMPLE FROM A MEMBER OF STAFF WHOSE ROLE GAVE HIM/HER ACCESS.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Drew Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Spectrum Holobyte</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>03F13DD5</hash>
		<image>./images/Iron Helix (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Iron Helix (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Iron Helix (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Iron Helix (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12812" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jaguar XJ220 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Jaguar XJ220</name>
		<desc>IN THE EARLY NINETIES, THE JAGUAR XJ220 WAS THE FASTEST SERIAL-PRODUCED CAR EVER. CORE DESIGN ACQUIRED THE RIGHT TO BUILD A GAME AROUND IT, IN A MOVE TO COUNTER GREMLIN'S IMMENSELY SUCCESSFUL LOTUS SERIES.

JUST LIKE LOTUS, JAGUAR XJ200 IS A VIEW FROM BEHIND RACER. THERE ARE 32 TRACKS ALL OVER THE WORLD, WITH VARYING ROAD CONDITIONS AND ANIMATED WEATHER CONDITIONS SUCH AS RAIN AND FOG IN ENGLAND, SNOW IN SWITZERLAND, AND TUMBLEWEED CROSSING THE STREET IN EGYPT. YOU RACE YOUR JAGUAR IN A CONSTRUCTOR GRAND PRIX, WITH OPPONENTS RUNNING FOR PORSCHE, FERRARI AND OTHER FAMOUS MAKERS. BETWEEN RACES, YOU MUST MEND THE DAMAGE YOUR CAR HAS SUSTAINED, WHICH EATS UP YOUR PRIZE MONEY. BACKGROUND MUSIC IS SELECTED THROUGH A DASHBOARD CD PLAYER, WHICH ALSO FEATURES SOME RATHER UNINSPIRING RADIO STATIONS.

THE GAME CAN ALSO BE PLAYED IN A TWO-PLAYER SPLIT-SCREEN MODE AND FEATURES A TRACK EDITOR FOR WHEN YOU TIRE OF THE BUILT-IN COURSES.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F4053B65</hash>
		<image>./images/Jaguar XJ220 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Jaguar XJ220 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Jaguar XJ220 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jaguar XJ220 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58718" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jeopardy! (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Jeopardy!</name>
		<desc>BASED ON THE TV QUIZ SHOW OF THE SAME NAME. THIS CD GAME FEATURES FULL MOTION VIDEO SPRITES OF THE HOST, ALEX TREBEK, AND THE CONTESTANTS AS WELL AS DIGITAL TRACK OF THE THEME SONG AND THE HOST'S VOICE.

YOU CAN PLAY IN A MULTIPLAYER GAME OR AGAINST THE COMPUTER AND CAN SELECT THE NUMBER OF CONTESTANTS AND THE GENDER AND APPEARANCE OF YOUR OWN CONTESTANT.

THERE IS A LARGER DATABASE OF QUESTIONS THAN ANY OF THE CARTRIDGE VERSIONS DUE TO THE INCREASED CAPACITY OF THE CD MEDIA VERSUS CARTRIDGE MEDIA OF THE TIME.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>DD4BC463</hash>
		<image>./images/Jeopardy! (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Jeopardy! (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Jeopardy! (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jeopardy! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97359" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Joe Montana's NFL Football (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Joe Montana's NFL Football</name>
		<desc>THIS ENHANCED VERSION OF THE JOE MONTANA SERIES FEATURES 3D MODELS AND EVEN FULL-MOTION VIDEO OF JOE MONTANA HIMSELF.  IT SPORTS A FULL NFL LICENSE WITH ALL 28 TEAMS OF THE TIME WITH THEIR RESPECTIVE NICKNAMES AND LOGOS, ALONG WITH 10 OF THE ALL-TIME GREATEST SUPER BOWL TEAMS INCLUDING '85 BEARS, THE '72 DOLPHINS, JUST TO NAME A FEW, THAT THE PLAYER CAN COMPETE AGAINST IF THEY WIN THE BIGGEST GAME OF THE YEAR.

THE GAMEPLAY IS A BEHIND THE QUARTERBACK VIEW WITH 3D ANGLES INCLUDING FOUR DIFFERENT REPLAY OPTIONS INCLUDING A "HELMET CAM".  IT FEATURES DIGITIZED VOICES AND VIDEOS INCLUDING JOE MONTANA IN WHICH THE PLAYER CAN CONSULT HIM THREE TIMES DURING A GAME.  THE STANDARD MODES ALSO APPLY INCLUDING REGULAR EXHIBITION GAMES AND A FULL-SEASON MODE COMPLETE WITH PLAYOFFS AND THE EVER IMPORTANT, SUPER BOWL.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>511B4E9B</hash>
		<image>./images/Joe Montana's NFL Football (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Joe Montana's NFL Football (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Joe Montana's NFL Football (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Joe Montana's NFL Football (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12714" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jurassic Park (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>THIS IS THE SEGA CD GAME BASED ON THE 1993 STEVEN SPIELBERG MOVIE BASED ON THE BOOK BY MICHAEL CRICHTON. THIS GAME DIFFERS GREATLY FROM OTHER JURASSIC PARK GAMES. IT IS A POINT-AND-CLICK ADVENTURE GAME, WITH A STRONG EMPHASIS ON ACTION SEQUENCES WHICH REQUIRE SPLIT-SECOND TIMING.

THE STORY TAKES PLACE AFTER THE EVENTS OF THE MOVIE/BOOK. YOU ARE SENT BACK TO JURASSIC PARK TO RETRIEVE DINOSAUR EGGS FROM AROUND THE PARK AND PUT THEM IN AN INCUBATOR. YOU ONLY HAVE 12 HOURS TO RETRIEVE ONE EGG FROM EVERY SPECIES OF DINO IN THE PARK. UNFORTUNATELY, SHORTLY BEFORE ARRIVING AT THE PARK, YOUR HELICOPTER CRASHES!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5D3D1ED6</hash>
		<image>./images/Jurassic Park (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Jurassic Park (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Jurassic Park (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jurassic Park (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12740" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Keio Flying Squadron (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Keio Flying Squadron</name>
		<desc>KEIO FLYING SQUADRON CHRONICLES THE ADVENTURES OF RAMI, THE LITTLE BUNNY-SUITED MEMBER OF THE FLYING SQUADRON TASKED WITH THE PROTECTION OF THE "SPECIAL HOLY OBJECT". UNFORTUNATELY AS THE GAME STARTS THE OBJECT IN QUESTION GETS STOLEN BY THE EVIL DR. PON, AND SO RAMI JUMPS ATOP HER TRUSTY DRAGON IN PURSUIT OF DR. PON.

THE GAME PLAYS AS A CLASSIC 2D SHOOTER WITH UPGRADABLE WEAPONS AND OPTION CHARACTERS, WITH A DISTINCT CARTOONISH AND FAMILY-FRIENDLY DESIGN.

FEATURES 7 LEVELS AND 3 DIFFICULTY SETTINGS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JVC</developer>
		<publisher>JVC</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>38EB00AA</hash>
		<image>./images/Keio Flying Squadron (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Keio Flying Squadron (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Keio Flying Squadron (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Keio Flying Squadron (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97362" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kids on Site (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Kids on Site</name>
		<desc>REMEMBER THE DAYS AS A KID WHEN YOU WERE FASCINATED WITH THESE BIG MACHINES ON THE BUILDING SITE? WITH THIS GAME YOU HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO TRY THEM OUT! YOU CAN USE EITHER THE EXCAVATOR, BULLDOZER, STEAMROLLER OR WRECKING BALL. THE HANDLING COULDN'T BE EASIER, THERE ARE JUST THREE BUTTONS TO PRESS: LEFT, RIGHT AND USE.

WITH EACH MACHINE YOU GET A SIMPLE TASK, E.G. CARRY THREE SHOVELS OF DIRT ON A TRUCK. BUT THE FUN THING IS THAT YOU AREN'T RESTRICTED TO THIS AND CAN JUST SCREW AROUND. WHY WRECK AN OLD HOUSE WHEN THE PIT LATRINE IS SO MUCH MORE TEMPTING? THE WHOLE GAME IS PRESENTED IN FULL MOTION VIDEO - THE REACTIONS ARE VERY HUMOROUS AND WITH A FAIR SHARE OF SLAPSTICK. TO IMPROVE THE LONG TIME MOTIVATION THERE ARE EVEN MULTIPLE VIDEOS FOR EVERY ACTION, E.G. THE FIRST TIME YOU BREAK A ROAD BLOCK WITH THE THE EXCAVATOR YOU DRIVE ON A HIGHWAY, THE SECOND TIME INTO A CANYON, THE THIRD TIME ONTO A ROLLERCOASTER AND SO ON...</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>754836D3</hash>
		<image>./images/Kids on Site (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Kids on Site (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Kids on Site (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kids on Site (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12792" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Lethal Enforcers II: Gun Fighters</name>
		<desc>NESTA SEQUENCIA DE LETHAL ENFORCERS VOCÊ É O XERIFE DE UMA CIDADE SITUADA NO SELVAGEM VELHO OESTE. USANDO O CONTROLE OU A JUSTIFY LIGHTGUN DA KONAMI, VOCÊ ENFRENTARÁ CRIMINOSOS QUE ESTÃO SEQUESTRANDO INOCENTES E ROUBANDO BANCOS. VOCÊ É A ÚNICA SALVAÇÃO PARA ELES.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./images/Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58720" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lethal Enforcers (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Lethal Enforcers</name>
		<desc>PICK UP YOUR PISTOL AND BE THE COP YOU NEED TO BE IN ORDER TO RID THE STREETS OF THE CRIMINALS OUT TO MAKE YOUR DAY HELL. AIM WISELY AND QUICKLY, OTHERWISE YOUR LIVES WILL BE LOST QUICKLY IN THIS 1ST PERSON ARCADE SHOOTER, CLEANING UP THE STREETS. THE HIGHER THE DIFFICULTY LEVEL, THE MORE CRIMES THERE WILL BE TO ELIMINATE, BUT WATCH OUT FOR THE OTHER WEAPONS THAT CAN HELP YOU ALONG THE WAY.

GO STRAIGHT INTO THE MAYHEM, PRACTICE IN THE TARGETING RANGE OR HAVE A FRIEND BACK YOU UP IN TWO PLAYER MODE. USE A GUN ACCESSORY OR PLAY WITH THE GAMEPAD.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>12061A73</hash>
		<image>./images/Lethal Enforcers (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Lethal Enforcers (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Lethal Enforcers (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lethal Enforcers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58740" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Links - The Challenge of Golf (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Links: The Challenge of Golf</name>
		<desc>LINKS: THE CHALLENGE OF GOLF IS A GOLF SIMULATION THAT TRIES TO IMPLEMENT REALISTIC ASPECTS OF GOLF IN A VIDEO GAME FORMAT.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Papyrus</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<hash>9A73F375</hash>
		<image>./images/Links - The Challenge of Golf (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Links - The Challenge of Golf (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Links - The Challenge of Golf (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Links - The Challenge of Golf (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12837" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Loadstar - The Legend of Tully Bodine (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Loadstar: The Legend of Tully Bodine</name>
		<desc>LOADSTAR IS A RAIL-SHOOTER CONCERNED WITH SHOOTING ENEMIES WHILE NAVIGATING YOUR SHIP, MUCH LIKE SEWER SHARK. YOU'RE ACTUALLY ON RAILS IN THIS GAME, AS YOU TRAVEL IN A TRUCK/TRAIN CALLED LOADSTAR ALONG A MAGNETIC RAIL NETWORK COVERING THE MOON. SHIFTING THE CURSOR TO THE EDGE OF THE SCREEN CHANGES TO A DIFFERENT TRACK WHEN AVAILABLE, WITH INCORRECT TURNS EITHER KILLING YOU INSTANTLY OR MOVING YOU OFF-COURSE FROM THE LEVEL END. DIRECTION INDICATORS AND DISTANT LANDMARKS HELP KEEP YOU DRIVING IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION, WHILE ACCIDENTS, TRACK CLOSURES, AND ROBOT COPS WORK TO KEEP YOU FROM IT. YOUR WEAPONS "TAG" ENEMIES AND FORCE THEM TO EXPLODE, OR CAN TAG INCOMING SHOTS AND DEFLECT THEM WITH A SEPARATE SHIELD BUTTON.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rocket Science Games</developer>
		<publisher>Rocket Science Games</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>222B6CC6</hash>
		<image>./images/Loadstar - The Legend of Tully Bodine (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Loadstar - The Legend of Tully Bodine (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Loadstar - The Legend of Tully Bodine (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Loadstar - The Legend of Tully Bodine (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12767" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lords of Thunder (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Lords of Thunder</name>
		<desc>NA OUTRORA PACÍFICA TERRA DE MISTRAL, A LENDA FALA DE UM VALENTE CAVALEIRO CHAMADO DRAK QUE SELOU UM DEUS MALIGNO CHAMADO DEORIC SOB OS SEIS CONTINENTES DA TERRA. NO ENTANTO, A PAZ NUNCA DURA. O IMPÉRIO GARUDA INVADIU AS TERRAS DE MISTRAL, E OS SEIS GENERAIS DAS TREVAS, LIDERADOS POR SORNBUL, CONQUISTARAM OS CONTINENTES. A AMBIÇÃO DE SORNBUL É NADA MENOS QUE RESSUSCITAR DEORIC E MERGULHAR A TERRA NO CAOS. DURAN, DESCENDENTE DE DRAK, É O ÚNICO QUE PODE PARAR O PLANO MALUCO DO IMPÉRIO GARUDA, E COM O PODER DAS ARMADURAS MÍSTICAS DE DRAK, ELE SAI PARA DETER SORNBUL A QUALQUER CUSTO. OS SEIS CONTINENTES DE MISTRAL PODEM SER DESAFIADOS EM QUALQUER ORDEM, CADA UM DOS QUAIS ESTÁ CHEIO DE HORDAS DE DEMÔNIOS E UM DOS DARK GENERALS DE SORNBUL. DEPOIS DE COMPLETAR TODOS OS SEIS CONTINENTES, O JOGADOR ENFRENTARÁ SORNBUL NA ILHA FINAL. ANTES DE UM NÍVEL, O JOGADOR PODE ESCOLHER ENTRE UMA DAS QUATRO ARMADURAS ELEMENTARES, CADA UMA COM SUA PRÓPRIA BALA E BOMBA ÚNICA. OS INIMIGOS DROPAM CRISTAIS QUE SÃO USADOS ??EM UMA LOJA ENTRE NÍVEIS PARA COMPRAR MAIS SAÚDE, BOMBAS E CONTINUES.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>50423025</hash>
		<image>./images/Lords of Thunder (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Lords of Thunder (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Lords of Thunder (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lords of Thunder (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12781" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lunar - Eternal Blue (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Lunar: Eternal Blue</name>
		<desc>VOLTE PARA O MUNDO ENCANTADOR DE LUNAR! JUNTE-SE A HIRO E RUBY 1.000 ANOS APÓS A PRIMEIRA AVENTURA, ENQUANTO ELES TRABALHAM PARA DESVENDAR OS SEGREDOS DA BLUE SPIRE E DA JOVEM ESTRANHA QUE ENCONTRARAM DENTRO DELA! MAS TENHA CUIDADO! FORÇAS ESTÃO NO TRABALHO TENTANDO REVIVER O MAL ZOFAR E MERGULHAR LUNAR NA ESCURIDÃO PARA SEMPRE! VIAJE PARA TERRAS DISTANTES EM BUSCA DA DEUSA ALTHENA, QUE PODE SER A ÚNICA PODEROSA O SUFICIENTE PARA PARAR ZOFAR. AO LONGO DO CAMINHO, VOCÊ CONHECERÁ PERSONAGENS NOVOS E EMOCIONANTES, LUTARÁ COM MONSTROS TOTALMENTE ANIMADOS, ATRAVESSARÁ PICOS COBERTOS DE NEVE E RASTEJARÁ POR CALABOUÇOS ESCORREGADIOS ENQUANTO VOCÊ TRABALHA EM DIREÇÃO AO CLÍMAX ATERRORIZANTE!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Game Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8C669538</hash>
		<image>./images/Lunar - Eternal Blue (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Lunar - Eternal Blue (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Lunar - Eternal Blue (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lunar - Eternal Blue (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12741" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lunar - The Silver Star (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Lunar: The Silver Star</name>
		<desc>BEM-VINDO AO MUNDO DE LUNAR, ONDE OS DRAGÕES AINDA VIVEM E A MAGIA É VALORIZADA ACIMA DE TUDO. JUNTE-SE A ALEX, O JOVEM AVENTUREIRO, ENQUANTO ELE COMEÇA UMA MISSÃO COM SEUS AMIGOS PARA SALVAR SUAS TERRAS DOS AVANÇOS ESMAGADORES DO IMPERADOR MÁGICO. EXPLORE CALABOUÇOS, LUTE CONTRA MONSTROS ATERRORIZANTES E COLETE INFORMAÇÕES DOS LOCAIS ENQUANTO AVANÇA EM DIREÇÃO AO CONFRONTO EXPLOSIVO COM O PRÓPRIO IMPERADOR MÁGICO! PREPARE-SE PARA A AVENTURA DA SUA VIDA!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Working Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Game Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8CCA4D1E</hash>
		<image>./images/Lunar - The Silver Star (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Lunar - The Silver Star (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Lunar - The Silver Star (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lunar - The Silver Star (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12761" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mad Dog McCree II - The Lost Gold (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mad Dog II: The Lost Gold</name>
		<desc>MAD DOG II : THE LOST GOLD SUR MEGA-CD EST UN JEU DE TIR À LA PREMIÈRE PERSONNE SE DÉROULANT AU FAR WEST. ENTREZ EN PLEIN COEUR D'UN FILM INTERACTIF ET TESTEZ VOS RÉFLEXES EN TIRANT PLUS VITE QUE VOTRE OMBRE FACE AUX GANGSTERS, INDIENS, ET AUTRES ENNEMIS. ENFIN, RETROUVEZ VOTRE PLUS GRAND ENNEMI, MAD DOG POUR UN FACE-À-FACE QUI PROMET D'ÊTRE ENFLAMMÉ.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>American Laser Games</developer>
		<publisher>American Laser Games</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./images/Mad Dog McCree II - The Lost Gold (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mad Dog McCree II - The Lost Gold (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mad Dog McCree II - The Lost Gold (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mad Dog McCree II - The Lost Gold (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12784" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mad Dog McCree (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mad Dog McCree</name>
		<desc>MAG DOG MCCREE E SUA GANGUE SEQÜESTRARAM O PREFEITO E SUA FILHA, E DEPENDE DE VOCÊ RESGATÁ-LOS. VOCÊ DEVE ATIRAR ATRAVÉS DE BARRAS E ROUBOS DE BANCO PARA ELIMINAR A GANGUE E SALVAR TUDO O QUE VOCÊ CONSIDERA TÃO BOM E VERDADEIRO. ONDE O JOGO DIFERIU DE OUTROS LANÇAMENTOS DE INFLUÊNCIAS DA WOLFGANG DA OPERAÇÃO WOLF FOI NO USO DE VÍDEO AO VIVO, COM PESSOAS REAIS APARECENDO NA TELA ANTES DE DERRUBÁ-LAS.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>American Laser Games</developer>
		<publisher>American Laser Games</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./images/Mad Dog McCree (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mad Dog McCree (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mad Dog McCree (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mad Dog McCree (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Make My Video - Kriss Kross (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Make My Video - Kriss Kross (USA)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Make My Video - Kriss Kross (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Make My Video - Kriss Kross (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Make My Video - Kriss Kross (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Make My Video - Kriss Kross (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58738" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Make My Video - INXS (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Make My Video: INXS</name>
		<desc>MAKE MY VIDEO: INXS IS A VIDEO GAME BASED ON REAL-TIME EDITING OF MUSIC VIDEO FOOTAGE. THE SETUP IS THAT A PAIR OF FEMALE FRIENDS IS HANGING AROUND A BAR AND MONOPOLIZING THE POOL TABLE. THE GAME EXPLORES THE DUO'S INTERPERSONAL INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER PATRONS AT THE BAR: THERE'S THE FLY, AN ALOOF COOL GUY; TED AND GOMEZ, BRAINDEAD SURFER DUDES TRYING TO PICK UP THE LADIES, AND WHO ARE THINLY-VEILED PARODIES OF BILL &amp; TED; POINDEXTER, THE NERD WHO IS ALSO TRYING TO WORK UP THE COURAGE TO TALK TO THE WOMEN; AND FLO AND TIGER, A PAIR OF LEATHER-CLAD TOUGH CHICKS WHOSE INTEREST IS BEATING THE MAIN SUBJECTS OF THE GAME SO THAT THEY CAN CONTROL THE BAR MUSIC AND PLAY THEIR MEGADETH VIDEOTAPE. EACH PERSON OR PAIR HAS OWN THEIR IDEAS ABOUT WHAT AN IDEAL INXS VIDEO SHOULD OR SHOULD NOT CONTAIN. THE SPECIFICATIONS NORMALLY COME IN THE FORM OF A SET OF PICTURES THEY EITHER DO OR DON'T WANT TO SEE, AND PERHAPS SOME EFFECTS. THE GAME FEATURES THREE INXS VIDEOS FROM WHICH TO CHOOSE: "HEAVEN SENT", "NOT ENOUGH TIME", AND "BABY DONÂT CRY".</desc>
		<rating>0.15</rating>
		<releasedate>19921015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0E64D89B</hash>
		<image>./images/Make My Video - INXS (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Make My Video - INXS (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Make My Video - INXS (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Make My Video - INXS (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12762" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mansion of Hidden Souls (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mansion of Hidden Souls</name>
		<desc>MANSION OF HIDDEN SOULS IS AN ADVENTURE GAME CREATED ENTIRELY WITH FULL-MOTION VIDEO. IT TAKES PLACE IN A PRE-RENDERED MANSION THAT THE PLAYER EXPLORES FROM A FIRST-PERSON PERSPECTIVE. AS THEY WANDER FROM ROOM TO ROOM, THE ACTION UNFOLDS VIA VIDEO SEQUENCES.

THE PLAYER TAKES ON THE ROLE OF JONATHAN, A BOY WHOSE SISTER HAS WANDERED INTO THE SPOOKY MANSION. WHEN SHE ENTERED THE MANSION, SHE DISAPPEARED! WHAT'S MORE, THE MANSION IS FULL OF TALKING BUTTERFLIES. THE PLAYER MUST SEARCH THE WHOLE MANSION TO UNLOCK ITS SECRETS AND FIND JONATHAN'S SISTER.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vic Tokai</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>99BD2BEB</hash>
		<image>./images/Mansion of Hidden Souls (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mansion of Hidden Souls (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mansion of Hidden Souls (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mansion of Hidden Souls (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="102825" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Make My Video - Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Marky Mark And The Funky Bunch</name>
		<desc>MARKY MARK AND THE FUNKY BUNCH IS AN ENTRY IN THE MAKE MY VIDEO SERIES FOR THE SEGA MEGA-CD. IT FEATURES MUSIC FROM MARKY MARK AND THE FUNKY BUNCH. THIS IS THE ONLY MAKE MY VIDEO GAME NOT TO BE RELEASED IN EUROPE.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Make My Video - Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Make My Video - Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Make My Video - Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Make My Video - Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97354" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mary Shelley's Frankenstein (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mary Shelley's Frankenstein</name>
		<desc>MARY SHELLEY'S FRANKENSTEIN IS A VIDEO GAME THAT IS BASED ON THE 1994 FILM OF THE SAME NAME. THIS VERSION INCLUDES A BONUS GAME: BRAM STOKER'S DRACULA.

THE PLAYER CONTROLS FRANKENSTEIN'S MONSTER AS HE STOMPS THROUGH THE STREETS OF INGOLSTADT, BAVARIA, IN THE YEAR 1793 SEEKING REVENGE AGAINST A CERTAIN MAN NAMED VICTOR FOR REJECTING HIM ONCE HE WAS CREATED. SINCE HE IS A PRODUCT OF ARTIFICIAL MANUFACTURING, HE IS CONDEMNED AND DECLARED AN EXPENDABLE PARIAH BY PEASANTS AND SOLDIERS. THE COMMON FOLKS THAT STRIVE TO KILL FRANKENSTEIN'S MONSTER ARE HIGHLY IGNORANT ABOUT MODERN SCIENCE AND BELIEVE THAT HE IS TRULY A DEMON.

THE PLAYER USES A WOODEN STICK TO WARD OFF ENEMIES. THE STICK THAT FRANKENSTEIN'S MONSTER CARRIES CAN BE PUT ON FIRE IF SWUNG TOWARDS FIRE. FRANKENSTEIN ALSO HAS AN ADDITIONAL ATTACK; A BLUE BALL OF NEGATIVE ENERGY THAT POPS UP WHEN THE PLAYER RELEASES THE BUTTON. PEASANTS IN THE GAME CAN EITHER BE MALE OR FEMALE; SOLDIERS ARE ALWAYS MALE. THE FEMALE PEASANTS ATTACK WITH POTS WHILE THE MALE PEASANTS ATTACK WITH MELEE WEAPONS. HOWEVER, THE SOLDIERS (MEN DRESSED IN RED) ATTACK THE PLAYER WITH MUSKET SHOTS. SIMPLE PUZZLES INVOLVING SWITCHES AND PULLEYS MUST BE SOLVED IN ORDER TO PROGRESS WITHIN THE LEVELS.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D1B7EDB0</hash>
		<image>./images/Mary Shelley's Frankenstein (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mary Shelley's Frankenstein (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mary Shelley's Frankenstein (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mary Shelley's Frankenstein (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Masked Rider, The - Kamen Rider ZO (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Masked Rider, The - Kamen Rider ZO (USA)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Masked Rider, The - Kamen Rider ZO (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Masked Rider, The - Kamen Rider ZO (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Masked Rider, The - Kamen Rider ZO (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Masked Rider, The - Kamen Rider ZO (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12776" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./MegaRace (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Megarace</name>
		<desc>VIRTUAL TELEVISION HAS GIVEN US A CHANCE TO DO THE THINGS THAT WE CAN'T MAKE REAL IN EVERYDAY LIFE: RACE THROUGH 14 GREAT TRACKS IN 5 DIFFERENT ENVIRONMENTS IN A TOTALLY VIRTUAL PLACE WHERE YOU CAN KILL EACH OTHER QUITE EASILY WITH SIDEKICKS OR GUNS. IN EVERY TRACK YOU WILL SEE SOME SYMBOLS THAT CAN MAKE YOUR CAR SPEED UP, SLOW UP OR EVEN BLOW UP, LIKE YOUR MEGA-HOST LANCE BOYLE SAYS, "WHO KNOWS; WHO CARES!" EVERYTHING YOU SEE IN MEGARACE IS VIRTUAL AND NO ONE REALLY DIES THERE. SO HAVE FUN!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cryo Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Cryo Interactive</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6C768FCE</hash>
		<image>./images/MegaRace (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/MegaRace (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/MegaRace (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/MegaRace (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12707" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mickey Mania - The Timeless Adventures of Mickey Mouse (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mickey Mania: The Timeless Adventures of Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>"MICKEY MANIA" É UM TÍTULO QUE PRESTA HOMENAGEM AOS CLÁSSICOS DE ANIMAÇÃO DO PERSONAGEM, QUE ESTAVA PREVISTO PARA SER LANÇADO NO ANO EM QUE COMPLETAVA 65 ANOS DE CRIAÇÃO, MAS CHEGANDO AO MERCADO UM ANO DEPOIS. SEGUE O ESTILO PLATAFORMA, COM FASES BEM ELABORADAS E CRIATIVAS, QUE SE DESTACAM PELAS BELAS ANIMAÇÕES E VISUAIS DETALHADOS. A AVENTURA CONTA COM AMBIENTES INSPIRADOS NOS DESENHOS "STEAMBOAT WILLIE", DE 1928 (O COMEÇO DA FASE É EM PRETO E BRANCO, ASSIM COMO O DESENHO ORIGINAL), PASSANDO POR "THE MAD DOCTOR", DE 1933, "THE BAND CONCERT" DE 1935, "MOOSE HUNTERS" DE 1937, "LONESOME GHOSTS" DE 1937, "MICKEY AND THE BEANSTALK" DE 1947 E "THE PRINCE AND THE PAUPER", DE 1990.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19941002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Santa Monica Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Traveller's Tales</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0687A776</hash>
		<image>./images/Mickey Mania - The Timeless Adventures of Mickey Mouse (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mickey Mania - The Timeless Adventures of Mickey Mouse (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mickey Mania - The Timeless Adventures of Mickey Mouse (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mickey Mania - The Timeless Adventures of Mickey Mouse (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12774" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Microcosm (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Microcosm</name>
		<desc>IN THE YEAR 2051, TWO MEGA CORPORATIONS BATTLE IT OUT FOR SUPREMACY OVER AN OVERCROWDED, OVERPOLLUTED PLANET.  CYBERTECH INDUSTRIES, THE DOMINANT COMPANY ON THE PLANET, IS BEING CHALLENGED BY AXIOM, WHO BLAMES THE FORMER FOR THEIR PRESIDENT'S DEATH.  TO GAIN REVENGE, THEY SECRETLY INJECT CYBERTECH'S PRESIDENT, ANTON KORSBY, WITH A VIRUS THAT THREATENS TO TAKE OVER HIS BODY, AND ULTIMATELY DESTROY HIMSELF AND CYBERTECH. YOUR MISSION IS TO ENTER KORSBY'S BODY, DESTROY THE VIRUS, AND DEFEAT THE ORGANISM THAT CONTROLS HIS BRAIN.

MICROCOSM IS A 3D ACTION SHOOTER, SIMILAR TO DESCENT, THAT TAKES PLACE ENTIRELY WITHIN THE HUMAN BODY. THE CONCEPT WAS INSPIRED BY THE 1966 MOVIE FANTASTIC VOYAGE. THE PLAYER PILOTS HIS WAY THROUGH VARIOUS PARTS OF THE ANATOMY, BLASTING VIRII AND ENEMY SHIPS, WHILE GAINING POWER-UPS AND FASTER, STRONGER CRAFT. THE GOAL OF THE GAME IS TO EVENTUALLY REACH THE BRAIN TO STOP GREY M, THE ENTITY THAT CONTROLS KORSBY'S BODY.

MICROCOSM MAKES HEAVY USE OF FULL-MOTION VIDEO AND FEATURES HIGH-RESOLUTION FRACTAL GRAPHICS (TO SIMULATE THE WALLS OF VEINS AND ARTERIES), DIGITAL MUSIC AND SOUND EFFECTS.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D7D949A0</hash>
		<image>./images/Microcosm (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Microcosm (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Microcosm (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Microcosm (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97376" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Midnight Raiders (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Midnight Raiders</name>
		<desc>A FMV RAIL SHOOTER PLACING YOU IN THE HELMET OF ROOKIE CHOPPER GUNNER "JOKER." TERRORISTS HAVE KIDNAPPED A GERMAN BIOCHEMIST AND TAKEN HIM TO A MIDDLE EASTERN OIL REFINERY, WHERE HE IS FORCED TO WORK ON A LETHAL TOXIN. JOKER AND CREW MUST FLY TO THE REFINERY, SHOOTING DOWN ENEMY TANKS AND HELICOPTERS, THEN JOKER MUST RAPPEL DOWN TO THE REFINERY AND RESCUE THE CHEMIST ON FOOT.

THE HELICOPTER SECTIONS FOLLOW A PATTERN SIMILAR TO TOMCAT ALLEY, SHOWING BRIEF CLIPS OF THE CAST IN THE COCKPIT, FOLLOWED BY A "NOSE CAMERA" SHOT OF AN ENEMY APPROACHING. DURING THIS SHOT, YOU HAVE THE ABILITY TO MOVE A SET OF CROSSHAIRS OVER THE ENEMY AND PRESS THE "FIRE" BUTTON. IF YOU'RE ON TARGET, YOU ARE REWARDED WITH MILITARY ARCHIVAL FOOTAGE OF HELICOPTERS SHOOTING ROCKETS, AND CLOSE UP FOOTAGE OF MODELS EXPLODING. 

THE ON-FOOT SECTIONS FOLLOW AN IDENTICAL PATTERN, THOUGH WITH HAND-HELD CAMERAS PLACING YOU IN THE "EYES" OF JOKER, AND BLACK-CLAD GUARDS TAKING THE PLACE OF HELICOPTERS. OTHERWISE, THE IDEA OF HAVING A FEW SECONDS TO REACT AND AIM CROSSHAIRS IS THE SAME. THE PLOT IS EXPANDED THROUGH OCCASIONAL CUTSCENES IN BOTH THE HELICOPTER AND FOOT SECTIONS.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Stargate Films</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E4BEFA4F</hash>
		<image>./images/Midnight Raiders (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Midnight Raiders (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Midnight Raiders (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Midnight Raiders (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12731" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers</name>
		<desc>THIS TAKE ON THE POWER RANGERS FRANCHISE IS DIFFERENT FROM THE MANY OTHER POWER RANGER GAMES AS IT FEATURES FMV WITH REAL VIDEO OF THE ACTUAL TV SHOW. THE FOOTAGE IS SPLICED FROM NINE DIFFERENT EPISODES AND THE GAMEPLAY IS REMINISCENT OF GAMES SUCH AS DRAGON'S LAIR AND SPACE ACE WHERE THE PLAYER MUST PRESS A BUTTON AT A CERTAIN TIME TO AVOID BEING PUNCHED, KICKED, AVOID A TRAP, ETC. FAILURE TO MISS PRESSING A BUTTON WILL CONTINUE TO PLAY THE FOOTAGE, BUT CAUSE THE PLAYER TO LOOSE A LIFE.  AFTER A CERTAIN SET OF LIVES ARE LOST, THE GAME WILL BE OVER.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Banpresto</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A92DE8B1</hash>
		<image>./images/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12704" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mortal Kombat (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat</name>
		<desc>FIVE HUNDRED YEARS AGO, AN ANCIENT AND WELL RESPECTED SHAOLIN FIGHTING TOURNAMENT, HELD EVERY 50 YEARS, WAS CORRUPTED BY AN EVIL AND ELDERLY SORCERER BY THE NAME OF SHANG TSUNG.  SHANG WAS ACCOMPANIED BY PRINCE GORO, A WARRIOR OF THE SHOKAN RACE (A FOUR ARMED HALF-HUMAN/HALF-DRAGON). KNOWING THAT IF TEN TOURNAMENTS IN A ROW WERE WON BY THE OUTWORLD CHAMPION, THE EARTH REALM WOULD BE CONQUERED BY EVIL AND FALL INTO DARKNESS, SHANG ENTERED GORO IN THE TOURNAMENT AND HAD HIM DEFEAT THE GREAT KUNG LAO. GORO HAS BEEN  REIGNING SUPREME AS THE UNDEFEATED FIGHTING CHAMPION FOR FIVE HUNDRED YEARS NOW. AS THE LAST TOURNAMENT REQUIRED DRAWS NEAR, RAIDEN, THUNDER GOD AND PROTECTOR OF THE EARTH REALM, ENACTS A PLAN TO TIP THE SCALES IN THE HUMANS FAVOR, SEVEN FIGHTERS STEP INTO THE ARENA ON SHANG TSUNG'S MYSTERIOUS ISLAND: SHAOLIN WARRIOR LIU KANG, SPECIAL FORCES OPERATIVE SONYA BLADE, THE MERCENARY THUG KANO, FAME-SEEKING ACTOR JOHNNY CAGE, THE ICE WIELDING LIN KUEI WARRIOR SUB-ZERO AND HIS UNDEAD ADVERSARY SCORPION, AND RAIDEN HIMSELF.

MORTAL KOMBAT IS A SIDE-SCROLLING 1 ON 1 FIGHTING GAME. FIGHTING IS SET AS ONE ON ONE KOMBAT, ALLOWING EACH PLAYER TO PERFORM A VARIETY OF PUNCHES, KICKS, AND SPECIAL MOVES IN ORDER TO DEFEAT THEIR OPPONENT.  WHEN THE OPPONENT FACES THEIR SECOND ROUND LOSS, THE WINNER CAN PERFORM A FINISHING MOVE CALLED A "FATALITY" ON THE LOSER.  THE FATALITY IS A MOVE UNIQUE TO EACH FIGHTER THAT GRAPHICALLY KILLS THE LOSER IN A BLOOD-SOAKED FINALE.

MORTAL KOMBAT BEGAN ITS LIFE AS A 2-PLAYER ARCADE TITLE. IT IS NOTABLE FOR ITS USE OF DIGITIZED ACTORS TO REPRESENT THE GAME'S FIGHTERS, AS WELL AS ITS USE OF COPIOUS AMOUNTS OF BLOOD DURING GAMEPLAY.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19931202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>811F4E78</hash>
		<image>./images/Mortal Kombat (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Mortal Kombat (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Mortal Kombat (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mortal Kombat (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12846" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./My Paint - The Animated Paint Program (USA).chd</path>
		<name>My Paint: The Animated Paint Program</name>
		<desc>MY PAINT, THE WORLD'S FIRST ANIMATED PAINT PROGRAM GIVES YOU THE POWER TO PUSH YOUR CREATIVITY TO NEW HEIGHTS! IT'S A FULL FEATURED PAINT PROGRAM YOU NOT ONLY SEE, BUT HEAR! FREEHAND DRAW YOUR OWN MASTERPIECE OR CHOOSE FROM ANY OF THE OVER 200 BUILT-IN DRAWINGS. EVERYTHING FROM PLANES, TRAINS AND AUTOMOBILES TO VELOCIRAPTORS, BATS AND PANTHERS ARE INCLUDED. USE ANY OF THE MANY PATTERNS LIKE DINOSAUR SKINS, MOVING WATER, STRIPES, DOTS, OR THE COOL ANIMATED STICKERS TO BRING YOUR DRAWINGS TO LIFE!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Saddleback Graphics</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A371C9CC</hash>
		<image>./images/My Paint - The Animated Paint Program (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/My Paint - The Animated Paint Program (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/My Paint - The Animated Paint Program (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/My Paint - The Animated Paint Program (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12779" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./NBA Jam (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NBA Jam</name>
		<desc>NBA JAM IS A TWO-ON-TWO BASKETBALL GAME YOU CAN PLAY ANY NBA TEAM, AND YOU CAN PLAY AS PLAYERS LIKE BARKLEY, STARKS, PIPPEN, AND GRANT. EACH HUMAN PLAYER CONTROLS A SINGLE PLAYER, SO CHOOSE YOUR SQUAD WISELY TO TAKE TEAM-MATE SKILL INTO ACCOUNT. THE GAME IS ACTION-ORIENTED, AND PLAYERS CAN PERFORM UNREALISTIC SLAM-DUNKS. FULL PERFORMANCE STATISTICS ARE AUTOMATICALLY RECORDED. THE PLAY CLOCK AND 3-POINT LINE APPLY, BUT OTHER RULES ARE LARGELY OVERLOOKED.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>BB5331DF</hash>
		<image>./images/NBA Jam (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/NBA Jam (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/NBA Jam (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/NBA Jam (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97369" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./NFL Football Trivia Challenge (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NFL Football Trivia Challenge</name>
		<desc>NFL FOOTBALL TRIVIA CHALLENGE É UM JOGO DE TRIVIA COM UMA LICENÇA DA NATIONAL FOOTBALL LEAGUE. CADA JOGADOR PODE ESCOLHER SEU TIME FAVORITO PARA JOGAR. OS COMENTARISTAS DE TV PAT SUMMERALL E TOM BOOKSHIER DESCREVERAM VÁRIAS SITUAÇÕES EM JOGO ACOMPANHADAS POR 1200 IMAGENS E 300 CLIPES EM FULL MOTION VIDEO. 1500 QUESTÕES DE MÚLTIPLA ESCOLHA NO JOGO. PARA CADA RESPOSTA CORRETA, O JOGADOR GANHA UMA JARDA NO JOGO E AUMENTA SUAS CHANCES DE MARCAR UM PONTO. O JOGADOR COM MAIS PONTOS APÓS 60 PERGUNTAS GANHA O JOGO. EXISTEM TRÊS NÍVEIS DE DIFICULDADE DIFERENTES PARA JOGAR.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capitol Disc Interactive Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Capitol Disc Interactive Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>216948F4</hash>
		<image>./images/NFL Football Trivia Challenge (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/NFL Football Trivia Challenge (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/NFL Football Trivia Challenge (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/NFL Football Trivia Challenge (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12851" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./NFL's Greatest - San Francisco vs. Dallas 1978-1993 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Nfl's Greatest - San Francisco Vs. Dallas 1978-1993</name>
		<desc>TOP STARS FOR THE COWBOYS AND 49ERS FROM THE 70'S, 80'S, AND 90'S IN ONE GAME. STAUBACH, DORSETT, "TOO TALL" JONES, AIKMAN, IRVIN, SMITH - TAKE THE FIELD AGAINST MONTANA, LOTT, CLARK, RICE, WATTERS, YOUNG - JUST TO NAME A FEW! YOU CHOOSE THE QUARTERBACK, YOU CALL THE PLAYS - THEN WATCH THE ACTION UNFOLD IN FULL COLOR TRUVIDEO! IMAGINE TONY DORSETT AND TROY AIKMAN IN THE SAME BACKFIELD, OR STEVE YOUNG HITTING DWIGHT CLARK WITHA TD PASS, OR "TOO TALL" JONES CHASING DOWN YOUNG - IT CAN HAPPEN! 15 YEARS OF REAL FOOTBALL FOOTAGE FROM THE NFL FILMS LIBRARY AND THE LATEST SEGA CD SOUND AND TECHNOLOGY MAKE YOUR DREAM GAME COME TO LIFE.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>EA9A699F</hash>
		<image>./images/NFL's Greatest - San Francisco vs. Dallas 1978-1993 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/NFL's Greatest - San Francisco vs. Dallas 1978-1993 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/NFL's Greatest - San Francisco vs. Dallas 1978-1993 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/NFL's Greatest - San Francisco vs. Dallas 1978-1993 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12778" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./NHL '94 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NHL '94</name>
		<desc>DEPOIS DE SE ESTABELECER NAS PISTAS VIRTUAIS, A EA COMBINOU AS LICENÇAS NHL E NHLPA NA NHL '94, PERMITINDO QUE ELAS APRESENTASSEM AS 26 EQUIPES REAIS (INCLUINDO AMBAS AS EQUIPES DE EXPANSÃO) E OS JOGADORES DA NOVA TEMPORADA DA NHL PELA PRIMEIRA VEZ NA SÉRIE. ALÉM DAS LICENÇAS, A JOGABILIDADE PARA ESTA EDIÇÃO VÊ PELA PRIMEIRA VEZ A INCLUSÃO DO DEVASTADOR TIRO COM UM CRONÔMETRO, MAS PARA CONTINUAR (LITERALMENTE) EM XEQUE, OS DEFENSORES TAMBÉM APRESENTAM VERIFICAÇÕES CORPORAIS MAIS DIFÍCEIS, COM NOVAS ANIMAÇÕES. PARA UM DESAFIO ADICIONAL, OS JOGADORES TAMBÉM PODEM ESCOLHER CONTROLAR O GOLEIRO MANUALMENTE. UMA CARACTERÍSTICA POPULAR NAS EDIÇÕES ANTERIORES, A LUTA É COMPLETAMENTE REMOVIDA DO JOGO. OS MODOS DE JOGO INCLUEM JOGOS DE EXIBIÇÃO (OU "TEMPORADA REGULAR" NO JOGO), PLAYOFFS (MELHOR DE UM OU MELHOR DE SETE) E UM NOVO MODO DE DISPUTA.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Score Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>E6152985</hash>
		<image>./images/NHL '94 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/NHL '94 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/NHL '94 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/NHL '94 (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Night Trap (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12720" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Night Trap (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Night Trap (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>CINCO GAROTAS VÃO A UMA FESTA EM UMA BELA CASA À BEIRA DO LAGO. CINCO MENINAS DESAPARECEM SEM DEIXAR VESTÍGIOS ... AGORA, MAIS CINCO MENINAS VÃO LÁ, PARA PASSAR AS FÉRIAS COM OS MARTINS, OS DONOS DA CASA, EM PARTICULAR COM A ADORÁVEL SRTA. MARTIN. DESTA VEZ, VOCÊ NÃO DEVE DEIXÁ-LOS TER UMA MORTE HORRÍVEL! PORQUE "PESSOAS LEGAIS" ÀS VEZES PODEM SER ... SIM, ISSO MESMO - VAMPIROS. A CASA INTEIRA ESTÁ CHEIA DE ARMADILHAS, QUE SE DESTINAM A PEGAR AS POBRES MENINAS INOCENTES, PARA QUE OS VAMPIROS POSSAM SUGAR SEU SANGUE ... UGH. FELIZMENTE, O BRAVO AVENTUREIRO ESTÁ LÁ PARA DEIXAR DE SER CAÇADO E SE TORNAR UM CAÇADOR! DEFINA AS ARMADILHAS PARA QUE ELAS CAPTUREM OS VILÕES, USANDO UM TIMING PRECISO E UMA BOA ORGANIZAÇÃO.

NIGHT TRAP FOI O PRIMEIRO JOGO QUE USOU A TECNOLOGIA FMV (FULL-MOTION VIDEO) COM ATORES AO VIVO. EMBORA NÃO CONTENHA NUDEZ OU CENAS PARTICULARMENTE SANGRENTAS, FOI CONSIDERADO UM DOS PRIMEIROS JOGOS A TER UM CONTEÚDO MADURO.

A VERSÃO PARA SEGA CD 32X TRAZ MELHORIAS NA INTERFACE DO GAME E GRÁFICOS (FMV) COM IMAGENS MAIORES E RESOLUÇÃO APRIMORADA.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Night Trap (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Night Trap (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Night Trap (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Night Trap (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12720" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Night Trap (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Night Trap (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>CINCO GAROTAS VÃO A UMA FESTA EM UMA BELA CASA À BEIRA DO LAGO. CINCO MENINAS DESAPARECEM SEM DEIXAR VESTÍGIOS ... AGORA, MAIS CINCO MENINAS VÃO LÁ, PARA PASSAR AS FÉRIAS COM OS MARTINS, OS DONOS DA CASA, EM PARTICULAR COM A ADORÁVEL SRTA. MARTIN. DESTA VEZ, VOCÊ NÃO DEVE DEIXÁ-LOS TER UMA MORTE HORRÍVEL! PORQUE "PESSOAS LEGAIS" ÀS VEZES PODEM SER ... SIM, ISSO MESMO - VAMPIROS. A CASA INTEIRA ESTÁ CHEIA DE ARMADILHAS, QUE SE DESTINAM A PEGAR AS POBRES MENINAS INOCENTES, PARA QUE OS VAMPIROS POSSAM SUGAR SEU SANGUE ... UGH. FELIZMENTE, O BRAVO AVENTUREIRO ESTÁ LÁ PARA DEIXAR DE SER CAÇADO E SE TORNAR UM CAÇADOR! DEFINA AS ARMADILHAS PARA QUE ELAS CAPTUREM OS VILÕES, USANDO UM TIMING PRECISO E UMA BOA ORGANIZAÇÃO.

NIGHT TRAP FOI O PRIMEIRO JOGO QUE USOU A TECNOLOGIA FMV (FULL-MOTION VIDEO) COM ATORES AO VIVO. EMBORA NÃO CONTENHA NUDEZ OU CENAS PARTICULARMENTE SANGRENTAS, FOI CONSIDERADO UM DOS PRIMEIROS JOGOS A TER UM CONTEÚDO MADURO.

A VERSÃO PARA SEGA CD 32X TRAZ MELHORIAS NA INTERFACE DO GAME E GRÁFICOS (FMV) COM IMAGENS MAIORES E RESOLUÇÃO APRIMORADA.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Night Trap (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Night Trap (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Night Trap (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Night Trap (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12820" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Novastorm (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Novastorm</name>
		<desc>A BEHIND-THE-VIEW PERSPECTIVE OF A SHOOTER'S DREAM:  BLAST ENEMIES AGAINST A CINEMATIC BACKDROP.  KILL THE COMPUTER-CONTROLLED FIGHTERS BEFORE THEY TAKE OVER THE WORLD!

UNLIKE FIRST-GENERATION INTERACTIVE MOVIES WITH ACTION, NOVASTORM HAS HOOKS INTO THE ENVIRONMENT; IF YOU MOVE INTO THE PATH OF A PRE-RENDERED OBSTACLE AND IT "HITS" YOU, YOU TAKE DAMAGE, ETC.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>800AE536</hash>
		<image>./images/Novastorm (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Novastorm (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Novastorm (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Novastorm (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12793" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Panic! (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Panic!</name>
		<desc>A VIRUS HAS INFECTED THE WORLD'S COMPUTER NETWORK, WHICH EFFECTS ALL ELECTRONICAL DEVICES ON THE EARTH. HOWEVER, A SPECIAL PROGRAM CALLED "PANIC!" IS DESIGNED TO COUNTER THE EFFECTS OF THE VIRUS AND RESTORE THE NETWORK BACK TO WORKING ORDER. YOU PLAY SLAP THE BOY AND HIS SIDEKICK, STICK THE DOG(THEY'RE NOT ACTIONS, IT'S THEIR NAMES) WHO SET OUT TO RESTORE THE NETWORK BACK TO WORKING ORDER.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<hash>26041A78</hash>
		<image>./images/Panic! (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Panic! (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Panic! (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Panic! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="188996" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>PENN &amp; TELLER'S SMOKE AND MIRRORS É UM VIDEOGAME INÉDITO ENDOSSADO PELOS MÁGICOS PENN JILLETTE E TELLER. ELE FOI PLANEJADO PARA SER LANÇADO PARA O MEGA-CD DA SEGA EM ABRIL DE 1995, COM VERSÕES DE PC E 3DO SENDO LANÇADAS NO FINAL DO ANO, MAS FOI CANCELADA QUANDO A EDITORA, A ABSOLUTE ENTERTAINMENT, FOI À FALÊNCIA.

FRANK CIFALDI, EDITOR DO LOST LEVELS, TROUXE O JOGO AO PÚBLICO DEPOIS DE RECEBER UMA CÓPIA DE UM REVISOR DE REVISTA. É UMA COMPILAÇÃO DE MINIGAMES E UM JOGO DE PLATAFORMAS ESTRELANDO OS DOIS MÁGICOS, FEITOS PARA ENGANAR SEUS AMIGOS.

O JOGO FICOU FAMOSO DEVIDO À INCLUSÃO DO MINIJOGO "DESERT BUS". EM DESERT BUS, O JOGADOR DIRIGE UM ÔNIBUS PELOS ESTADOS UNIDOS, DE TUCSON, ARIZONA ATÉ LAS VEGAS, NEVADA, A UMA VELOCIDADE MÁXIMA EM TEMPO REAL DE 45 QUILÔMETROS POR HORA. ISSO SIGNIFICA QUE A JORNADA TEM OITO HORAS DE DURAÇÃO E, COMO O JOGO NÃO PODE SER PAUSADO, O JOGO É CONTÍNUO. NÃO HÁ NENHUM CENÁRIO PARA FALAR E NENHUM TRÁFEGO, E O ÔNIBUS SEMPRE SE MOVE LIGEIRAMENTE PARA A DIREITA, O QUE SIGNIFICA QUE O JOGADOR NÃO PODE DEIXAR O CONTROLE DENTRO DESSE TEMPO. A VIAGEM TAMBÉM É UMA LINHA PERFEITAMENTE RETA, E UMA VEZ QUE VOCÊ CHEGOU A LAS VEGAS, VOCÊ MARCARÁ UM PONTO E TERÁ A CHANCE DE FAZER A VIAGEM DE VOLTA.

O CONTADOR DE PONTOS AUMENTA PARA UM MÁXIMO DE 99, O QUE SIGNIFICA QUE A JOGABILIDADE É DE 41 DIAS. ESTE MINIGAME É USADO ANUALMENTE PARA O EVENTO DE CARIDADE "DESERT BUS FOR HOPE", QUE ARRECADOU US $ 233.678,47 NOS ÚLTIMOS TRÊS ANOS, LEVANDO AS PESSOAS A JOGAR NO DESERT BUS O MAIOR TEMPO POSSÍVEL. SUPOSTAMENTE, O TEMPO DE VIAGEM REALISTA FOI CONSTRUÍDO EM RESPOSTA DIRETA À CONTROVÉRSIA DO VIDEOGAME EM TORNO DE MUITOS JOGOS VIOLENTOS DA ÉPOCA.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineering</developer>
		<publisher>Absolute Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>281468BD</hash>
		<image>./images/Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Penn &amp; Teller - Smoke and Mirrors (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12755" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Pitfall: The Mayan Adventure</name>
		<desc>MANTENDO O ESTILO DO CLÁSSICO ORIGINAL, "THE MAYAN ADVENTURE" É UM JOGO DE PLATAFORMA 2D RECHEADO DE CAMINHOS, PASSAGENS SECRETAS E MUITOS PERIGOS E OBSTÁCULOS, QUE VÃO EXIGIR UM RACIOCÍNIO RÁPIDO E MUITA HABILIDADE POR PARTE DOS JOGADORES. A HISTÓRIA SE PASSA VÁRIOS ANOS APÓS AS AVENTURAS ORIGINAIS NO ATARI E DESTA VEZ PROTAGONIZADA PELO FILHO DO AUDACIOSO AVENTUREIRO, PITFALL HARRY JR. JUNTOS, OS DOIS RESOLVEM EXPLORAR A AMÉRICA CENTRAL EM BUSCA DOS TESOUROS PERDIDOS DOS MAIA. MAS ALGO TERRÍVEL ACONTECE: PITFALL HARRY É CAPTURADO PELO ESPÍRITO DE UM GUERREIRO MAIA DIABÓLICO CHAMADO DE ZAKELUA: O SENHOR DO MAL. AGORA ARMADO APENAS COM UM ESTILINGUE, O JOVEM HARRY JR. DEVE SE AVENTURAR NO DESCONHECIDO MUNDO PARA RESGATAR O SEU PAI. FELIZMENTE DURANTE O PERCURSO É POSSÍVEL ENCONTRAR ANTIGAS ARMAS MAIA QUE AJUDARÃO NOSSO HERÓI A COMBATER INIMIGOS E OBSTÁCULOS COMO BUMERANGUES E PEDRAS EXPLOSIVAS.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>90C7206B</hash>
		<image>./images/Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12807" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Popful Mail (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Popful Mail</name>
		<desc>TUDO COMEÇA EM UM MUNDO DE FANTASIA MEDIEVAL, MAIL UMA ELFA DE LONGOS CABELOS VERMELHOS É UMA CAÇADORA DE RECOMPENSAS E ESTÁ ATRÁS DE UM PERIGOSO VILÃO CHAMADO NUTS CRACKER, MAIL ESTÁ PROCURANDO NUTS EM UMA FLORESTA ATÉ QUE O ENCONTRA, MAIL ATACA NUTS MAS ELE ESCAPA DEIXANDO APENAS SUA "CABEÇA" EVITANDO QUE MAIL O PRENDA E RECEBA A RECOMPENSA PELA SUA PRISÃO, MUITO FRUSTRADA MAIL CHEGA EM UMA PEQUENA CIDADE ONDE TENTA A TODO CUSTO VENDER A "CABEÇA" DE NUTS CRACKER MAS NINGUÉM SE INTERESSA A DAR RECOMPENSA ALGUMA A ELA, CHEGANDO EM UMA LOJA DE EQUIPAMENTOS MAIL ENCONTRA UM CARTAZ DE PROCURA-SE COM O VALOR DE 2,000,000 GOLD DE UM MAGO CRIMINOSO CHAMADO MUTTONHEAD, ADMIRADA COM TAMANHO VALOR DA RECOMPENSA MAIL DECIDE PARTIR EM UMA AVENTURA PARA ACHAR E PRENDER MUTTONHEAD, O MAGO CRIMINOSO E PODER RECEBER A GRANDIOSA RECOMPENSA. ASSIM COMEÇA POPFUL MAIL!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Working Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Falcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A24405ED</hash>
		<image>./images/Popful Mail (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Popful Mail (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Popful Mail (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Popful Mail (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Power Factory featuring C+C Music Factory (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Factory featuring C+C Music Factory (USA)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Power Factory featuring C+C Music Factory (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Power Factory featuring C+C Music Factory (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Power Factory featuring C+C Music Factory (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Power Factory featuring C+C Music Factory (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12816" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Power Monger (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Monger</name>
		<desc>POWERMONGER TAKES THE BASIC DESIGN AND CONCEPTS OF BULLFROG'S PREVIOUS GAME POPULOUS, AND PLACES IT IN A WAR CONTEXT. THE GAME CAST THE PLAYER AS A DISPOSSESSED WARLORD PLUNDERING HIS WAY THROUGH 195 TERRITORIES ON THE WAY TO WORLD CONQUEST. SEVERAL OTHER LEADERS HAVE THE SAME GOAL.

THE GAMEWORLD IS NOW MADE UP OF POLYGONS, SO THE VIEW CAN BE ROTATED AND MOVED WITH GREATER FREEDOM THAN POPULOUS. TRADE, DIPLOMACY, INVENTIONS, AND SCORCHED EARTH INVASIONS ALL PLAY A KEY ROLE IN HOW THE PLAYER PROGRESSED THROUGH THE GAME.  TWO-PLAYER GAMES VIA MODEM LINKS ARE AVAILABLE ON COMPUTER VERSIONS.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DAFEA843</hash>
		<image>./images/Power Monger (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Power Monger (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Power Monger (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Power Monger (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12721" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Prince of Persia (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<desc>THE GRAND VIZIER JAFFAR HAS THROWN YOU INTO A DARK DUNGEON AND PLANS TO MARRY THE GIRL OF YOUR DREAMS IN AN HOUR. YOU'RE NOT GOING TO LET THAT HAPPEN ARE YOU? TRY TO ESCAPE FROM THE DUNGEON, TAKE OUT JAFFAR'S GUARDS, FIND YOUR WAY THROUGH THE SULTAN'S PALACE AND DEFEAT JAFFAR HIMSELF. NOW GO, YOU'VE GOT 60 MINUTES!

PRINCE OF PERSIA IS A 2D PLATFORMER WITH RUN AND JUMP GAMEPLAY. YOUR HERO MUST AVOID DEADLY TRAPS, SOLVE SOME SIMPLE PUZZLES AND ENGAGE IN SWORD FIGHTS WITH THE GUARDS. THE PLAYER HAS AN INFINITE AMOUNT OF LIVES, BUT HAS TO RESTART AT THE BEGINNING OF A LEVEL EACH TIME HE DIES, AND MUST COMPLETE THE GAME WITHIN AN HOUR. AN ESPECIALLY NOTEWORTHY ASPECT OF THE GAME IS THE VERY FLUENT ANIMATION OF YOUR CHARACTER.

THE GAME BOY COLOR AND SNES VERSIONS OF THE GAME FEATURE ADDITIONAL LEVELS AND NEW ENEMIES. THE GENESIS VERSION HAS A NEW INTRO AND AN ALTERED SET OF GRAPHICS BUT THE LEVEL LAYOUT REMAINS ALMOST IDENTICAL TO THAT OF THE ORIGINAL.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>49A4E3BC</hash>
		<image>./images/Prince of Persia (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Prince of Persia (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Prince of Persia (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Prince of Persia (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12821" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Prize Fighter (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>PRIZE FIGHTER IS A FMV BOXING GAME WHICH PUTS THE PLAYER IN THE BODY  OF "THE KID" AGAINST FOUR OPPONENTS: HONEYBOY FERNANDEZ, MEGA JOE FALCO, REX HAWKINS, AND THE ULTIMATE CHALLENGE, NUKE "THE DUKE" JOHNSON, DIVIDED OVER TWO CDS.

WHILE THE GAME REQUIRES A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT APPROACH THAN SPRITE OR POLYGONAL GAMES, THE TACTICS ARE STILL THE SAME - JAB, PUNCH AND DELIVER UPPERCUTS WHEN THE OPPONENT HAS HIS DEFENSES DOWN, AND BLOCK AND BOB AS HE MAKES HIS MOVES. AFTER A WIN THE PLAYER CAN IMPROVE HIS LEFT AND RIGHT GLOVE ABILITIES AND STAMINA BY ASSIGNING "POWER POINTS" TO EACH AREA.

THE ONLY SPRITES VISIBLE DURING THE BOUTS ARE THE PLAYER GLOVES AND THE HEALTH INDICATORS - THE BOXERS AND THE REST OF THE RING ARE BLACK AND WHITE FMV. LIKE WITH OTHER FMV GAMES, THE PLAYER CAN ENABLE  TIPS, WHICH INDICATES TO HIT CERTAIN BUTTTONS WHEN REQUIRED.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>45ED9D8B</hash>
		<image>./images/Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12821" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Prize Fighter (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>PRIZE FIGHTER IS A FMV BOXING GAME WHICH PUTS THE PLAYER IN THE BODY  OF "THE KID" AGAINST FOUR OPPONENTS: HONEYBOY FERNANDEZ, MEGA JOE FALCO, REX HAWKINS, AND THE ULTIMATE CHALLENGE, NUKE "THE DUKE" JOHNSON, DIVIDED OVER TWO CDS.

WHILE THE GAME REQUIRES A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT APPROACH THAN SPRITE OR POLYGONAL GAMES, THE TACTICS ARE STILL THE SAME - JAB, PUNCH AND DELIVER UPPERCUTS WHEN THE OPPONENT HAS HIS DEFENSES DOWN, AND BLOCK AND BOB AS HE MAKES HIS MOVES. AFTER A WIN THE PLAYER CAN IMPROVE HIS LEFT AND RIGHT GLOVE ABILITIES AND STAMINA BY ASSIGNING "POWER POINTS" TO EACH AREA.

THE ONLY SPRITES VISIBLE DURING THE BOUTS ARE THE PLAYER GLOVES AND THE HEALTH INDICATORS - THE BOXERS AND THE REST OF THE RING ARE BLACK AND WHITE FMV. LIKE WITH OTHER FMV GAMES, THE PLAYER CAN ENABLE  TIPS, WHICH INDICATES TO HIT CERTAIN BUTTTONS WHEN REQUIRED.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FF943C5B</hash>
		<image>./images/Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Prize Fighter (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12782" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Puggsy (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Puggsy</name>
		<desc>PUGGSY IS A PLATFORM GAME WITH A COMBINATION OF ACTION AND PUZZLE-SOLVING ELEMENTS. YOU CONTROL THE THE CREATURE PUGGSY, WHO HAS CRASH LANDED ON AN ALIEN PLANET AND HAD HIS SPACESHIP STOLEN. YOUR GOAL IS FIND THE SPACESHIP SO YOU CAN GET OFF THE PLANET AND RETURN HOME.  TO DO THIS, YOU WILL NEED TO MAKE YOUR WAY FROM THE START TO THE EXIT OF NUMEROUS LEVELS WHICH TAKE PLACE IN A VARIETY OF ENVIRONMENTS. THROUGHOUT EACH LEVEL ARE A VARIETY OF OBJECTS WHICH YOU CAN PICK UP; ON MANY OF THE LEVELS YOU WILL NEED TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO USE THE OBJECTS AVAILABLE TO YOU IN ORDER TO REACH THE EXIT. SOME OBJECTS CAN USED (LIKE A GUN OR KEYS), AND OBJECTS MAY BE THROWN, MOVED AROUND AND STACKED. OF COURSE, EACH LEVEL WILL ALSO HAVE A VARIETY OF BAD GUYS WANDERING ABOUT WHICH WILL COST PUGGSY ONE OF HIS LIVES IF HE'S CAUGHT. ON YOUR QUEST THERE WILL ALSO BE SIX EVIL GUARDIANS WHICH WILL NEED TO BE DEFEATED BEFORE YOU GET YOUR SPACESHIP BACK!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Traveller's Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>38D13142</hash>
		<image>./images/Puggsy (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Puggsy (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Puggsy (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Puggsy (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12813" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Racing Aces (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Racing Aces</name>
		<desc>THE COLD WAR HAS ENDED. BIG DEFENSE CONTRACTORS, SPECIFICALLY THE ONES THAT MAKE FIGHTER PLANES, ORGANIZE A NEW SPORT. PILOTS FLY PLANES OF VARIOUS HISTORICAL SIGNIFICANCE IN LOW ALTITUDE RACES FOR BIG PRIZES.

RACING ACES PUTS YOU BEHIND THE STICK OF WORLD WAR 1, WORLD WAR 2, AND MODERN DAY FIGHTING AIRCRAFT.  EACH COMPETITION IS A DOGFIGHT AS MUCH AS A RACE, AND YOU WILL HAVE TO GUN DOWN YOUR ENEMIES TO WIN. THE TRACKS ARE LITTERED WITH POWER UP BALLOONS TO GIVE YOU EXTRA WEAPONS AND SPEED.

THE RACES ARE VIEWED FROM A BEHIND-THE-PLANE PERSPECTIVE, AND THE COURSES ARE DRAWN IN 3D USING POLYGONS.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>49300A14</hash>
		<image>./images/Racing Aces (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Racing Aces (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Racing Aces (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Racing Aces (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12834" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Radical Rex (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Radical Rex</name>
		<desc>RADICAL REX É UM TIRANOSSAURO QUE ESPIRRA FOGO EM UM SKATE E TEM QUE SALVAR A CORRIDA DE DINOSSAUROS SOB O FEITIÇO DE UMA CRIATURA DO MAL. O JOGO CONSISTE EM 10 NÍVEIS DEFINIDOS NA IDADE PRÉ-HISTÓRICA. RADICAL REX PODE USAR UM SKATE OU DESCER COLINAS, PULAR, CHUTAR E ESPIRRAR FOGO. OS INIMIGOS MAIS DUROS PRECISAM DE MÚLTIPLOS ATAQUES E O REX PRECISA CHUTÁ-LOS MAIS UMA VEZ PARA DESTRUÍ-LOS OU USAR SEU GRITO (ATINGE TUDO NA TELA). AO JOGAR, REX COLETA OVOS, SAÚDE, POWER-UPS PARA SEU ESPIRRO DE FOGO E RECARGAS DE GRITOS. OS PONTOS DE VERIFICAÇÃO SÃO MOSTRADOS COMO TOCHAS QUE PRECISAM SER CARREGADAS COM FOGO. DEPOIS DE CADA NÍVEL, HÁ UMA SEQUÊNCIA SEMELHANTE A BOMBERMAN PARA GANHAR UMA CONTINUAÇÃO EXTRA. OS INIMIGOS INCLUEM MOSCAS, TARTARUGAS, SAPOS E TODOS OS TIPOS DE DINOSSAUROS.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D35AE45E</hash>
		<image>./images/Radical Rex (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Radical Rex (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Radical Rex (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Radical Rex (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97374" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./RDF Global Conflict (USA).chd</path>
		<name>RDF: Global Conflict</name>
		<desc>USING A THRILLING COMBINATION OF 3D RENDERING AND EXPLOSIVE COMBAT ACTION, RDF: GLOBAL CONFLICT IS AN INTERACTIVE MULTIMEDIA EXPERIENCE THAT PUSHES THE SEGA CD SYSTEM TO ITS LIMITS! AS A TANK COMMANDER IN THE RDF - THE ELITE RAPID DEPLOYMENT FORCE - YOU'LL TEST YOUR BATTLE SAVVY IN A REALISTIC VIRTUAL WORLD, FROM THE WAR-TORN COUNTRYSIDE OF EASTERN EUROPE TO ALASKA'S DESOLATE TUNDRA! BUT WATCH YOUR BACK! AN EVIL GENIUS MAY POSE A THREAT NOT ONLY TO THE TEAM - BUT TO ALL OF MANKIND!</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineering</developer>
		<publisher>Absolute Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1AC9F810</hash>
		<image>./images/RDF Global Conflict (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/RDF Global Conflict (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/RDF Global Conflict (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/RDF Global Conflict (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12804" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Revenge of the Ninja (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Revenge of the Ninja</name>
		<desc>THE STORY TAKES PLACE IN JAPAN, YOU PLAY AS HAYATE, A YOUNG UP AND COMING NINJA WARRIOR OUT TO STOP THE EVIL OF LOUGI AND HIS ARMY OF GHOULS AND GOBLINS. YOU ARE OUT TO AVENGE YOUR FATHER'S DEATH AS WELL AS THE EMPEROR AND RESCUE YOUR GIRLFRIEND FROM THE CLUTCHES OF EVIL AND BRING AN END TO THE TERROR VISITED UPON YOUR LANDS.

SOME OF THE VILLIANS YOU FACE ARE MARCO KILLMORE (A HALF MAN, HALF EAGLE SAMURAI WARRIOR), ZALLEN (A DISGRACED SAMURAI WARRIOR OUT TO DESTROY HAYATE), VENGOR (A STONE SHIVA-TYPE CHARACTER), DESFAL (A MEDUSA-LIKE WOMAN), DESTROYER MPK (A POSSESSED COLLECTION OF SAMURAI ARMOR) AND OF COURSE THE EVIL SAMURAI KNIGHT HIMSELF, LOUGI.

TO PLAY THE GAME YOU MUST PRESS THE CORRESPONDING BUTTONS ON THE SCREEN AT A CERTAIN TIME, SUCH AS PRESSING LEFT TO GO LEFT OR POSSIBLY TO AVOID A ENEMIES WEAPON OR PRESSING ONE OF THE REGULAR BUTTONS TO DRAW YOUR WEAPON AND ATTACK A CERTAIN ENEMY, MUCH LIKE DRAGON'S LAIR AND SPACE ACE. THERE ARE THREE DIFFICULTY LEVELS, EACH ONE GIVING YOU A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF TIME TO PRESS THE BUTTONS, THE HARDEST SETTING GIVING YOU THE LEAST AMOUNT OF TIME.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wolf Team</developer>
		<publisher>Renovation Products</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>266DE8FF</hash>
		<image>./images/Revenge of the Ninja (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Revenge of the Ninja (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Revenge of the Ninja (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Revenge of the Ninja (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="102821" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Revengers of Vengeance (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Revengers of Vengeance</name>
		<desc>REVENGERS OF VENGEANCE IS A COMBINATION OF RPG, VERTICAL SHOOTER, AND FIGHTING GAME WITH A FANTASY/ANIME STYLE. THERE ARE TEN AVAILABLE CHARACTERS, EACH WITH THEIR OWN ANIMATED BACKSTORY AND FIGHTING TECHNIQUES. YOU MUST CHOOSE A HERO AND GUIDE THEIR STATS TO CREATE A FORMIDABLE FIGHTER CAPABLE OF TAKING DOWN THE DEVIL KING AND FREEING THE LAND.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micronet</developer>
		<publisher>Extreme Entertainment Group</publisher>
		<hash>B326E077</hash>
		<image>./images/Revengers of Vengeance (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Revengers of Vengeance (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Revengers of Vengeance (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Revengers of Vengeance (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12831" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rise of the Dragon (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Rise of the Dragon</name>
		<desc>A FUTURISTIC ADVENTURE GAME THAT BORROWS GRAPHICAL ELEMENTS FROM BLADE RUNNER (IN FACT, THE TITLE CHARACTER'S NAME IS "BLADE HUNTER").  YOU MUST FIND OUT WHAT IS KILLING--BY HORRIBLE, SPONTANEOUS MUTATION--INHABITANTS OF THE CITY, BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.  AN ORIENTAL CULT, DRUGS, AND STREET INFORMANTS ARE AMONG THE PLACES YOU FIND CLUES.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Dynamix</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B4D6CBBA</hash>
		<image>./images/Rise of the Dragon (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Rise of the Dragon (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Rise of the Dragon (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rise of the Dragon (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12746" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Road Avenger (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Road Avenger</name>
		<desc>ROAD AVENGER DATES FROM THE ERA WHEN INTERACTIVE MOVIES (E.G. DRAGON'S LAIR, ESCAPE FROM CYBERCITY, TIME GAL...) WITH FILM-QUALITY GRAPHICS, BUT LIMITED PLAYER MOVEMENT, WERE HIGHLY POPULAR.

PLAYERS ASSUME THE ROLE OF AN ANGRY COP ON A WILD RIDE AS HE PURSUES A GANG OF BIKERS WHO KILLED HIS WIFE. PLAYERS NEED TO RACE THROUGH ONCOMING TRAFFIC, SQUEEZE BETWEEN TRUCKS, TRASH MOTORCYCLES AND STEER THROUGH LOTS OF EXPLOSIONS. THE ONLY THING NEEDED ARE QUICK REFLEXES TO FOLLOW THE INSTRUCTIONS ON THE SCREEN (WITH AN INCREASING DIFFICULTY) IN ORDER TO KEEP THE ANIMATION GOING.

THE ACTION IS SHOWN FROM A FIRST-PERSON VIEW AND FAST-PACED, WHILE STILL MAINTAINING SMOOTH AND DETAILED ANIME DRAWN GRAPHICS.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wolf Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>07F7F7E0</hash>
		<image>./images/Road Avenger (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Road Avenger (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Road Avenger (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Road Avenger (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12722" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Road Rash (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Road Rash</name>
		<desc>THIS IS A REMAKE OF THE ORIGINAL ROAD RASH FROM THE EARLY NINETIES. FOR THOSE WHO HAVE NOT PLAYED THE ORIGINAL, YOU ARE COMPETING AGAINST THIRTEEN OTHER "ROAD RASHERS" WHO WILL STOP AT NOTHING TO WIN 1ST, 2ND, OR 3RD PLACE. DURING THE RACE, YOU HAVE TWO OPTIONS AVAILABLE TO YOU: YOU CAN EITHER DO YOUR BEST TO CROSS THE FINISH LINE, OR USE YOUR WEAPON TO BRING THE RASHERS TO THE GROUND IF THEY ARE GIVING YOU TROUBLE. IF YOU DO THE LATTER, YOUR OPPONENTS WILL DO THE SAME TO YOU DURING THE NEXT RACE THAT TAKES PLACE. 

THERE ARE FIVE CIRCUITS TO RACE: THE CITY, THE PENINSULA, PACIFIC HIGHWAY, SIERRA NEVADA, AND NAPA VALLEY. SOME OF THESE CIRCUITS ARE DANGEROUS. AS WELL AS THE OBSTACLES AND TRAFFIC THAT YOU ENCOUNTER ALONG THE WAY, THERE ARE ALSO COPS DRIVING ON BIKES WHO WILL ARREST YOU IF YOU HAPPEN TO CRASH OR STOP YOUR BIKE NEAR THEM, AND YOU HAVE TO PAY A FINE IN ORDER TO GET IN ANY MORE RACES. YOUR BIKE WILL BE WRECKED IF YOU CRASH TOO MANY TIMES, AND YOU HAVE TO PAY FOR DAMAGES, BUT THE AMOUNT YOU HAVE TO PAY DEPENDS ON THE BIKE THAT YOU ARE RIDING. ONCE YOU HAVE COMPLETED THE FIRST FIVE CIRCUITS, YOU HAVE TO RACE THEM AGAIN ANOTHER FOUR TIMES - BUT AT A MUCH MORE DIFFICULT LEVEL. MANAGE TO WIN ALL FIVE CIRCUITS ON ALL LEVELS, AND YOU WIN THE ROAD RASH CUP.

THERE ARE ABOUT FIVE BIKES TO CHOOSE FROM, WHICH ARE DIVIDED INTO THREE GROUPS. RAT, SPORT, AND SUPER. YOU START THE FIRST LEVEL WITH A RAT BIKE, BUT AS YOU PROCEED THROUGH THE LEVELS, IT IS IMPORTANT TO PICK BIKES FROM A DIFFERENT BIKE CLASS.

IF YOU HAVE NO PLANS TO WIN THE ROAD RASH CUP, YOU CAN CHOOSE THE GAME'S THRASH MODE. THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THIS AND THE OTHER MODE IS THAT THERE IS NO MONEY INVOLVED (IE: YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED TO BUY BIKES), AND YOU ARE COMPETING AGAINST FOURTEEN OPPONENTS. AND IF YOU WRECK YOUR BIKE OR YOU GET BUSTED, YOU HAVE TO START ALL OVER AGAIN. REGARDLESS OF THE MODE YOU PICK, YOU WILL ALWAYS START IN THE LAST PLACE.

THE REMAKE ALSO CONTAINS FMV MOVIES THAT USUALLY DEPICT THE OUTCOME OF THE RACES, AS WELL AS LIMITED SONGS PERFORMED BY VARIOUS RECORDING ARTISTS, INCLUDING SOUNDGARDEN, THERAPY?, MONSTER MAGNET, AND SWERVEDRIVER. THESE SONGS CAN BE CHANGED ON-THE-FLY VIA THE GAME'S OPTIONS MENU.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>5C2946F2</hash>
		<image>./images/Road Rash (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Road Rash (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Road Rash (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Road Rash (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12756" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Robo Aleste (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Robo Aleste</name>
		<desc>OVERHEAD SHOOTER BASED IN JAPAN. THE BLOODTHIRSTY CHUGOKO WARLORDS OF THE WEST HAVE RULED AND RAVAGED THE ONCE-SUPREME ODA CLAN. TIME TO GET YOUR REVENGE. THIS IS AN OVERHEAD SHOOTER WITH LARGE BOSSES AND MASSIVE POWER-UPS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2EE74D1B</hash>
		<image>./images/Robo Aleste (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Robo Aleste (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Robo Aleste (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Robo Aleste (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58725" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Samurai Shodown (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown</name>
		<desc>IN EARLY JAPAN, A MAN NAMED SHIRO TOKISADA AMAKUSA PREACHES A HERETIC RELIGION. LITTLE DOES ANYONE KNOW THAT AMAKUSA IS REALLY A SERVANT OF THE EVIL AMBROSIA, WHO TOOK OVER AMAKUSA'S BODY. AMBROSIA WISHES TO SHROUD THE WORLD IN DARKNESS.
NOW, CHOOSE BETWEEN 12 WARRIORS (AND 3 BONUS CHARACTERS) TO FIGHT FOR THE HONOR OF DESTROYING AMAKUSA, AND FULFILLING A MISSION.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>JVC Musical Industries</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>E1517A95</hash>
		<image>./images/Samurai Shodown (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Samurai Shodown (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Samurai Shodown (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Samurai Shodown (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12712" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sega Classics Arcade Collection 4-in-1 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sega Classics Arcade Collection 4 in 1</name>
		<desc>SOLD ONLY IN A PACK-IN WITH THE SEGA MEGA-CD, THE COLLECTION ADDED SUPER MONACO GP BUT WAS OTHERWISE IDENTICAL TO THE 4-IN-1, INCLUDING THE VERSION OF REVENGE OF SHINOBI INCLUDED.

GAMES:
COLUMNS
GOLDEN AXE
REVENGE OF SHINOBI
STREETS OF RAGE
SUPER MONACO GP</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./images/Sega Classics Arcade Collection 4-in-1 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sega Classics Arcade Collection 4-in-1 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sega Classics Arcade Collection 4-in-1 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sega Classics Arcade Collection 4-in-1 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12712" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sega Classics Arcade Collection 5-in-1 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sega Classics Arcade Collection 5 in 1</name>
		<desc>SOLD ONLY IN A PACK-IN WITH THE SEGA MEGA-CD, THE COLLECTION ADDED SUPER MONACO GP BUT WAS OTHERWISE IDENTICAL TO THE 5-IN-1, INCLUDING THE VERSION OF REVENGE OF SHINOBI INCLUDED.

GAMES:
COLUMNS
GOLDEN AXE
REVENGE OF SHINOBI
STREETS OF RAGE
SUPER MONACO GP</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>6C2FD104</hash>
		<image>./images/Sega Classics Arcade Collection 5-in-1 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sega Classics Arcade Collection 5-in-1 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sega Classics Arcade Collection 5-in-1 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sega Classics Arcade Collection 5-in-1 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12822" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sewer Shark (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sewer Shark</name>
		<desc>SEWER SHARK IS AN FMV-BASED SHOOTER, AND ONE OF THE FIRST GAMES RELEASED FOR THE SEGA CD.  YOU MOVE A CROSSHAIR AROUND THE SCREEN AND SHOOT TARGETS.  OCCASIONALLY, YOU CAN ALSO CHOOSE TO CHANGE DIRECTIONS AT FIXED POINTS.

OF COURSE THE REAL ATTRACTION IN A GAME LIKE THIS IS THE STORY.  IN THE FUTURE, MAYBE IN THE YEAR 2000, PEOPLE WILL BE FORCED TO MOVE UNDERGROUND AND LIVE IN TUNNELS.  UNFORTUNATELY, THESE TUNNELS ARE INFESTED WITH MUTATED RAT / ALLIGATOR CREATURES KNOWN AS "RATIGATORS."  YOU ARE PILOT OF A SEWER SHARK, A CRAFT DESIGNED TO NAVIGATE THE SEWERS AND RID THEM OF RATIGATORS.  IT'S A DANGEROUS JOB, BUT IF YOU CLEAR OUT ENOUGH VERMIN YOU CAN WIN A ONE-WAY TRIP TO SOLAR CITY AND SUNNY BEACHES.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Electronic Publishing</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F6D0DAEA</hash>
		<image>./images/Sewer Shark (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sewer Shark (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sewer Shark (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sewer Shark (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12752" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Shadow of the Beast II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shadow of the Beast II</name>
		<desc>ESSENCIALMENTE, UM SIDE-ON SCROLLING BEAT 'EM UP, MAS COM UM ENREDO ÉPICO E QUEBRA-CABEÇAS.

A INTRODUÇÃO, AGORA UM CLÁSSICO DO AMIGA, MOSTRA O MAGO ZELEK SEQUESTRANDO SUA IRMÃZINHA E O OBJETIVO DO JOGO É RESGATÁ-LA. NO CAMINHO, UMA VARIEDADE DE QUEBRA-CABEÇAS, SUB-QUESTS E MONSTROS REALMENTE DESAGRADÁVEIS PERSEGUEM CADA PASSO SEU.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D1B379CF</hash>
		<image>./images/Shadow of the Beast II (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Shadow of the Beast II (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Shadow of the Beast II (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Shadow of the Beast II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12785" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sherlock Holmes: Consulting Detective Vol. I</name>
		<desc>SHERLOCK HOLMES: CONSULTING DETECTIVE IS A FULL MOTION VIDEO VIDEO GAME BASED ON A TABLETOP GAME-GAMEBOOK HYBRID WHICH HAD THE SAME NAME. THE GAME USES LIVE ACTORS AND SETS AS THE PLAYER CONTROLS SHERLOCK HOLMES AND HIS LONGTIME PARTNER DR. WATSON, TRYING TO SOLVE THREE SEPARATE CRIMES BY VISITING VARIOUS LOCATIONS, LISTENING TO THE DIALOGUE, READING THE INCLUDED MOCK LONDON NEWSPAPERS, AND, WHEN THE PLAYER GETS ENOUGH EVIDENCE, ANSWERING THE JUDGE'S QUESTIONS.

AT THE BEGINNING OF EACH CASE A FULL MOTION VIDEO CLIP DEPICTS HOLMES AND WATSON MEETING A CLIENT AND LEARNING A FEW BACKGROUND CLUES ABOUT THE CASE. THEN THE PLAYER MUST VISIT A PARTICULAR LOCATION OR PERSON, READ THE LONDON NEWSPAPERS FOR CLUES OR ASK ONE OF THE YOUNG BAKER STREET IRREGULARS TO INVESTIGATE. THE OBJECT OF EACH CASE IS TO GATHER ENOUGH CLUES IN THE SHORTEST TIME POSSIBLE, THEN GO BEFORE A JUDGE WHO WILL THEN ASK THE PLAYER TO ANSWER THE IMPORTANT QUESTIONS ABOUT THE CASE. IF THE PLAYER IS SUCCESSFUL, A FULL MOTION VIDEO CLIP WILL TAKE THE PLAYER BACK TO HOLMES' AND WATSON'S STUDY WHERE THEY WILL REVIEW THE EVENTS THAT TRANSPIRED, AND DR. WATSON WILL INFORM THE PLAYER OF HIS OR HER SCORE, BASED ON THE LENGTH OF TIME IT TOOK TO SOLVE THE CASE.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Icom</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12823" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Sherlock Holmes: Consulting Detective Vol. II (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>THE SAME STRUCTURE BRINGS A FAMILIAR LOOK, INVITING TO CHANNEL ALL ATTENTION TO THE TASK OF SOLVING MYSTERIES: YOUR INTELLIGENCE, SKILLS AND PATIENCE ARE REQUIRED TO FIND CLUES BY LISTENING TO PEOPLE, OBSERVING DETAILS, OR EVEN READING THE LONDON TIMES - BUT DON'T LET YOURSELF BE MISGUIDED BY A WRONG HINT.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>608EDABA</hash>
		<image>./images/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12823" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Sherlock Holmes: Consulting Detective Vol. II (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>THE SAME STRUCTURE BRINGS A FAMILIAR LOOK, INVITING TO CHANNEL ALL ATTENTION TO THE TASK OF SOLVING MYSTERIES: YOUR INTELLIGENCE, SKILLS AND PATIENCE ARE REQUIRED TO FIND CLUES BY LISTENING TO PEOPLE, OBSERVING DETAILS, OR EVEN READING THE LONDON TIMES - BUT DON'T LET YOURSELF BE MISGUIDED BY A WRONG HINT.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1AC89E12</hash>
		<image>./images/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective Vol. II (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12738" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Shining Force CD (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shining Force CD</name>
		<desc>SHINING FORCE CD É A COMPILAÇÃO DE DOIS JOGOS PARA GAME GEAR: SHINING FORCE GAIDEN E SHINING FORCE GAIDEN II - SWORD OF HAJYA. AMBOS FORAM REFEITOS COM A QUALIDADE DE UM 16 BITS, GRAFICAMENTE FALANDO, MAS COM SONS CRISTALINOS PROPORCIONADOS PELO SEGA CD. O JOGO É DIVIDIDO EM 4 "LIVROS" QUE PODEM SER JOGADOS EM SEQUENCIA OU SEPARADAMENTE. OS DOIS PRIMEIROS LIVROS SÃO OS DOIS JOGOS PARA GAME GEAR, JÁ OS DOIS ÚLTIMOS SÃO CENÁRIOS FEITOS EXCLUSIVAMENTE PARA O SEGA CD.NNA HISTÓRIA OCORRE 20 ANOS APÓS OS ACONTECIMENTOS DE SHINING FORCE I. ANRI AGORA É A RAINHA DE GUARDIANA, FORTEMENTE ACESSORADA POR NINGUÉM MENOS QUE LOWE E KEN, PERSONAGENS DO PRIMEIRO GAME TAMBÉM.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>651AFECD</hash>
		<image>./images/Shining Force CD (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Shining Force CD (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Shining Force CD (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Shining Force CD (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12742" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Silpheed (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Silpheed</name>
		<desc>SILPHEED FOR THE SEGA CD IS A SHOOT-'EM-UP SEQUEL TO THE PC TITLE OF THE SAME NAME. GAMEPLAY IS SIMILAR: THIS IS BASICALLY A 2D SHOOTER WITH 3D GRAPHICS.  YOU MOVE YOUR SHIP IN A 2D PLANE THAT REACHES INTO THE SCREEN, KIND OF LIKE A PINBALL TABLE. THE SEGA CD VERSION OF SILPHEED USES PRE-RENDERED VIDEO FOR THE BACKDROPS, AND FILLED POLYGON GRAPHICS FOR THE PLAYER SHIP AND ENEMIES. 

THE STORY HERE IS TYPICAL FOR A GAME OF THIS TYPE. THE CENTRAL COMPUTER SYSTEM CONTROLLING THE GALAXY NETWORK HAS BEEN HACKED BY TERRORISTS.  THE TERRORISTS ARE USING THE COMPUTER TO ATTACK COLONY PLANETS THROUGHOUT THE SYSTEM.  YOU ARE THE GALAXY UNION'S LAST RESORT: YOU MUST FIGHT YOUR WAY ACROSS 11 STAGES TO REACH EARTH, AND RE-TAKE CONTROL OF THE COMPUTER.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Game Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>89F72E5E</hash>
		<image>./images/Silpheed (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Silpheed (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Silpheed (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Silpheed (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>SLAM CITY WITH SCOTTIE PIPPEN IS A FULL-MOTION-VIDEO BASKETBALL GAME. IT USES PROPRIETARY TECHNOLOGY TO ALLOW SWITCHING FROM ONE SCENE TO ANOTHER WITHOUT LAG, WHICH ALLOWS FOR SMOOTHER INTERACTIVE VIDEO.

GAMEPLAY IS RELATIVELY SIMPLE, USING LITTLE MORE THAN ARROW KEYS, AND IS VERY DIFFERENT FROM ANY OTHER BASKETBALL SIMULATION. BASKETBALL IS MERELY THE SUBJECT FOR THE GAME'S PLOT, INVOLVING THE NEW-GUY, ACE (THE PLAYER), AND A HOST OF OTHER CHARACTERS, BASKETBALL PLAYERS OR JUST SPECTATORS, ALL WITH DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES. IT'S BASICALLY PLAY ONE-ON-ONE ON A WAREHOUSE COURT AND CLIMB THE "LADDERS" UNTIL YOU EARN ENOUGH RESPECT TO PLAY AGAINST SCOTTIE PIPPEN.

THE GAME FEATURES A TOTAL OF 13 CHARACTERS, 5 OF WHICH THE PLAYER HAS AN OPTION TO PLAY AGAINST, ALL OF WHICH ARE PLAYED BY REAL ACTORS.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>882B0F88</hash>
		<image>./images/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>SLAM CITY WITH SCOTTIE PIPPEN IS A FULL-MOTION-VIDEO BASKETBALL GAME. IT USES PROPRIETARY TECHNOLOGY TO ALLOW SWITCHING FROM ONE SCENE TO ANOTHER WITHOUT LAG, WHICH ALLOWS FOR SMOOTHER INTERACTIVE VIDEO.

GAMEPLAY IS RELATIVELY SIMPLE, USING LITTLE MORE THAN ARROW KEYS, AND IS VERY DIFFERENT FROM ANY OTHER BASKETBALL SIMULATION. BASKETBALL IS MERELY THE SUBJECT FOR THE GAME'S PLOT, INVOLVING THE NEW-GUY, ACE (THE PLAYER), AND A HOST OF OTHER CHARACTERS, BASKETBALL PLAYERS OR JUST SPECTATORS, ALL WITH DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES. IT'S BASICALLY PLAY ONE-ON-ONE ON A WAREHOUSE COURT AND CLIMB THE "LADDERS" UNTIL YOU EARN ENOUGH RESPECT TO PLAY AGAINST SCOTTIE PIPPEN.

THE GAME FEATURES A TOTAL OF 13 CHARACTERS, 5 OF WHICH THE PLAYER HAS AN OPTION TO PLAY AGAINST, ALL OF WHICH ARE PLAYED BY REAL ACTORS.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D04F2724</hash>
		<image>./images/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 3).chd</path>
		<name>Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (Disc 3)</name>
		<desc>SLAM CITY WITH SCOTTIE PIPPEN IS A FULL-MOTION-VIDEO BASKETBALL GAME. IT USES PROPRIETARY TECHNOLOGY TO ALLOW SWITCHING FROM ONE SCENE TO ANOTHER WITHOUT LAG, WHICH ALLOWS FOR SMOOTHER INTERACTIVE VIDEO.

GAMEPLAY IS RELATIVELY SIMPLE, USING LITTLE MORE THAN ARROW KEYS, AND IS VERY DIFFERENT FROM ANY OTHER BASKETBALL SIMULATION. BASKETBALL IS MERELY THE SUBJECT FOR THE GAME'S PLOT, INVOLVING THE NEW-GUY, ACE (THE PLAYER), AND A HOST OF OTHER CHARACTERS, BASKETBALL PLAYERS OR JUST SPECTATORS, ALL WITH DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES. IT'S BASICALLY PLAY ONE-ON-ONE ON A WAREHOUSE COURT AND CLIMB THE "LADDERS" UNTIL YOU EARN ENOUGH RESPECT TO PLAY AGAINST SCOTTIE PIPPEN.

THE GAME FEATURES A TOTAL OF 13 CHARACTERS, 5 OF WHICH THE PLAYER HAS AN OPTION TO PLAY AGAINST, ALL OF WHICH ARE PLAYED BY REAL ACTORS.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>14BC34B3</hash>
		<image>./images/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 3).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 3).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 3).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (32X) (USA) (Disc 3).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Slam City with Scottie Pippen (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>SLAM CITY WITH SCOTTIE PIPPEN IS A FULL-MOTION-VIDEO BASKETBALL GAME. IT USES PROPRIETARY TECHNOLOGY TO ALLOW SWITCHING FROM ONE SCENE TO ANOTHER WITHOUT LAG, WHICH ALLOWS FOR SMOOTHER INTERACTIVE VIDEO.

GAMEPLAY IS RELATIVELY SIMPLE, USING LITTLE MORE THAN ARROW KEYS, AND IS VERY DIFFERENT FROM ANY OTHER BASKETBALL SIMULATION. BASKETBALL IS MERELY THE SUBJECT FOR THE GAME'S PLOT, INVOLVING THE NEW-GUY, ACE (THE PLAYER), AND A HOST OF OTHER CHARACTERS, BASKETBALL PLAYERS OR JUST SPECTATORS, ALL WITH DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES. IT'S BASICALLY PLAY ONE-ON-ONE ON A WAREHOUSE COURT AND CLIMB THE "LADDERS" UNTIL YOU EARN ENOUGH RESPECT TO PLAY AGAINST SCOTTIE PIPPEN.

THE GAME FEATURES A TOTAL OF 13 CHARACTERS, 5 OF WHICH THE PLAYER HAS AN OPTION TO PLAY AGAINST, ALL OF WHICH ARE PLAYED BY REAL ACTORS.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>91BF8BF6</hash>
		<image>./images/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Slam City with Scottie Pippen (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>SLAM CITY WITH SCOTTIE PIPPEN IS A FULL-MOTION-VIDEO BASKETBALL GAME. IT USES PROPRIETARY TECHNOLOGY TO ALLOW SWITCHING FROM ONE SCENE TO ANOTHER WITHOUT LAG, WHICH ALLOWS FOR SMOOTHER INTERACTIVE VIDEO.

GAMEPLAY IS RELATIVELY SIMPLE, USING LITTLE MORE THAN ARROW KEYS, AND IS VERY DIFFERENT FROM ANY OTHER BASKETBALL SIMULATION. BASKETBALL IS MERELY THE SUBJECT FOR THE GAME'S PLOT, INVOLVING THE NEW-GUY, ACE (THE PLAYER), AND A HOST OF OTHER CHARACTERS, BASKETBALL PLAYERS OR JUST SPECTATORS, ALL WITH DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES. IT'S BASICALLY PLAY ONE-ON-ONE ON A WAREHOUSE COURT AND CLIMB THE "LADDERS" UNTIL YOU EARN ENOUGH RESPECT TO PLAY AGAINST SCOTTIE PIPPEN.

THE GAME FEATURES A TOTAL OF 13 CHARACTERS, 5 OF WHICH THE PLAYER HAS AN OPTION TO PLAY AGAINST, ALL OF WHICH ARE PLAYED BY REAL ACTORS.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E0ABA6EA</hash>
		<image>./images/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 3).chd</path>
		<name>Slam City with Scottie Pippen (Disc 3)</name>
		<desc>SLAM CITY WITH SCOTTIE PIPPEN IS A FULL-MOTION-VIDEO BASKETBALL GAME. IT USES PROPRIETARY TECHNOLOGY TO ALLOW SWITCHING FROM ONE SCENE TO ANOTHER WITHOUT LAG, WHICH ALLOWS FOR SMOOTHER INTERACTIVE VIDEO.

GAMEPLAY IS RELATIVELY SIMPLE, USING LITTLE MORE THAN ARROW KEYS, AND IS VERY DIFFERENT FROM ANY OTHER BASKETBALL SIMULATION. BASKETBALL IS MERELY THE SUBJECT FOR THE GAME'S PLOT, INVOLVING THE NEW-GUY, ACE (THE PLAYER), AND A HOST OF OTHER CHARACTERS, BASKETBALL PLAYERS OR JUST SPECTATORS, ALL WITH DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES. IT'S BASICALLY PLAY ONE-ON-ONE ON A WAREHOUSE COURT AND CLIMB THE "LADDERS" UNTIL YOU EARN ENOUGH RESPECT TO PLAY AGAINST SCOTTIE PIPPEN.

THE GAME FEATURES A TOTAL OF 13 CHARACTERS, 5 OF WHICH THE PLAYER HAS AN OPTION TO PLAY AGAINST, ALL OF WHICH ARE PLAYED BY REAL ACTORS.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CD1EA1D8</hash>
		<image>./images/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 3).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 3).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 3).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 3).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 4).chd</path>
		<name>Slam City with Scottie Pippen (Disc 4)</name>
		<desc>SLAM CITY WITH SCOTTIE PIPPEN IS A FULL-MOTION-VIDEO BASKETBALL GAME. IT USES PROPRIETARY TECHNOLOGY TO ALLOW SWITCHING FROM ONE SCENE TO ANOTHER WITHOUT LAG, WHICH ALLOWS FOR SMOOTHER INTERACTIVE VIDEO.

GAMEPLAY IS RELATIVELY SIMPLE, USING LITTLE MORE THAN ARROW KEYS, AND IS VERY DIFFERENT FROM ANY OTHER BASKETBALL SIMULATION. BASKETBALL IS MERELY THE SUBJECT FOR THE GAME'S PLOT, INVOLVING THE NEW-GUY, ACE (THE PLAYER), AND A HOST OF OTHER CHARACTERS, BASKETBALL PLAYERS OR JUST SPECTATORS, ALL WITH DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES. IT'S BASICALLY PLAY ONE-ON-ONE ON A WAREHOUSE COURT AND CLIMB THE "LADDERS" UNTIL YOU EARN ENOUGH RESPECT TO PLAY AGAINST SCOTTIE PIPPEN.

THE GAME FEATURES A TOTAL OF 13 CHARACTERS, 5 OF WHICH THE PLAYER HAS AN OPTION TO PLAY AGAINST, ALL OF WHICH ARE PLAYED BY REAL ACTORS.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9A1C1246</hash>
		<image>./images/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 4).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 4).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 4).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Slam City with Scottie Pippen (USA) (Disc 4).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12726" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Snatcher (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Snatcher</name>
		<desc>TUDO COMEÇOU EM 1996, ANO EM QUE 50% DA POPULAÇÃO HUMANA MORREU NO EVENTO CONHECIDO COMO "CATÁSTROFE", POR CAUSA DE UMA ARMA BIOLÓGICA CHAMADA "LUCIFER ALPHA" QUE FOI LIBERADA NA ATMOSFERA. DEZ ANOS DEPOIS O VÍRUS LÚCIFER-ALPHA SOFREU UMA MUTAÇÃO PASSANDO PARA UMA FORMA NÃO-LETAL. CINQUENTA ANOS DEPOIS, EM 2044, SERIA DESCOBERTO O PRIMEIRO CIBERNÉTICO EM FORMA HUMANA, TOTALMENTE DESCONTROLADO E PERIGOSO. ESSAS AMEAÇAS ROBÓTICAS FORAM BATIZADAS DE SNATCHERS E MATAVAM OS HUMANOS PARA ASSUMIREM OS SEUS LUGARES. NINGUÉM SABE DE ONDE ELES VIERAM OU QUAIS SÃO OS SEUS PROPÓSITOS. NA CIDADE COM O MAIOR ÍNDICE DE SURGIMENTO DE SNATCHERS, NEO-KOBE, LOCALIZADA NO JAPÃO FORMOU-SE UMA UNIDADE PARA COMBATÊ-LOS, A JUNKER. VOCÊ ENCARNA O PAPEL DE GILLIAM SEED, UM NOVATO NA JUNKER QUE SOFRE DE AMNÉSIA. GILLIAM E SUA NAMORADA JAMIE FORAM ENCONTRADOS NO LOCAL ONDE O PRIMEIRO SNATCHER APARECEU, PORÉM AMBOS NÃO SE RECORDAM DE NADA. UM DOS JUNKERS DESAPARECEU EM CAMPO. VOCÊ DEVE IR ATÉ O LOCAL ONDE ELE FEZ SUA ÚLTIMA CHAMADA E DESCOBRIR O QUE ACONTECEU.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>729EC364</hash>
		<image>./images/Snatcher (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Snatcher (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Snatcher (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Snatcher (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12794" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sol-Feace (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sol-Feace</name>
		<desc>SOL-FEACE (SOL-DEACE IN THE GENESIS) IS A TYPICAL 2D SHOOTER WITH WEAPON POWERUPS. THE GAME FEATURES SIX LEVELS: SIRIUS, ENEMY ARSENAL, ARTIFISTAR, PLUTO BASE, ALMATHEA, AND FINAL BATTLE. 

ALONG THE WAY VARIOUS WEAPONS CAN BE PICKED UP INCLUDING PLASMA BULLETS, DOUBLE PLASMA BULLETS, LASERS, AND MISSILES.

THE MOST UNIQUE FEATURE OF THE GAME IS THAT YOU CAN REALIGN YOUR UPGRADED GUNS TO FIRE FRONT-BACK, UP-DOWN, TIGHT SPREAD, WIDE SPREAD OR WHATEVER THE CURRENT SITUATION REQUIRED.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wolf Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0F7700EE</hash>
		<image>./images/Sol-Feace (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sol-Feace (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sol-Feace (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sol-Feace (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12702" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic CD (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog CD</name>
		<desc>SONIC THE HEDGEHOG E SUA NAMORADA AUTO-PROCLAMADA AMY ROSE VIAJAM ATÉ NEVER LAKE, APENAS PARA DESCOBRIR O QUE LENDÁRIO LITTLE PLANET ESTÁ AMARRADO EM CORRENTES E COBERTO POR METAL. PARECE QUE O ARQUI-INIMIGO DO SONIC, DR. EGGMAN ESTÁ USANDO OS PODERES DO PLANETA PARA MANIPULAR O TECIDO DO TEMPO. ELE CRIOU A CONTRAPARTE MALIGNA DO SONIC, METAL SONIC, QUE SEQUESTRA AMY E DESAPARECE. AGORA O VALENTE OURIÇO DEVE EXPLORAR LITTLE PLANET, RECOLHER AS SETE TIME STONES, JÓIAS CAPAZES DE ALTERAR A PASSAGEM DO TEMPO, LIBERTAR AMY E DERROTAR METAL SONIC JUNTO COM SEU MESTRE.NNNNSONIC CD É UM JOGO DE PLATAFORMA DE SIDE-SCROLLING SEMELHANTE A OUTROS JOGOS DA SÉRIE. SONIC USA SEUS PATENTEADOS SPIN ATTACKS PARA DESTRUIR OS BADNIKS E COLETAR VÁRIOS ITENS, COMO ANÉIS, ESCUDOS E SAPATOS. SEUS ATAQUES ESPECIAIS INCLUEM O SPIN DASH E O SUPER PEEL OUT. UMA CARACTERÍSTICA NOVA DO JOGO É A CAPACIDADE DE SONIC VIAJAR PARA VERSÕES PASSADAS E FUTURAS DAS FASES QUE ELE ATRAVESSA. DEPENDENDO DA AÇÃO DO JOGADOR NAS FASES ANTERIORES DAS ZONAS, AS VERSÕES FUTURAS DELAS (QUE CONTÊM CHEFÕES OBRIGATÓRIOS) MUDARÃO DE "RUIM" PARA "BOM", TENDO MAIS OU MENOS INIMIGOS E OBSTÁCULOS, RESPECTIVAMENTE.NNNNAS TIME STONES PODEM SER COLETADAS ATRAVÉS DA CONCLUSÃO DE FASES ESPECIAIS, EM QUE SONIC TEM DE DESTRUIR OVNIS DENTRO DE UM LIMITE DE TEMPO ATRIBUÍDO. O FINAL "BOM" DO JOGO PODE SER CONSEGUIDO COLETANDO TODAS AS SETE TIME STONES OU TRANSFORMANDO TODAS AS VERSÕES FUTURAS DAS ZONAS EM "BOM". O JOGO TEM RECURSOS QUE APROVEITAM O FORMATO DE CD, COMO ÁUDIO DE CD E ANIMAÇÕES.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B2F71AC0</hash>
		<image>./images/Sonic CD (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Sonic CD (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Sonic CD (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sonic CD (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12777" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Soulstar (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Soul Star</name>
		<desc>O SOULSTAR PARA O SEGA CD / MEGA CD É UM SHOOT-EM-UP 3D QUE COMBINA VÁRIOS TIPOS DIFERENTES DE JOGABILIDADE NUM ÚNICO JOGO. ALGUNS NÍVEIS NESTE JOGO ESTÃO EM UM CAMINHO FIXO, SEMELHANTE AO SPACE HARRIER OU STAR FOX. OUTROS NÍVEIS PERMITEM QUE SUA ESPAÇONAVE FLUTUE LIVREMENTE AO REDOR DE UM AMBIENTE 3D, E EM OUTROS NÍVEIS, SUA NAVE SE TRANSFORMA EM UM ROBÔ.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>1FBC3BAE</hash>
		<image>./images/Soulstar (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Soulstar (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Soulstar (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Soulstar (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12798" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Space Ace (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Space Ace</name>
		<desc>FOLLOWING THE SUCCESSFUL GAMEPLAY OF DRAGON'S LAIR, DON BLUTH RELEASED THIS SECOND CONVERSION OF HIS LASERDISC GAMES SERIES.

YOU'RE PLAYING DEXTER, A GUY FIGHTING THE EVIL MADMAN BORF WHO HAS KIDNAPPED YOUR GIRLFRIEND KIMBERLY AND IS NOW THREATENING THE WORLD WITH HIS DREADED WEAPON, THE "INFANTO RAY" WHICH TURNS ADULTS INTO SMALL CHILDREN.

THE GAME PLAYS LIKE A COMIC STRIP - VISUALS ARE SIMILAR TO MANY CARTOON MOVIES. IN EACH SCENE YOU ONLY HAVE TO DECIDE WHICH DIRECTION OF THE KEYBOARD HAS TO BE HIT IN ORDER TO AVOID ONE OF THE COUNTLESS DEATH SCREENS AND TO ADVANCE TO THE NEXT SCREEN...</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ReadySoft Incorporated</developer>
		<publisher>ReadySoft Incorporated</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Space Ace (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Space Ace (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Space Ace (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Space Ace (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12717" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Wars Rebel Assault (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Rebel Assault</name>
		<desc>STAR WARS: REBEL ASSAULT ON MEGA-CD IS AN ACTION GAME BASED ON THE UNIVERSE OF STAR WARS. THE PLAYER PLAYS ROOKIE ONE, A YOUNG FARMER ON TATOOINE WHO HAS JUST JOINED THE REBELLIOUS ALLIANCE AND HAS TO ACCOMPLISH DIFFERENT KINDS OF MISSIONS: DESTRUCTION OF SHIPS, INFILTRATION, ...</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JVC</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Star Wars Rebel Assault (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Star Wars Rebel Assault (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Star Wars Rebel Assault (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars Rebel Assault (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12800" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Starblade (USA).chd</path>
		<name>StarBlade</name>
		<desc>SITTING IN THE GUNNER POSITION OF A "GEOSWORD" FIGHTERCRAFT, YOU MUST SHOOT YOUR WAY THROUGH THE ENEMY ARMADA AND BRING THE FIGHT TO THEIR BASE PLANET, REDEYE. ALTOGETHER YOU'LL HAVE AROUND 10 MISSIONS TO GET THROUGH BEFORE THE GALAXY IS SAFE AND YOUR WINGMEN WILL HELP YOU ALONG THE WAY. AND DURING THOSE MISSIONS, YOU'LL BE EXPECTED TO SHOOT OUT THE SIDES OF HUGE ENEMY BATTLECRUISERS, TRAVEL INSIDE OF ENEMY CARRIERS AND TRAVEL THROUGH THE CANYONS OF REDEYE TO DELIVER YOUR PAYLOAD.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>00C0F81E</hash>
		<image>./images/Starblade (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Starblade (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Starblade (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Starblade (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97383" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Stellar-Fire (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Stellar-Fire</name>
		<desc>THE DREADED DRAXON RACE HAS BEEN AT IT AGAIN, PUSHING THE HUMAN RACE AROUND, WORKING TO EITHER ENSLAVE ALL 10 BILLION HUMANS OR WIPE THEM OUT COMPLETELY. AS THE LAST SURVIVING PILOT SENT ON A MISSION TO THWART THE DRAXONS' PLANS, ALL HOPE RESTS ON YOU. INVADE EACH OF THE FORTIFIED MOONS ORBITING THE DRAXONS' HOMEWORLD OF ARCTAURUS AND THEN AIM FOR THE MOTHER PLANET ITSELF.

THE ACTION TAKES PLACE IN YOUR HOVERMORPH CRAFT. IN THE GAME'S INTRODUCTION, THE SHIP PROVES TO BE A DEADLY STARFIGHTER. WHEN IT ENTERS THE MOON'S ATMOSPHERE AND APPROACHES THE SURFACE, THE HOVERMORPH TRANSFORMS INTO A POWERFUL HOVERSHIP. BLAST AWAY DRAXON ENEMIES, BOTH GROUND- AND AIR-BASED, FROM A FIRST-PERSON PERSPECTIVE ON A 3D POLYGONAL BATTLEFIELD.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infinite Laser Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Dynamix, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>200C732A</hash>
		<image>./images/Stellar-Fire (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Stellar-Fire (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Stellar-Fire (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Stellar-Fire (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12801" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Supreme Warrior (32X) (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>SUPREME WARRIOR IS A FULL-MOTION VIDEO FIGHTING GAME.  THE GAME, OR INTERACTIVE MOVIE, IS SET IN CHINA HUNDREDS OF YEARS AGO.  YOU ARE TASKED WITH PROTECTING HALF OF A MAGICAL MASK.  THE WEARER OF THE MASK WILL BE GRANTED UNTOLD POWER.  UNFORTUNATELY, THE VILLANOUS WANG TU HAS THE OTHER HALF OF THE MASK, AND WANTS YOUR HALF BADLY.  SO, YOU MUST FIGHT OFF WANG TU'S MINIONS, AND EVENTUALLY FANG TU HIMSELF.

THE GAMEPLAY IN SUPREME WARRIOR CONSISTS OF DIGITIZED VIDEO WITH INTERACTIVE ELEMENTS.  AT MANY POINTS DURING THE VIDEO, YOU CAN UNLEASH A PUNCH, KICK, OR BLOCK.  IF YOUR TIMING IS CORRECT, YOU INFLICT DAMAGE ON YOUR OPPONENT.  IF YOU TIMING IS OFF, YOUR OPPONENT HURTS YOU.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3E13E7ED</hash>
		<image>./images/Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12801" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Supreme Warrior (32X) (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>SUPREME WARRIOR IS A FULL-MOTION VIDEO FIGHTING GAME.  THE GAME, OR INTERACTIVE MOVIE, IS SET IN CHINA HUNDREDS OF YEARS AGO.  YOU ARE TASKED WITH PROTECTING HALF OF A MAGICAL MASK.  THE WEARER OF THE MASK WILL BE GRANTED UNTOLD POWER.  UNFORTUNATELY, THE VILLANOUS WANG TU HAS THE OTHER HALF OF THE MASK, AND WANTS YOUR HALF BADLY.  SO, YOU MUST FIGHT OFF WANG TU'S MINIONS, AND EVENTUALLY FANG TU HIMSELF.

THE GAMEPLAY IN SUPREME WARRIOR CONSISTS OF DIGITIZED VIDEO WITH INTERACTIVE ELEMENTS.  AT MANY POINTS DURING THE VIDEO, YOU CAN UNLEASH A PUNCH, KICK, OR BLOCK.  IF YOUR TIMING IS CORRECT, YOU INFLICT DAMAGE ON YOUR OPPONENT.  IF YOU TIMING IS OFF, YOUR OPPONENT HURTS YOU.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>684FA966</hash>
		<image>./images/Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Supreme Warrior (32X) (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12801" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Supreme Warrior (Disc 1)</name>
		<desc>SUPREME WARRIOR IS A FULL-MOTION VIDEO FIGHTING GAME.  THE GAME, OR INTERACTIVE MOVIE, IS SET IN CHINA HUNDREDS OF YEARS AGO.  YOU ARE TASKED WITH PROTECTING HALF OF A MAGICAL MASK.  THE WEARER OF THE MASK WILL BE GRANTED UNTOLD POWER.  UNFORTUNATELY, THE VILLANOUS WANG TU HAS THE OTHER HALF OF THE MASK, AND WANTS YOUR HALF BADLY.  SO, YOU MUST FIGHT OFF WANG TU'S MINIONS, AND EVENTUALLY FANG TU HIMSELF.

THE GAMEPLAY IN SUPREME WARRIOR CONSISTS OF DIGITIZED VIDEO WITH INTERACTIVE ELEMENTS.  AT MANY POINTS DURING THE VIDEO, YOU CAN UNLEASH A PUNCH, KICK, OR BLOCK.  IF YOUR TIMING IS CORRECT, YOU INFLICT DAMAGE ON YOUR OPPONENT.  IF YOU TIMING IS OFF, YOUR OPPONENT HURTS YOU.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E41C99B2</hash>
		<image>./images/Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 1).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 1).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 1).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 1).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12801" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Supreme Warrior (Disc 2)</name>
		<desc>SUPREME WARRIOR IS A FULL-MOTION VIDEO FIGHTING GAME.  THE GAME, OR INTERACTIVE MOVIE, IS SET IN CHINA HUNDREDS OF YEARS AGO.  YOU ARE TASKED WITH PROTECTING HALF OF A MAGICAL MASK.  THE WEARER OF THE MASK WILL BE GRANTED UNTOLD POWER.  UNFORTUNATELY, THE VILLANOUS WANG TU HAS THE OTHER HALF OF THE MASK, AND WANTS YOUR HALF BADLY.  SO, YOU MUST FIGHT OFF WANG TU'S MINIONS, AND EVENTUALLY FANG TU HIMSELF.

THE GAMEPLAY IN SUPREME WARRIOR CONSISTS OF DIGITIZED VIDEO WITH INTERACTIVE ELEMENTS.  AT MANY POINTS DURING THE VIDEO, YOU CAN UNLEASH A PUNCH, KICK, OR BLOCK.  IF YOUR TIMING IS CORRECT, YOU INFLICT DAMAGE ON YOUR OPPONENT.  IF YOU TIMING IS OFF, YOUR OPPONENT HURTS YOU.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Pictures</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Pictures</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>60C7D93F</hash>
		<image>./images/Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 2).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 2).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 2).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Supreme Warrior (USA) (Disc 2).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12795" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Surgical Strike (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Surgical Strike</name>
		<desc>A MIDDLE EASTERN MADMAN HAS BEGUN LAUNCHING ROCKETS AGAINST INNOCENT CIVILIAN POPULATION CENTERS. THE UNITED NATIONS HAS DEEMED THIS BEHAVIOR UNACCEPTABLE AND THE SECRETARY-GENERAL HAS ORDERED A SURGICAL STRIKE IN AN EFFORT THE CURB THESE ATTACKS. TO THAT END, YOU ARE TO PILOT THE MOST ADVANCED WAR VEHICLE DEVISED TO DATE-- A HEAVILY ARMORED AND ARMED HOVERCRAFT.

SURGICAL STRIKE IS AN ON-RAILS ACTION SHOOTER GAME THAT TAKES PLACE AGAINST A FULL MOTION VIDEO BACKDROP DEPICTING CHAOTIC, WAR-RAVAGED CITYSCAPES. YOU ARE TO PILOT THE HOVERCRAFT, FIRE EITHER BULLETS OR ROCKETS AT OPPORTUNE MOMENTS, AND ISSUE TURN DIRECTIVES AT KEY JUNCTURES. MISS A CUE AND ANOTHER PRECIOUS MILITARY HOVERCRAFT WILL BE TOAST AND YOU'LL BE CHEWED OUT BY YOUR SUPERIOR OFFICER AND PEERS ALIKE.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6974ABAB</hash>
		<image>./images/Surgical Strike (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Surgical Strike (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Surgical Strike (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Surgical Strike (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12737" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin</name>
		<desc>ROBIN E O COMISSÁRIO GORDON DESAPARECERAM. O CAVALEIRO DAS TREVAS SUSPEITA QUE UM OU MAIS DOS SUSPEITOS DE COSTUME PODEM ESTAR ENVOLVIDOS, INCLUINDO POISON IVY, RIDDLER E THE JOKER. ELE VAI EM SEU FIEL BATMÓVEL PARA ACERTAR A SITUAÇÃO. GRANDE PARTE DO JOGO CONSISTE EM AÇÃO DE CONDUÇÃO 3D AO VOLANTE DO BATMÓVEL. HÁ TAMBÉM NÍVEIS EM QUE O CAPED CRUSADER DEVE REALIZAR UM ATAQUE AÉREO USANDO O BATWING. ENTRE OS NÍVEIS, O JOGADOR É TRATADO COM UMA SÉRIE DE CENAS QUE COMPÕEM QUASE TODO UM EPISÓDIO EXCLUSIVO DE BATMAN: THE ANIMATED SERIES, SOBRE O QUAL O JOGO É BASEADO.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clockwork Tortoise</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8033350B</hash>
		<image>./images/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12803" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Adventures of Willy Beamish, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Adventures of Willy Beamish</name>
		<desc>WILLY BEAMISH IS A KID WHO LIKES TO GOOF OFF AND HAVE FUN. NATURALLY ALL THE GROWN-UPS GET IN THE WAY BY MAKING HIM GO TO SCHOOL, MAKING HIM CLEAN HIS ROOM, ETC. BUT NOW THAT'S SCHOOL'S OUT FOR THE SUMMER, WILLY IS DETERMINED TO HAVE A GOOD TIME AND MAYBE EVEN HAVE HIS PET FROG WIN THE FROG JUMPING CONTEST. HOWEVER WILLY HAS A HABIT OF GETTING INTO TROUBLE, AND NATURALLY THAT MEANS IT WILL BE A CHALLENGE TO GET OUT OF IT.

THE ADVENTURES OF WILLY BEAMISH IS A POINT-AND-CLICK GRAPHICAL ADVENTURE. YOU PLAY WILLY BEAMISH, AN EIGHT YEAR-OLD KID WHO IS JUST TRYING TO GET THROUGH LIFE WITHOUT LOSING HIS LUNCH MONEY. BUT HE'LL HAVE TO DEAL WITH PARENTS, TEACHERS, BABYSITTERS AND BRATTY SISTERS. THE PLAYER MUST SOLVE DIFFERENT PUZZLES TO ENSURE WILLY CAN PROGRESS, GET OUT OF TROUBLE AND GENERALLY AVOID ENDING UP GROUNDED. 

THE IN-GAME TIME PROGRESSES EVEN IF NO ACTION IS TAKEN. THIS MEANS MANY PUZZLES HAVE TO BE SOLVED IN A CERTAIN TIME FRAME OR RELY ON BEING IN THE RIGHT PLACE AT THE RIGHT TIME. A SPECIAL ASPECT OF THIS GAME IS A BAR WHICH SHOWS WILLY'S RELATIONSHIP TO HIS PARENTS. IT GETS AFFECTED BY THE WAY CERTAIN SITUATIONS ARE RESOLVED, E.G. IT INCREASES IF WILLY REFUSES TO PLAY WITH HIS SISTER, AND WHEN IT IS FULL THEY SEND WILLY TO A MILITARY SCHOOL AND THE GAME IS LOST.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dynamix</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Adventures of Willy Beamish, The (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Adventures of Willy Beamish, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Adventures of Willy Beamish, The (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Adventures of Willy Beamish, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12833" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lawnmower Man, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Lawnmower Man</name>
		<desc>THE LAWNMOWER MAN IS THE GAME BASED ON THE 1992 MOVIE OF THE SAME NAME (ITSELF LOOSELY BASED ON A STEPHEN KING SHORT STORY)  STARRING PRE-BOND FAME PIERCE BROSNAN AS DR. LAWRENCE ANGELO, A SCIENTIST WORKING FOR VIRTUAL SPACE INDUSTRIES IN "PROJECT 5", A SECRET RESEARCH THAT ATTEMPTS TO INCREASE THE INTELLIGENCE OF PRIMATES USING PSYCHOTROPIC DRUGS AND VR TRAINING. 

WITH HIS RELUCTANCE TO AIM THE RESEARCH TO MILITARY PURPOSE, AFTER ONE OF THE CHIMPS ESCAPES AND SHOOTS A GUARD IN THE PROCESS HE IS GIVEN A FORCED VACATION, AND WHILE TAKING NOTES ON THE NEED FOR EXPERIMENT WITH A HUMAN SUBJECT, HE NOTICES JOBE SMITH (JEFF FAHEY), A SIMPLETON WHO MAKES HIS LIVING ON ODD JOBS SUCH AS MOWING THE GRASS (HENCE, THE TITLE ROLE). THE FIRST EXPERIMENTS QUICKLY INCREASE JOBE'S INTELLIGENCE, AND WHILE AFTER AN ACCIDENT ANGELO STOPPED THE EXPERIMENTS, THE SHOP, A SECRET AGENCY OVERVIEWING PROJECT 5, REINSERTED THE DRUGS RESPONSIBLE FOR VIOLENT BEHAVIOUR INTO THE PROGRAM AND SPED UP THE TREATMENT. AS JOBE STARTS TO DEVELOP TELEKINETIC POWERS, HE STARTS TO TAKE REVENGE ON THOSE WHO ABUSED HIM BEFORE HE STARTED THE TREATMENTS, AND PLOTS TO TAKE OVER ALL COMPUTERS IN THE WORLD.

WHILE THE CD VERSION OF THE GAME (PC, MEGA CD) IS AN INTERACTIVE MOVIE, BOTH CARTRIDGE VERSIONS ARE PLATFORMERS, THE PLAYER TAKING CONTROL OF DR. ANGELO OR CARLA PARKETTE (MOTHER OF JOBE'S BEST FRIEND) IN TYPICAL SIDE-SCROLLING SHOOTING ACTION. THE PLAYER CAN COLLECT BETTER WEAPONS OR DATA DISCS, WHICH AFTER COLLECTING A NUMBER OF THEM ALLOW TO MORPH INTO THE VIRTUAL SUIT, WHICH GIVES PROTECTION AGAINST A FIRST HIT. THE PLAYER VISITS SEVERAL LOCATIONS SEEN IN THE MOVIE, SUCH AS THE GAS PUMP AND THE VSI HEADQUARTERS. 

THE TWISTS OF THE GAME ARE TRUE-3D LEVEL CONNECTORS, BASED ON THE CG SEQUENCES OF THE MOVIE, USUALLY ALL INVOLVING AVOIDING OBSTACLES (AND THE OCCASIONAL SHOOTING) AT HIGH SPEED IN THE VR WORLD. THERE ARE FOUR DIFFERENT (VIRTUAL WORLD, CYBER WAR, CYBER RUN AND CYBER TUBE), EACH TAKING A SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT APPROACH (VIRTUAL WORLD IS SEEN IN FIRST PERSON, THE OBJECTIVE BEING DODGING OBSTACLES SUCH AS TREES AND ARCHS AND REACH THE EXIT, CYBER WAR SIMILAR TO VIRTUAL WORLD BUT WITH SOME SHOOTING STOPS, CYBER RUN IS SEEN IN THIRD PERSON AND REQUIRES OCCASIONAL SHOOTING OF OBSTACLES, WHILE CYBER TUBE IS A FAST TRAVEL WITH PLENTY OF ENEMIES IN A VR TUNNEL).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Sales Curve</developer>
		<publisher>Time Warner Interactive</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4309DFA1</hash>
		<image>./images/Lawnmower Man, The (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Lawnmower Man, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Lawnmower Man, The (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lawnmower Man, The (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="108015" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./San Diego Zoo Presents... The Animals!, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The San Diego Zoo Presents... The Animals!</name>
		<desc>BREAKTHROUGH VIDEO-WITH-SOUND TECHNOLOGY IN THE ANIMALS! LETS YOU SEE AND HEAR OVER 200 EXOTIC MAMMALS, BIRDS, AND REPTILES IN OVER 60 MINUTES OF VIDEO CLIPS. USING MOVIES, SOUNDS AND STORIES, THE ANIMALS! ALSO BRINGS YOU THE MOST COMPLETE AND UP-TO-DATE INFORMATION ABOUT OUR ANIMAL NEIGHBORS FROM EXPERTS AT THE WORLD-RENOWNED SAN DIEGO ZOO. IF YOU LOVE ANIMALS, YOU'LL LOVE THE ANIMALS! IT'S FUN AND EASY FOR CHILDREN AND ADULTS TO EXPLORE THE VAST RESOURCES OF THE ANIMALS! CLICKING ON THE HABITAT MAP TAKES YOU INSTANTLY TO THE ANIMALS THAT LIVE IN ONE OF THE EARTH'S MAJOR CLIMATE ZONES INCLUDING: TROPICAL FORESTS, DESERTS, SAVANNAS, OR TUNDRA. CLIMB ABOARD THE MULTIMEDIA TOUR BUS FOR A NARRATED TOUR OF ANIMALS IN DISGUISE, FACT OR FABLE, AND JAWS, CLAWS AND CREATURE FEATURES. IN THE STORYBOOK THEATER, YOU'LL HEAR FASCINATING ANIMAL STORIES SUCH AS RAISING GORDY GORILLA, PROTECTING ENDANGERED SPECIES, AND WILD SAFARI.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Toolworks</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<hash>12A88886</hash>
		<image>./images/San Diego Zoo Presents... The Animals!, The (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/San Diego Zoo Presents... The Animals!, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/San Diego Zoo Presents... The Animals!, The (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/San Diego Zoo Presents... The Animals!, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12705" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Secret Of Monkey Island, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Secret of Monkey Island</name>
		<desc>THE SECRET OF MONKEY ISLAND NOS LEVA A UMA GRANDE AVENTURA COM O PIRATA APRENDIZ GUYBRUSH THREEPWOOD. ATRAVÉS DE UMA HISTÓRIA CHEIA DE SITUAÇÕES ENGRAÇADAS, GUYBRUSH IRÁ VER-SE EM BATALHAS DE DISCUÇÕES ANTES DE TENTAR DESVENDAR O MISTÉRIO DA FAMOSA MONKEY ISLAND.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CF866859</hash>
		<image>./images/Secret Of Monkey Island, The (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Secret Of Monkey Island, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Secret Of Monkey Island, The (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Secret Of Monkey Island, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12730" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Smurfs, The (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>The Smurfs</name>
		<desc>THE SMURFS ON MEGA CD IS A PLATFORM GAME INSPIRED BY THE COMIC BOOK OF THE SAME NAME. THE PLAYER EMBODIES ONE OF THESE ADORABLE BLUE CREATURES AND LEAVES TO FREE HIS FRIENDS, IMPRISONED BY THE HORRIBLE GARGAMEL. 20 LEVELS DURING, MAKE YOUR WAY IN A VARIETY OF SCENERIES AND FAITHFUL TO THE UNIVERSE IMAGINED BY PEYO.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F8E97676</hash>
		<image>./images/Smurfs, The (Europe).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Smurfs, The (Europe).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Smurfs, The (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Smurfs, The (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12728" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Wars Chess (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Software Toolworks' Star Wars Chess</name>
		<desc>STAR WARS CHESS IS A CHESS GAME WHERE THE PIECES ARE CHARACTERS FROM THE STAR WARS UNIVERSE.  WHEN PIECES ARE TAKEN, AN ANIMATED BATTLE IS SHOWN, MUCH LIKE IN BATTLE CHESS.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Toolworks</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>08F9E80B</hash>
		<image>./images/Star Wars Chess (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Star Wars Chess (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Star Wars Chess (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars Chess (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58742" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Space Adventure, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Space Adventure</name>
		<desc>IT IS THE SEQUEL TO A JAPAN ONLY GAME TITLED COBRA: KOKURYUUOU NO DENSETSU RELEASED FOR THE PC ENGINE CD IN 1989, BOTH BEING BASED ON THE MANGA AND ANIME SERIES COBRA BY BUICHI TERASAWA. IT WAS ONE OF THE LAST GAMES TO BE PUBLISHED FOR THE SEGA CD IN BOTH NORTH AMERICA AND EUROPE. THE FORMAT OF THE GAME IS SIMILAR TO SNATCHER WHILE THE PLOT IS BASED ON ONE OF COBRA'S EARLY ADVENTURES.

THE PLAYER TAKES THE ROLE OF THE MANGA HERO COBRA, WHO AFTER WALKING INTO A BAR, LEARNS THAT A BOUNTY HAS BEEN PLACED ON HIS HEAD BY THE GALAXY PATROL AND THAT HE IS BEING HUNTED BY A BOUNTY HUNTER NAMED JANE ROYAL. AFTER IT IS DISCOVERED THAT COBRA'S ARCHENEMY CRYSTAL BOY IS AFTER A TREASURE HIDDEN BY JANE'S FATHER, THE LOCATION OF WHICH HE ENCODED IN THE FORM OF TATTOOS ON HIS TRIPLET DAUGHTERS, COBRA AND JANE AGREE TO JOIN FORCES TO LOCATE HER SISTERS AND DEFEAT CRYSTAL BOY.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>328C1C27</hash>
		<image>./images/Space Adventure, The (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Space Adventure, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Space Adventure, The (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Space Adventure, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12709" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Terminator, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Terminator</name>
		<desc>O JOGO SEGUE FIELMENTE A HISTÓRIA DO FILME: NO ANO DE 2029 O MUNDO FOI DESTRUÍDO NUMA GUERRA CONTRA AS MÁQUINAS, QUE SE TORNARAM INTELIGENTES E AUTO-SUFICIENTES. O LÍDER DA RESISTÊNCIA HUMANA, CHAMADO JOHN CONNOR, É A ÚNICA AMEAÇA PARA A DOMINAÇÃO TOTAL DAS MÁQUINAS, QUE PARA SE LIVRAR DELE, MANDAM PARA O PASSADO UM EXTERMINADOR ? UM ROBÔ HUMANOIDE REVESTIDO DE PELE HUMANA ? PARA LOCALIZAR SUA MÃE, SARAH CONNOR, E MATÁ-LA, IMPEDINDO ASSIM O NASCIMENTO DE JOHN CONNOR. MAS JOHN DESCOBRE O PLANO DAS MÁQUINAS E MANDA UM SOLDADO DE SUA EXTREMA CONFIANÇA, O CORAJOSO KYLE REESE, QUE TEM A MISSÃO DE VOLTAR PARA O PASSADO E PROTEGER SARAH CONNOR DO TERRÍVEL ASSASSINO ROBÓTICO. EM COMPARAÇÃO COM A VERSÃO DE MEGADRIVE, UM MAIOR NÚMERO DE FASES, GRÁFICOS MELHORES E UMA TRILHA SONORA ARRASADORA, É O QUE A VIRGIN FEZ PARA MELHORAR, UM ANO DEPOIS, O JOGO EM SUA VERSÃO CD.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Software</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8CA4F2A1</hash>
		<image>./images/Terminator, The (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Terminator, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Terminator, The (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Terminator, The (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12773" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Third World War (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The Third World War</name>
		<desc>THIRD WORLD WAR IS A "HYPOTHETICAL/WHAT IF" WARGAME WITH A TWIST. SET SOMETIME IN THE LATE 20TH CENTURY, WHEN CONFLICTS ALL OVER THE WORLD HAVE ERUPTED, AND WORLD PEACE IS BUT A THING OF THE PAST.

AS THE LEADER OF ONE OF 16 NATIONS, YOUR ULTIMATE GOAL IS NONE OTHER THAN WORLD DOMINATION. TO ACCOMPLISH THIS YOU HAVE A MULTITUDE OF OPTIONS RANGING FROM RAW MILITARY MIGHT, DIPLOMACY, FOREIGN OR DOMESTIC INVESTMENT POLICY, AIDING TERRORISTS OR REVOLUTIONARIES, TO MEDIA MANIPULATION. IN OTHER WORDS, IT'S JUST LIKE THE REAL WORLD.

THE GAME OFFERS 5 DISTINCT SCENARIOS, ALL OF WHICH REQUIRE DIFFERENT STRATEGIES TO WIN.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micronet</developer>
		<publisher>Micronet</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>727A424A</hash>
		<image>./images/Third World War (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Third World War (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Third World War (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Third World War (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12780" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Amazing Spider-Man vs. The Kingpin, The (USA).chd</path>
		<name>The	Amazing Spider-Man vs. The Kingpin</name>
		<desc>THE CITY OF NEW YORK IS CERTAINLY A GREAT PLACE TO BE, BUT NOT WHEN THERE'S THE CRIMINAL ELEMENT RUNNING ABOUT. LUCKY FOR THE NYPD, THERE'S ALSO THE HEROIC SPIDER-MAN ON THEIR SIDE!BUT NOW ONE OF THE BIGGEST CRIMINALS IN THE CITY, WILSON FISK, A.K.A. THE</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C7A7939F</hash>
		<image>./images/Amazing Spider-Man vs. The Kingpin, The (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Amazing Spider-Man vs. The Kingpin, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Amazing Spider-Man vs. The Kingpin, The (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Amazing Spider-Man vs. The Kingpin, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12703" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Theme Park (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Theme Park</name>
		<desc>DOMINATING THE EXCITING WORLD OF THEME PARK OWNERSHIP IS YOUR GOAL IN THIS STRATEGY GAME FROM BULLFROG. THE FIRST TASK IS TO SET UP YOUR RIDES WITHIN THE AVAILABLE LAND, STRUCTURING CONVENIENT PATHS AND QUEUES AND IDEALLY LEAVING SOME SPACE FOR BIGGER RIDES ONCE THEY BECOME AVAILABLE, AND INCLUDE SOME LAKES AND TREES TO INCREASE THE PARK'S ALLURE. RIDES RANGE FROM TEACUPS AND HAUNTED HOUSES TO THE BIGGEST MOST ELABORATE ROLLER-COASTER YOU CAN DESIGN, AND WATER RIDES THAT LOOP AROUND OTHER RIDES.

SHOPS MUST ALSO BE INCLUDED, SO THAT THE VISITORS CAN BUY FOOD, DRINKS AND SOUVENIRS - THE CUNNING PLAYER WILL COMBINE SALT, SUGAR AND CAFFEINE SETTINGS TO MAXIMIZE CONSUMER INTEREST. STAFF MUST BE HIRED TO KEEP EVERYTHING RUNNING SMOOTHLY, AND THEY WILL ONLY WORK FOR WHAT THEY CONSIDER A FAIR RATE OF PAY.

YOU ARE COMPETING AGAINST OTHER THEME PARKS, SO DON'T LET THEM GET AN ADVANTAGE OVER YOU - MONITOR YOUR SUCCESS IN ATTRACTING CUSTOMERS AND FINANCIAL VIABILITY CLOSELY USING THE SUPPLIED STATISTICS PAGES. MORE IMPORTANT, ENSURE THAT RESEARCH IS ADEQUATELY FUNDED TO PRODUCE NEW RIDES.

IT CAN BE PLAYED IN THREE MODES - SANDBOX LEVEL LETS YOU CONCENTRATE ON THE PARK DESIGN ELEMENTS, WHILE SIM AND FULL ADD MORE STRATEGIC FEATURES.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Domark</developer>
		<publisher>Bullfrog</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9FE8E410</hash>
		<image>./images/Theme Park (Europe).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Theme Park (Europe).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Theme Park (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Theme Park (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12759" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Time Gal (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Time Gal</name>
		<desc>THE YEAR IS 4001. THE EVIL LUNA HAS STOLEN A TIME MACHINE AND PLANS TO USE IT TO TAKE OVER THE WORLD. YOU ARE THE TIME GAL, A SKILLFUL AND PRETTY SCIENTIST, AND YOUR MISSION IS TO CHASE LUNA THROUGH DIFFERENT TIME PERIODS, TO GET THE TIME MACHINE BACK, AND TO SAVE THE WORLD.

CREATED DURING THE FIRST AGE OF "FULL MOTION" STYLE, TIME GAL IS A CONVERSION OF AN EARLY ARCADE TITLE. YOU WATCH ANIMATIONS OF YOUR HEROINE WHILE SHE TRAVELS THROUGH LEVELS, AND OVERCOME OBSTACLES BY PUSHING THE CORRECT BUTTON AT THE RIGHT MOMENT. YOU CAN CHANGE DIRECTIONS, JUMP, SHOOT, ETC., BUT EVERYTHING IS CONTROLLED DURING THE NEVER-ENDING FLUENT MOTION OF THE TIME GAL. AT CERTAIN POINTS THE HEROINE STOPS THE TIME, AND YOU HAVE THREE CHOICES TO CHOOSE FROM.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renovation Products</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>86A9EE26</hash>
		<image>./images/Time Gal (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Time Gal (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Time Gal (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Time Gal (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12796" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tomcat Alley (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tomcat Alley</name>
		<desc>TOMCAT ALLEY IS ONE OF THE LAST OF SEGA'S TRUVIDEO GAMES FOR THE SEGACD, FEATURING YOU AND YOUR F-14 TOMCAT DOING WHAT YOU DO BEST - DOGFIGHTING RUSSIAN MIGS!

THIS TIME, A RENEGADE SOVIET COMMANDER IS THREATENING THE UNITED STATES WITH CHEMICAL WEAPONS FROM HIS BASE IN THE MEXICAN DESERT, AND ITS UP TO YOU AND YOUR WINGMEN TO FINE-TUNE YOUR AIR-TO-AIR COMBAT STRATEGIES TO MAKE THE ENTIRE WESTERN HEMISPHERE SAFE AGAIN!

TOMCAT ALLEY WAS ONE OF SEGA'S LAST TRUVIDEO GAMES, FEATURING WHAT IS CALLED "ACTIVE MATRIX" SOFTWARE, WHICH ALLOWS FOR MANY DIFFERENT OUTCOMES TO ANY GIVEN SITUATION.  THIS MEANS ONLY ONE THING - MUCH MORE INTERACTION AND VARIATION THAN PREVIOUS FMV (FULL MOTION VIDEO) GAMES!</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Code Monkeys</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./images/Tomcat Alley (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Tomcat Alley (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Tomcat Alley (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tomcat Alley (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12843" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Trivial Pursuit - Interactive Multimedia Game (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Trivial Pursuit: Interactive Multimedia Game</name>
		<desc>THIS IS THE FIRST MULTIMEDIA VERSION OF THE CLASSIC PARKER BROTHERS BOARD GAME. IT USES PHOTOS, ANIMATIONS, VIDEOS &amp; VOICE CLIPS TO POSE OVER 2000 QUESTIONS AND ANSWERS TO TRIVIAL PURSUIT QUESTIONS.

IN THE CLASSIC GAME, UP TO 6 PLAYERS ROLL AN ON-SCREEN DIE AND MOVE THEIR 'PIE-DISH' MARKER AROUND THE SPOKE-AND-WHEEL GAME BOARD, JUST LIKE THE BOARD GAME. THE SQUARE YOU LAND ON IS COLOR CODED TO ONE OF SIX TRIVIA CATEGORIES: PEOPLE &amp; PLACES, SPORTS &amp; LEISURE, HISTORY, ARTS &amp; ENTERTAINMENT, SCIENCE &amp; NATURE, AND WILD CARD. ANSWERING THE TRIVIA QUESTION CORRECTLY LETS YOU TAKE ANOTHER TURN.

FURTHER, IF YOU ARE ON THE 'PRIZE' SQUARE AT THE END OF EACH SPOKE (1 SPOKE END FOR EACH CATEGORY COLOR), THE CORRECT ANSWER GRANTS YOU A COLORED PIE PIECE IN YOUR PIE-DISH MARKER FOR THAT CATEGORY. ONCE YOU HAVE ALL 6 PIE PIECES IN YOUR DISH, YOU NEED TO HEAD BACK TO THE HUB FOR A FINAL RANDOM QUESTION TO WIN THE GAME.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Western Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<hash>D8FA30DB</hash>
		<image>./images/Trivial Pursuit - Interactive Multimedia Game (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Trivial Pursuit - Interactive Multimedia Game (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Trivial Pursuit - Interactive Multimedia Game (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Trivial Pursuit - Interactive Multimedia Game (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12838" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ultraverse Prime (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ultraverse Prime</name>
		<desc>PLAYERS CONTROL THE SUPERHERO PRIME, A THIRTEEN YEAR-OLD BOY CALLED KEVIN GREEN THAT HAS THE POWER TO TRANSFORM INTO A SUPERHERO ADULT VERSION OF HIMSELF. PRIME CAN PUNCH, KICK AND JUMP, AND COMBINE THESE INTO SOME NEW MOVES AND COMBOS. THE PLAYER AS WELL AS THE ENEMIES CAN ALSO OCCASIONALLY FIND WEAPONS OR OBJECTS TO PICK UP AND THROW. SOME STAGES ARE MUCH FASTER AS PRIME FLIES AT A FAST SPEED AND NEEDS TO PUNCH OBSTACLES AND ENEMIES OUT OF THE AIR.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Malibu Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2B7A2BF9</hash>
		<image>./images/Ultraverse Prime (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Ultraverse Prime (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Ultraverse Prime (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ultraverse Prime (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="58743" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Vay (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Vay</name>
		<desc>VAY É A HISTÓRIA DO PRÍNCIPE SANDOR DE LORATH, SUA BUSCA PARA VINGAR O ASSASSINATO DE SEUS PAIS E RESGATAR SUA AMADA LADY ELIN. NO QUE SERÁ O DIA DE SEU CASAMENTO, O CASTELO LORATH É ATACADO PELOS DANEK, QUE CONSEGUIRAM RECONSTRUIR PARCIALMENTE A TECNOLOGIA DE ROBÔS ALIENÍGENAS DE UM MILÊNIO ATRÁS. AS DEFESAS DO CASTELO SÃO IMPOTENTES CONTRA OS ROBÔS GIGANTES, E O REI E A RAINHA SÃO MORTOS NO ATAQUE. OS INVASORES ROUBAM ELIN NO MEIO DE SEUS VOTOS DE CASAMENTO. O PRÍNCIPE SANDOR, QUE AGORA É O REI, DECIDE RESGATAR SUA NOIVA E DESCOBRIR UMA MANEIRA DE DERROTAR A TEMÍVEL TECNOLOGIA ALIENÍGENA. O JOGO É UM RPG CLÁSSICO COM COMBATE BASEADO EM TURNOS, GANHANDO EXPERIÊNCIA E OURO NO PROCESSO. OS PERSONAGENS POSSUEM CLASSES PREDEFINIDAS (MAGO, BARDO, ETC.) E APRENDEM HABILIDADES/FEITIÇOS AUTOMATICAMENTE À MEDIDA QUE SOBEM DE NÍVEL.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SIMS Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>AE5AEBE3</hash>
		<image>./images/Vay (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Vay (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Vay (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Vay (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Virtual VCR - The Colors of Modern Rock (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Virtual VCR - The Colors of Modern Rock (USA)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<image>./images/Virtual VCR - The Colors of Modern Rock (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Virtual VCR - The Colors of Modern Rock (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Virtual VCR - The Colors of Modern Rock (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Virtual VCR - The Colors of Modern Rock (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12825" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wheel of Fortune (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wheel of Fortune</name>
		<desc>ONE OF THE MANY WHEEL OF FORTUNES VERSIONS RELEASED, THE SEGA CD VERSION HAS 6,000 DIFFERENT PUZZLES WITH FULL MOTION VIDEO OF VANNA WHITE HERSELF, HOWEVER PAT SAJAK DOES MAKE AN APPEARANCE IN THE GAME.  THE GAMEPLAY WAS AS SAME AS OTHER GAMES, USING A POWER METER TO SPIN THE WHEEL, PICK LETTERS TO FILL IN PUZZLES AND SOLVE THEM IN ORDER TO MAKE IT TO THE BONUS ROUND FOR A CHANCE TO WIN EITHER BIG MONEY.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<hash>3A90C43E</hash>
		<image>./images/Wheel of Fortune (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Wheel of Fortune (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Wheel of Fortune (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wheel of Fortune (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97364" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Who Shot Johnny Rock (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Who Shot Johnny Rock?</name>
		<desc>IT'S THE ROLLICKING '30S AND SOMEONE HAS KILLED POPULAR SINGER JOHNNY ROCK IN THIS ACTION-PACKED GANGSTER WHODUNIT. THE PLAYER WILL NEED TO NAVIGATE THE BACK STREETS, GAMING HALLS, FUNERAL PARLORS AND THE DIRTY SECTIONS OF THE CITY TO GET AT THE CLUES HELD BY A NUMBER OF SHADY CHARACTERS AND SOLVE THIS MURDER MYSTERY. BAD GUYS WITH MACHINE GUNS PROVIDE A HIGH LEVELS OF CHALLENGE.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>American Laser Games</developer>
		<publisher>American Laser Games</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./images/Who Shot Johnny Rock (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Who Shot Johnny Rock (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Who Shot Johnny Rock (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Who Shot Johnny Rock (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97365" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wild Woody (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wild Woody</name>
		<desc>AN ADVENTURER NAMED DUSTY RETURNS HOME WITH AN ENCHANTED TOTEM POLE. DUE TO AN ASSORTMENT OF RARE EVENTS, THE SPIRITS OF THE TOTEM HAVE BEEN FREED AND THEY HAVE CREATED A BIZARRE PARALLEL UNIVERSE THAT CAN DEVOUR THE WORLD. LOWMAN, THE "HEAD" OF THE TOTEM, NEEDS SOME "MUSCLE" AS HE CALLS IT, TO BRING THEM BACK. HE FINDS A PENCIL ON THE DESK AND MAKES IT COME TO LIFE. THE PENCIL TELLS LOWMAN TO CALL HIM WOODY, WILLLLLLLLD WOODY. LOWMAN EXPLAINS WHAT HAS HAPPENED WITH HIS TOTEM BROTHERS AND NOW WOODY GOES INTO THE PARALLEL UNIVERSE, DIMENSION BY DIMENSION, AND ROUNDS UP LOWMAN'S TOTEM BROTHERS.

IN THIS GAME, YOU DESTROY YOUR ENEMIES BY JUMPING ON TOP OF THEM AND WOODY CAN ALSO WIPE THEM OUT WITH HIS ERASER. YOU CAN ERASE CERTAIN WALLS TO GET THROUGH THEM AND YOU CAN ALSO ERASE BOXES THAT MOST OF THE TIME TELEPORT IF YOU PRESS DOWN. OTHER BOXES CONTAIN ITEMS. YOU ALSO CAN SKETCH THINGS AND THEY WILL COME TO LIFE, BUT YOU CAN ONLY DO THIS TWICE BECAUSE WOODY SHRINKS VERY QUICKLY FROM DOING THIS. THERE ARE ALSO POWER-UPS THAT MAKE YOU GROW AGAIN.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1B9A3B55</hash>
		<image>./images/Wild Woody (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Wild Woody (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Wild Woody (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wild Woody (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12747" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wing Commander (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wing Commander</name>
		<desc>THE CONFEDERATION HAVE BEEN AT WAR WITH THE KILRATHI FOR THE PAST 20 YEARS, AND YOU'RE JUST NOW JOINING THE VEGA CAMPAIGN. YOU'RE A 2ND LIEUTENANT JUST OUT OF THE ACADEMY, WITH SOME GOOD WORK UNDER YOUR BELT. YOU'RE POSTED TO TIGER'S CLAW, THE FLAGSHIP OF THE CONFEDERATION FLEET.  WILL YOU HELP THE CONFEDERATION TO VICTORY, OR GO DOWN IN INFAMY? 

WING COMMANDER IS A SPACE COMBAT SIMULATOR INTERSPERSED WITH SHIPBOARD DIALOGS. ONBOARD THE SHIP, YOU CAN SAVE/LOAD GAME, VISIT THE BAR TO GET THE LATEST GOSSIP, OR GO ON TO THE NEXT MISSION BRIEFING, AND THE 3D SPACE COMBAT PART. 

THE 3D SPACE COMBAT HAVE YOU SITTING IN THE COCKPIT, WHERE YOU CONTROL THE CRAFT LIKE ROLL, TURN, UP/DOWN, AFTERBURNER, AS WELL AS FIRE GUNS AND LAUNCH MISSILES. THERE ARE FOUR DIFFERENT CRAFTS ON THE CONFED SIDE, EACH WITH DIFFERENT FLIGHT CHARACTERISTICS AND ARMAMENT. YOU WILL HAVE A WINGMAN ON EACH MISSION, AND YOU SHOULD KEEP THE WINGMAN ALIVE AS THE WINGMAN WILL HELP YOU IF YOU ISSUE THE RIGHT ORDERS. YOU CAN ALSO TAUNT THE ENEMY. YOU'LL BE FIGHTING SEVERAL DIFFERENT TYPES OF ENEMY FIGHTERS AND CAPITAL SHIPS, AND EVEN COMBAT A FEW KILRATHI ACES. 

WHEN THE MISSION IS COMPLETE, LAND BACK ONBOARD THE SHIP AND GET READY FOR THE NEXT ONE. THE CAMPAIGN TREE HAVE BOTH WINNING AND LOSING PATHS. 

WING COMMANDER FEATURED A HYBRID BITMAP/3D GRAPHICS  ENGINE THAT ALLOWED EVEN 286'S TO DISPLAY DETAILED 3D GRAPHICS TO AN EXTENT NEVER BEFORE POSSIBLE. WITH EMS AVAILABLE, IT CAN DISPLAY EVEN MORE DETAILED GRAPHICS AND IN-COCKPIT ANIMATIONS.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Origin Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Origin Systems</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9FE41F50</hash>
		<image>./images/Wing Commander (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Wing Commander (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Wing Commander (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wing Commander (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12832" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wirehead (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wirehead</name>
		<desc>WIREHEAD HAS YOU CONTROLLING NED HUBBARD, A MAN WITH A WIRELESS CONTROLLER IMPLANTED IN HIS BRAIN, VIA YOUR GENESIS JOYPAD.

THE BAD GUYS ARE CHASING AFTER NED FOR HIS "MIND IMPLANT", AND OF COURSE, THE ONLY WAY TO GET IT IS TO OPEN HIS HEAD. REMINISCENT OF DRAGON'S LAIR, A PATH WILL OPEN UP, AND YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE THE RIGHT DIRECTION OR NED GETS IT. 

THE SETS AND LOCATIONS ARE PROBABLY THE LARGEST SCOPE EVER FOR A FMV GAME, WITH REAL LIFE CHASE SEQUENCES AND STUNTS THAT TAKE THE PLAYER THROUGH AREAS LIKE THE QUEEN MARY, A SALOON FIGHT, AN AIRPLANE, A WATER RAFT, MULTIPLE CAR CHASES, AND EVEN WRESTLING WITH A BEAR!</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19950901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7F0BD7C3</hash>
		<image>./images/Wirehead (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Wirehead (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Wirehead (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wirehead (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12787" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wolfchild (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wolfchild</name>
		<desc>O DR. KAL MORROW, ESPECIALISTA EM PESQUISA GENÉTICA E CRIAÇÃO DE HÍBRIDOS DE HUMANOS E ANIMAIS, FOI SEQUESTRADO E SUA FAMÍLIA BRUTALMENTE ASSASSINADA PELA ORGANIZAÇÃO TERRORISTA CHIMERA. SEU FILHO SOBREVIVENTE, SAUL, DECIDE VINGAR SUA FAMÍLIA. USANDO A PESQUISA DE SEU PAI, ELE SE TRANSFORMA EM LOBISOMEM E PARTE PARA ENCONTRAR A BASE DE CHIMERA E DERROTAR SEU LÍDER, KARL DRAXX. COMO SAUL, É SEU TRABALHO PERCORRER CINCO ÁREAS DIFERENTES NO CAMINHO PARA O DRAXX. QUANDO SAUL COLETA POWER-UPS SUFICIENTES, ELE SE TRANSFORMA EM SUA FORMA DE LOBO E GANHA UM ATAQUE DE DISPARO PSÍQUICO ESPECIAL, QUE PODE SER MELHORADO COLETANDO MAIS POWER-UPS. NO ENTANTO, SE SAUL PERDER A SAÚDE, ELE VOLTA A SUA FORMA HUMANA E SÓ TEM SEUS PUNHOS PARA LUTAR CONTRA OS NUMEROSOS INIMIGOS.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3DD813C3</hash>
		<image>./images/Wolfchild (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Wolfchild (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Wolfchild (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wolfchild (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="12758" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wonder Dog (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wonder Dog</name>
		<desc>WONDER DOG IS A SIDE-SCROLLING PLATFORM GAME FEATURING A DOG WITH SUPER JUMPING ABILITY AND POWERFUL THROWING STARS.  WONDER DOG HAS THESE ABILITIES BECAUSE HE IS NOT FROM EARTH, BUT FROM PLANET K-9. WHEN WONDER DOG WAS A PUP, K-9 SCIENTISTS SENT HIM TO EARTH TO ESCAPE THE IMPENDING INVASION FROM THE PITBULLY ARMADA. NOW, ARMED WITH THE WONDER SERUM, WONDER DOG MUST FIGHT HIS WAY BACK TO LIBERATE K-9.

THIS GAME FEATURES A VARIETY OF COLORFUL STAGES, SEVERAL HIDDEN BONUS ROUNDS, AND A LARGE BOSS CHARACTER AT THE END OF NEARLY EVERY LEVEL.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JVC</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6B5B2371</hash>
		<image>./images/Wonder Dog (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Wonder Dog (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/Wonder Dog (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wonder Dog (USA).mp4</video>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game id="58727" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./World Cup USA '94 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>World Cup USA 94</name>
		<desc>FOR THE THIRD WORLD CUP IN SUCCESSION, US GOLD HAD THE LICENSE TO PRODUCE THE OFFICIAL GAME. THEY ENTRUSTED TIERTEX WITH THE TASK, WHO PRODUCED A TOP-DOWN GAME RECREATING THE FULL TOURNAMENT. AS WELL AS THE 24 TEAMS WHO QUALIFIED FOR THE TOURNAMENT, OTHER</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tiertex Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>DA5BBBBD</hash>
		<image>./images/World Cup USA '94 (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/World Cup USA '94 (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/World Cup USA '94 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/World Cup USA '94 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="12789" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./WWF Rage in the Cage (USA).chd</path>
		<name>WWF Rage in the Cage</name>
		<desc>WWF RAGE IN THE CAGE LETS PLAYERS CHOOSE FROM 30 UNIQUE WWF SUPERSTARS INCLUDING THE UNDERTAKER, YOKOZUNA, BRET HART, BAM BAM BIGELOW, SHAWN MICHAELS, RAZOR RAMON AMONG MANY MORE.  EACH SUPERSTARS HAS THEIR OWN STRENGTHS AND WEAKNESSES AND HAS A PERSONALIZED FINISHER SUCH AS THE TOMBSTONE FOR THE UNDERTAKER, SWEET CHIN MUSIC FOR SHAWN MICHAELS, ETC., ALONG WITH THE STANDARD SUPLEXES, BODY SLAMS.

THERE ARE A PLETHORA OF GAME MODES TO CHOOSE FROM INCLUDING A REGULAR SINGLE-FALLS MATCH, TAG TEAM, 6-MAN TAG TEAM, BATTLE ROYAL AND THE GAMES DREADED NAMESAKE, THE STEEL CAGE.  THE MAIN GAMEPLAY IS REMINISCENT OF WWF ROYAL RUMBLE WITH THE LOOK AND FEEL BUT FEATURES ENHANCED AUDIO AND GRAPHICS UTILIZING THE SEGA CD'S CAPABILITIES.</desc>
		<rating>0.15</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>15320117</hash>
		<image>./images/WWF Rage in the Cage (USA).png</image>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/WWF Rage in the Cage (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./marquee/WWF Rage in the Cage (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/WWF Rage in the Cage (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA).chd</path>
		<name>3 Ninjas Kick Back</name>
		<desc>3 NINJAS KICK BACK É UM TRADICIONAL JOGO DE PLATAFORMA, BASEADO NO FILME 3 NINJAS CONTRA-ATACAM. CADA UM DOS TRÊS NINJAS TEM ARMAS E HABILIDADES ÚNICAS. OS TRÊS PODEM CORRER, AGUACHAR, RASTEJAR, SUBIR, PULAR E PENDURAR EM ÁRVORES, CORDAS, ETC. VOCÊ ENCONTRARÁ MUITOS OBSTÁCULOS E INIMIGOS, TANTO REGULARES QUANTO CHEFÕES, QUE VOCÊ TERÁ QUE SUPERAR E VENCER.</desc>
		<image>./images/3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./marquee/3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA).png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190304T031420</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bram Stoker's Dracula (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bram Stoker's Dracula</name>
		<desc>VAGAMENTE BASEADO NO FILME DE 1992 DE MESMO NOME, OS JOGADORES ASSUMEM O PAPEL DE JONATHAN HARKER, CUJA MISSÃO É DESTRUIR "A HORRÍVEL CRIATURA CONHECIDA COMO DRÁCULA DE UMA VEZ POR TODAS", VISITANDO MUITOS DOS LOCAIS DO FILME E LUTANDO CONTRA OS INIMIGOS ALI LOCALIZADOS. .

ESTE JOGO DE SEGA CD É UM TÍTULO DE AÇÃO SIDE-SCROLLING QUE FAZ USO DE FUNDOS DIGITALIZADOS (ÀS VEZES COM EFEITOS INTERESSANTES), ATORES / OBJETOS DIGITALIZADOS, REPRODUÇÕES DE VOZ ANTES DE CADA NÍVEL E CENAS DE FULL MOTION VIDEO DO FILME.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bram Stoker's Dracula (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Bram Stoker's Dracula (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./marquee/Bram Stoker's Dracula (USA).png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Bram Stoker's Dracula (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190304T031439</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Android Assault - The Revenge of Bari-Arm (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Android Assault: The Revenge of Bari-Arm</name>
		<desc>LANÇADA PELO PLANETA ALIENÍGENA ZIAS, UMA ARMADA DE ANDRÓIDES ESMAGOU A FROTA ESPACIAL CONVENCIONAL TERRESTRE. DESESPERADA E DERROTADA, AS NAÇÕES UNIDAS DA TERRA NÃO TÊM ESCOLHA SENÃO CONTRA-ATACAR COM SUA PRÓPRIA MÁQUINA DE LUTA VIVA, BARI-ARM. ATUALIZE AS ARMAS PARA OBTER O INCRÍVEL PODER DE FOGO DO THUNDERCRACKER, BURNING WAVE E CHASE CANNON.</desc>
		<image>./images/Android Assault - The Revenge of Bari-Arm (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Android Assault - The Revenge of Bari-Arm (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./marquee/Android Assault - The Revenge of Bari-Arm (USA).png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./boxart/Android Assault - The Revenge of Bari-Arm (USA).png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Big Fun Games</publisher>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190304T031618</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
